<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	 <string id="bm_donald_desc">Politician, Commander-In-Chief, father. Has an ambition to serve this great nation for 8 years. A talkative man, no doubt.$NL;$NL;The 45th is one of the most controversial presidents in history. Among criminals however, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_dallas_rising">Risen Dallas Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_metalhead_desc">The origin of the Metalhead is unclear.$NL;$NL;It looks more of a helmet than a mask. It has spikes pointing out of it and looks very much like a pimped out gas mask made of iron. It&apos;s unclear if it protects the wearer from any gas or melee weapons however.$NL;$NL;It looks pretty rad though.$NL;$NL;This mask is Poetry Jam mask. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_02_desc">This cap may look like a normal, standard-issue M43 field cap. And you may think such humble headgear is an unusual choice for a man as vain as Wolfgang. But this cap holds special meaning for him. It may surprise you that Wolfgang can truly love. Pinned inside is a picture of his beloved. For whom he fights the good fight.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r700_b_medium">Medium Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_02_desc">Robot wars are easy to make fun of. Dead things that fight other dead things. But as the AI evolved, things turned real. Soldiers like Vizor played a crucial role in the mayhem orchestrated by long dead humans. Humans who pushed the button, but failed to experience the consequences. As robots turned against robots, soldiers like Vizor rose, and those with a heartbeat became a memory. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_06">Mega War</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_12_desc">Make both cops and civilians think they are in a 1960s horror movie as you unleash the sheer terror of this mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_player_style">Preview Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gcm">Golden Chains</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_croupier_rake">Croupier&apos;s Rake</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_smosh_01">Community 2</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pirate_skull_desc">In &apos;Buccaneers Ahoy!&apos;, these swashbuckling undead heisters terrorized the treasure-laden galleons of the Caribbean for years, proving forever that....pirates arrrrrrrrrrrr cool.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shillelagh">Clover&apos;s Shillelagh</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_asval_b_proto">Prototype Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_shuno">XL 5.56 Microgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_01_desc">Our darling Fluffedup is gone. He&apos;s 95 years old, and part of our family. Fluffedup is a happy little individual who&apos;s absolutely not been trying to throw himself into the blender or off the roof several times. We just want to keep him forever, and never let him go. So it&apos;s super important that we get him back to us, to our home where he lives and loves and absolutely doesn&apos;t hate!</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_casual_desc">No one will see you coming over the dunes of sand.</string>
	 <string id="bm_cs_continental_coin_cost">$cost; Continental Coins</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_item_locked">Not available</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dawg_desc">Such mask. Much disguise. Very robber.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_winchester1874">Repeater 1874 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_crimson">Micro Laser</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_remove_mask">Return mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oliver_desc">&quot;And the nominees for The Greatest Heisters In The World are.....&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mason_vanguard_veteran">Mason Vanguard Veteran</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ace">Ace</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jaw">The Jaw</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_02">Canis Lupus</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_total">Total</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_smoke_screen_grenade">Requires the Sicario Perk Deck Equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_micstand">Microphone Stand</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_switch_reticle">Switch reticle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_c96">Broomstick Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_aziz_desc">If you think that clocking your enemy on the head when they don&apos;t see you coming is unsporting, why not use this flashlight to shine right in their eyes obnoxiously before you let &apos;em have it?</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_clean">Alabama Razor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_war">War</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_slot_lever">Jackpot</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_washington">The 1st</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_myh_desc">Duke is a man of culture, virtue and stone-hard composure. Thus his mask has been modeled after the great historical statues as a reflection of his personality. The mask is a window into the mind and heart of this determined agent of sophisticated crime, elegant and unbreakable in the face of any heist.$NL;$NL;A big draw for Duke is his love of mystery- you never really know what&apos;s inside the safe until you open it, or behind the painting until you take it out of the frame. And with the Payday Gang, the biggest mystery may be just around the corner...</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tonys_revenge_desc">The near-perfect predator. Tigers are immensely strong, yet fast. They are brutal, yet patient. They can stalk silently, before exploding into violence. The perfect killing machine. Despite this, the tiger is in decline. Poachers prize the tiger penis in traditional medicine. So don&apos;t get taken alive.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sokol">Sokol</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_invader">Invader</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_usp_co_comp_2">Velocity .45</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_blue_desc">Bluer, but just as durable as the black version of this glove.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_colt_1911">Crosskill Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tonys_revenge">Tony&apos;s Revenge</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jaw_desc">Protect your glass chin with a metal jaw.$NL;$NL;The only thing you will be chewing from now on with your jaw is law enforcers, right?</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_four_desc">Like a sword hidden in the user&apos;s hand the shuriken is a deadly weapon and perfectly silent. First made of nails and needles, the throwing star has had a long history filled with blood and battle. These modern stars of stainless steel will pose a lethal threat to anyone in front of you, and as long as you can find them there will be no stopping you.$NL;$NL;The Shurikens have been coated in poison which deals damage over time and has a chance to interrupt enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_blue">Plastic Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_05_desc">Every war requires executioners. Not a simple soldier, but someone who can take a life with a threatening demeanor. Someone working for the &quot;system&quot;, who blindly follow orders. Skull was one of those. Someone who, tirelessly disconnected robot after robot, war criminals and everyone else deemed &quot;dangerous&quot; to the &quot;cause&quot;. </string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_m14_scopemount">Scope Mount</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_materials">Material</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_anonymous_desc">Don the mask, become anonymous and do as you wish.$NL;$NL;Do it because you mean it, do it because you were told to, or do it for the lulz.$NL;$NL;Do all the things that regular society will not allow you. Like robbing a bank.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_angry">Angry Baby</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_rambo">Trautman Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_01">Navy Beanie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spackle_desc">Once a well renowned circus clown Spackle was the best make-up artist in the scene. Known for her skill and ability to make people look so unlike themselves, she became obsessed with the art.$NL;$NL;With her own face as canvas she tirelessly applied layer after layer, each becoming more twisted. She was sent to an asylum after killing five people during their make-up process.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_standard_issue">Standard Issue Part</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_none_desc">This is the heister&apos;s default outfit with the selected armor.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_locked_erma">Complete the &quot;Prepare for War&quot; Aldstone&apos;s Heritage Job to unlock.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_serbu_s_nostock_short">Tactical Shorty Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_tree_stump">Tree Stump</string>
	 <string id="bm_cloaker_desc">Somehow bending the laws of physics, the special unit of the WPD nicknamed the &quot;Cloaker&quot; is the bane of every bad guy trying to prove they can do things on their own. The first Cloaker is rumored to just have been a regular SWAT officer who nobody wanted to team up with. Might be because he was a fucked up killing machine with kung fu-kicks and bullets flying everywhere around him. He used excessive force almost always and left any combat tactic behind together with his unit. But he produced results, so the brass kept him on and made him train like minded individuals.$NL;$NL;Activate Night Vision Mode by holding down the Fire Mode button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_ait_01">Community Safe 8</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_t800">Infamy Leather</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sr2_m_quick">Speed Pull Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor2">British Paratrooper</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kangee">Apache Mystic</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_contraband">Little Friend 7.62 Assault Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_01">Klaus</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_cobray">Akimbo Jacket&apos;s Piece</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saiga_fg_holy">Hollow Handle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fdm">The Fedora</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gumbo_desc">Little is known about the man known as the devouring clown, but for a long time people believed that his red eyes were part of his outfit. Needless to say, they were wrong. Now people fear the red eyed clown with a laugh so evil it makes even the most seasoned badasses quiver in fear.$NL;$NL;Word on the street is that he haunts alleyways in a demonic shape looking for something... Or someone. All that is known is that people end up dead, more dead than you thought possible...</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dragan">Dragan</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_04_desc">A fast and agile killer, sending blades flying through the air. Always ready to strike. A popular killer with many fans.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghx">Golden Hoxton</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_tomahawk">Survival Tomahawk</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_aa12">Steakout 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_no_mod">Preview weapon without mod</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_punk">The Being</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oro">Oro</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_g_ergo">Ergo Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_06_desc">With this helmet, make the cops think they are being assaulted by the God of All 80s Metal Bands!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45rds_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r870_waves">Big Kahuna</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_red">Teotihuacan</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saw_smosh">Loading</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saw_m_blade_sharp">Sharp Blade</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_hur_desc">A sharp axe is never wrong, and as this one is especially good when throwing, it got popular amongst bikers. Riding a bike, can sometimes be dangerous, and you need some &quot;protection&quot;. So this sporting axe suddenly ran out of stock as bikers found it extra handy for highway battles.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_medusa_desc">A hideous visage, snakes for hair, a petrifying gaze and a hate for men. Her gazing eyes still sends chills down spines... But this is just a mask, right?</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_mac10">Akimbo Mark 10 Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_bodybags_bag_desc">To use the Body Bag Case, you place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed, it cannot be moved, but it can be used by you and your crew by holding $BTN_INTERACT; to gain a body bag.$NL;$NL;The Body Bag Case has limited uses. You can see how many uses are left by looking at the Body Bag Case. The Body Bag Case carries additional bags, used for the transportation of corpses during stealth.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hoxton_desc">The mask of Hoxton.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_corey_desc">When you&apos;re the most delicious lunch on the savannah, you have to be fast, agile and cunning if you&apos;re going to survive. Corey is all of these things. Zebras are also peaceful, gentle and herbivorous. Corey is none of these things.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_chef">Psycho Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_cqc_desc">Originally a farming tool that saw battle in the hands of the shadow assassins of the east. The kunai can easily be carried in the hand, mouth, belt or hocked on a finger to always be at the ready.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hectors_helmet_desc">When you rat out the Payday Gang, you need to expect some form of retribution. And the gang aren&apos;t big on wagging fingers and a stern telling off. You can expect bullets, and plenty of them. This hard hat is old school riot cop tech - heavy iron, fronted with reinforced glass. Good luck getting through it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_desperado_desc">There are tales of wandering gunmen, dressed as musicians. Gunmen that fight against injustice, taking revenge for tragedies that have affected those who are not capable of doing so themselves. Yeah, that description doesn&apos;t really apply to the Payday Gang, does it?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_01_desc">A pilot in the Royal Air Force went down during WW2 a few miles outside Bialystok, Poland. Considered K.I.A, he was later found deep in the Bialowieza Forest where he&apos;d survived on fish, roots and animals he managed to caught - alive and well but madness had sunk his teeth into him. He&apos;d been forced to amputate his left leg. But still managed to survive without infections. A small hut was also found, together with salvaged parts from his aircraft. He was found in 1978.</string>
	 <string id="heist_contact_jimmy">Jimmy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_fox_desc">The Fox - slickest and slyest of all predators. No locks can keep you out, no defensive plan can withstand your guile and artifice. You will take what you want and leave everyone wondering who did it, or if it even happened at all.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kawaii_desc">Lovable, cute, adorable, cool and hip, charming, non-threatening, innocent, happy-go-lucky.$NL;$NL;These are words not commonly used in criminology.$NL;$NL;Because of you, they now are.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_daft">Android</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chains_clean">Chains Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_xmas_tuxedo">Dapper Dashing Holiday</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_black_solid">Solid Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_t1micro">The Professional&apos;s Choice Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_body_standard_black">Heat Treated Body</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_1911_co_2">Aggressor Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_locked_shock">Complete the Heavy Metal Achievement!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_g_mgrip">Straight Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_fg_standard_green">Enhanced Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nun_town">The Nun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_03">Retro Wolf</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_02">The Super Villain Moustache</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_buy_new_mask">Buy new mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_pis_medium_slim">Asepsis Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor3">Russian Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_08_desc">Raptor was a fighter pilot. Hooked into the central hub on each plane he flew, he steered with certainty. It became a matter of accumulated knowledge. Even though all pilots got the same software installed - an AI learns. And somehow, Raptor managed to stay alive enough to keep his knowledge. The Hive Mind was off limits to fighter pilots, as they could be captured and hacked when they crossed into enemy territory. But Raptor learned to be the best at taking out enemy bases without hesitation. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_01_desc">On gloomy nights when the moon is bright, one might witness how The Clawer emerges from the watery depths. It yearns for fresh meat and won&apos;t stop until its hunger is still. The Clawer is one of those urban myths that campfire teens tell - just before The Clawer strikes. Afterwards, it returns to the deep. Hibernating until its stomach growls yet again.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker">Hardtail</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_gray_dark_red">Gray / Dark Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_02">Golden Hour</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_deltaforce_desc">4th Domestic Operation Group-force Enforcers-Alpha (4th DOGE-A), popularly ridiculed as Alpha Force, is a U.S. Army component of the Joint Common Operations Command. Their reputation is pretty poor and have become a less and less respected force to deal with.$NL;$NL;One of the members probably dropped this helmet when he fled from you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_hare_desc">Mad as March Hare. As they stare into your crazed yellow eyes, they&apos;d better hand the cash over quick. Then take the money and run. No one outruns a hare.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_04">The Officer&apos;s Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shepheard_body_short">Short Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_sort_option">Sort by: $sort;</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_bloodhand">Smeared</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m60">M60 Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baitface_desc">The Funnyman knows how to make people laugh. The Funnyman might go too far and take a hit or two. Beware though, because a person who can control others laughter knows how to get the last laugh.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_1911_css">Castor and Pollux</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_cobalt_blue_solid">Solid Cobalt Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_continental_desc">Heisters are constantly judged by those they deal with. Wear the wrong tie to a meeting, and you might leave the place with a death mark on your head. Put on an off-the-rack suit to the boss&apos;s daughter&apos;s wedding and you might not get invited to the next high profile job. But gloves like these leave an impression that is neither good nor bad- just really unsettling and distracting. That&apos;s why Jimmy loves &apos;em, his lucky checkers.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_03">MOTH </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_01">Schneider</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_weapon_01">Sputnik Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_crimson_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_myh_begins">Duke Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_peacoat">The Casual Formal</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_churchill">British Bulldog</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_g_discrete">Discreet Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_concussion">Concussion Grenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_pgo_unlock">Buy the Tailor Pack 3 DLC to unlock</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_erma">Akimbo MP40 Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_unequip_deployable">Unequip deployable</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_02_desc">Wax on, wax off. Twirl it to your heart&apos;s content as you disappear into the foggy night with your bounty and laugh.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_01">Lust</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gage_blade">The Gage Blade</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_dallas">Pocket Patriot </string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_sell_tradable">Sell On Community Market</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_x400v">Combined Module</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_slaughterhouse_desc">Never say no to a good tactical vest and combat pants. With lots of pockets. You can never have enough pockets. Early in the career of the Payday gang, Chains spent the better part of two months getting this suit together, testing, configuring and researching to make sure that it would perform optimally during a heist. Now, so many years later, it has changed very little and is still a favorite getup to use on a physically demanding heist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_04_desc">Rivet is American, and Americans value tradition. From the office of the President, to the lowliest scum-sucker in the land, tradition matters. So if you&apos;re going to stick a gun in a chump&apos;s face and demand they &quot;hand it over&quot; you better damn well know your history. Like Jesse James, like Billy The Kid, you wear a bandana.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_shrew">Akimbo Crosskill Guard Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ben_s_collapsed">Collapsed Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_empty_weapon_slot">Empty weapon slot</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_08_desc">Devils and demons alike will tremble in awe as they behold the glory of any heister that chooses to don this mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_2">Lightweight Ballistic Vest</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_armors">Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_spa">John Wick Heists</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled_white_desc">No one saw you enter, no one saw you leave.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_facepaint_rainbow">Magic</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_smg_m45_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_uzi_fg_rail">Tactical Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_mp5_cat">Fluorescent</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_oxide">Rezkoye</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_04">Jamaican Nightmare</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smoker_desc">Only a true Technician could come up with a mask like this.$NL;$NL;Featuring a state of the art air filtration system, the mask can double as a chemist&apos;s hood in those unlikely &quot;must cook meth&quot; scenarios.$NL;$NL;This mask is an Infamy tree reward. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_smosh">Wiseguy</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_blain">Blain</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_04_desc">Liberty. Liberty for all those heisters that have fallen and been sent to prison. Liberty for all that gold which sits sadly in dark basement vaults of banks. Liberty for the spirit of enterprise, the will to take what you want, the rule of the gun. Liberty for those seeking a bigger payday.</string>
	 <string id="menu_l_global_value_sparkle">This is a Housewarming party item!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_scorpion_nin">Last Night</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_boxcutter">Utility Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_buck_01">Biker Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_hare">The Hare</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_tag_team_desc">A small gas dispenser that temporarily enhance the body&apos;s senses and provide a healing effect for two allies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_jowi_mxs">Scorpion</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_roman_desc">Stoic and Noble, the steel face of a warrior from the greatest empire represents tradition and values at a time when one faces the greatest enemy. A Centurion of Crime.net can embody the strength and power of ancient Rome with this piece of metal artistry.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_outfits">Armor &amp; Outfits</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_pis_medium">Standard Issue Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_03_desc">Every war has its traitor. Moth was one of them. A sentinel robot assembled to retrieve information - by any means necessary. But hierarchy and power are often coveted. Wars breed corruption, and Moth followed his logic and switched sides - causing millions of robots to disconnect. Celebrated by one side and hated by another - Moth came to be one of the pawns that turned the war. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ninja_hood_desc">A simple piece of cloth tied around their heads will transform anyone, be it beggar, farmer or common man into a ninja. A shadow among shadows, a dagger in the dark. He can be fierce or stealthy and can be anyone in a crowd. He does what he sets out to do and then disappears.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_primaries">Primary</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_boombox_desc">According to the brochure, Alesso&apos;s Boom Box features include &quot;No batteries to slay your vibe, sound insulation to keep suckas from hearing your beats and full-face armor to keep cops from checking your clock.&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_famas_g_retro">G2 Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_swat">SWAT Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_punk">The Vicious</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_boxing_gloves">OVERKILL Boxing Gloves</string>
	 <string id="bm_sparkle_party_desc">Party hats never get old. It&apos;s an essential accessory to any fun event, be it a festivity of misdeeds or a celebration of moving into a new home. Strap one on and loosen that tie. It&apos;s party time. Excellent.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_firemask">Firefighter&apos;s Helmet</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sokol_begins">Sokol Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_3">Ballistic Vest</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mrm">Mega Rust</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kage_desc">The kage mask was said to be haunted, originally from a kabuki theater in Osaka where the actor fell down dead on stage while wearing the mask. The last thing he said was &quot;No, I will not kill them, I will not&quot;. Legend says that the kage mask will kill whoever wears it if its thirst for blood is not satisfied.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_tux">Tuxedo</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pazuzu_desc">Pazuzu was the king of the wind demons according to ancient Babylonian mythology. Legends also tell of him as a beastial behemoth fighting groups of adveturers in far away lands, and some even say he walked the earth as an immortal warrior in human form.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_scalper">Scalper Tomahawk</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_g36_skf">Flames of Passion</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_dada_com">Matryoshka Grenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_wac">Lansquenet</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_smg_sho_peqbox_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_scarecrow">Mr. Sackcloth</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pitbull">Arnold</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_packrat_ns_extended">Contractor Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grant">The 18th</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_balaclava_desc">The weapons may change, the ideologies may shift and the accents may swap, but the balaclava has been a mainstay for the armed robber and terrorist for decades. Covering all but your steely, flint-like eyes and your cruel, twisted mouth, it keeps you warm when it&apos;s chilly too.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_swap_weapon">Swap Weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_m_long">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_dillan">Dillan</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_reflex">Speculator Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_hockey_desc">A tough hockey stick that is designed to be used on ice with a puck. It has however been proved to be effective off ice as well.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_04_desc">The friends you have right now, may not be all the friends you&apos;ll ever need. Don&apos;t miss out on a future gain by keeping new friends away.  It&apos;s easy to get lost in the desert. One wrong turn is all it takes. And when you do, those new friends might just be your ticket to an oasis.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_customize_player_style">Customize Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_04">Crazy Lou</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_boombox">Boom Box</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_sell">Sell weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_divided">Trickster Demon</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_orange">Plastic Orange</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_baaah">Raging Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_destroyer">Demonshank</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_green_dark">Jade Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_guppie_green_solid">Solid Guppie Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_unequip_weapon">Unequip weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_s_folding">Spartan Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_sad_seal">The Awkward Seal</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ak_m_quick">Speed Pull Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mp9_wac">Cossack</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_happy_desc">Ffff, gaga, bo, gaga bo GAGA GAGA? GAGAGAGA? GAGA? Gagag GOGOGO GAGA? GAGA! GOGO! Bah. Gaga bah gogo go.$NL;$NL;GAGA? GAGA! GOGO! Bah. GAGAGA? GAGA GOGO GAGAGA? GAGA! Gagaga gogoga. Fff.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brazil_baby_desc">GAGA? GAGA! GOGO! Boo! GAGAGA? GAGA GOGO GAGAGA? GAGA? GAGA!  GAGAGA? GAGA GAGAGA?$NL;$NL;GAGAGA? GAGAGAGOGO? Boo! BOOO! Gagagaga boo gaga.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_volt_desc">Being a snoopy lowlife, janitor David Davidson snuck around the military research facility he worked at, looking for something easy to steal. He found a door that he didn&apos;t have a key for. Curious, he kicked the door open and was instantly attacked by some kind of bright light. Somehow he survived the attack and got superhuman powers.$NL;$NL;With his new powers, he called himself Volt.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_system_m_high">High Temperature Mixture</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kangee_desc">The West that the white men entered was a land of mystery. A land populated with civilizations of warriors, who marked themselves, their lands and their mythologies with these sacred carvings.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1897_b_short">Ventilated Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_03">Dendron</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_tec9">Blaster 9mm Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_teal">Plastic Teal</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_carnotaurus">Alfred</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_body_tactic">Tactical Frame</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_greedy_the_elf_desc">Santa&apos;s elves have a tough job. No medical, dental and they endure the whip of Mrs. Claus, but at least they have these fucking sweet hats. </string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_grenade">Preview Throwable</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_ostry_desc">Kazaguruma, the Windmill, is a fast and deadly melee weapon that can slash through flesh as if it were butter.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_gloves">Preview Gloves</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_horned_king_desc">The Germanic Norse seafarers known as Vikings were fierce warriors during the late 8th to late 11th centuries. Equipped with their mighty axes and horned helmets, they stood tall and proud in the heat of battle. If you want to capture the spirit of these old fighters, this mask will do the job.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_flm">PNV - BriteNite</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_skin">Flesh</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_ranger_black">Ranger Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richard_returns_desc">Is this mask a reflection of a deep-seated psychological problem? Possibly a dissociative identity disorder? Schizophrenia? Trauma of a disturbed psyche? Or is it not a reflection at all, but instead something to cause them?</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_default_desc">Wolf walked into the record store, fully intent on buying, (as in actually paying for), the latest album by his favorite band. As the door closed behind him, a look of seldom-seen horror crossed his face. There wasn&apos;t a 12-inch cardboard record sleeve in sight! With a snarl, he stomped up to the track-suit wearing douchebag at the counter and grabbed his collar. &quot;Where are the fucking records?&quot;, he growled from under his beard. The poor guy managed to mumble something about CDs being superior to vinyl, whereupon Wolf proceeded to shoot many holes in the &quot;superior&quot; discs of plastic lining the shelves...</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shrunken">The Shrunken Head</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_ppk_g_laser">Laser Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_saiga">IZHMA 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_china_sfs">Gator Masher </string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_tomahawk_desc">Historically used as a general purpose tool, for throwing at people and the occasional hand-to-hand melee. A weapon with which almost any crook can attain some degree of proficiency. Only through proper heisting can one begin to realize the full potential of the tomahawk as both a tool and weapon. But mostly weapon.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_coal_css">Prototype</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_fir_com">Incendiary Grenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_weapon_skins">Weapon skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sputnik">Sputnik</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_famine">Famine</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_great">Great Sword</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_paint2">Jagged Stripes</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_alphabetic">Alphabetic</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_irondoom">Doctor Crime</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tiara_desc">Okay, it doesn&apos;t hide your face and it is certainly not going to stop any bullets whizzing your way....but, damn. You&apos;re going to look like the belle of the ball wearing Mrs Volkov&apos;s wedding tiara.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robberfly">Asilidae</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_dlc">dlc</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_clowns_in">The Insane</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_obama_desc">Politician, Commander-In-Chief, father. Served this great nation for 8 years. A hopeful man, no doubt..$NL;$NL;The 44th was one of the most ambitious presidents in history. Among criminals however, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_moneybundle_desc">Bundling money together with a strap is as old as money itself. Beating people with money is something rich people and pimps have been doing for a very long time.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_brass_knuckles_desc">Knuckle style weapons have been used all over the world for hundreds of years. Brass knuckles concentrate the punch&apos;s force by directing it toward a harder and smaller area, increasing the chances of tissue disruption. Hit hard enough and you&apos;ll even fracture some bones.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pirate_skull">Pirate Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_wac_01">John Wick Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_nin_01">Community Safe 9</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_01_desc">There is something for the distinguished heister in everyone. This vintage hat, made by famous hatters in New York, is sure to distract the gaze of any law enforcement officer.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pumpkin_king_desc">Legend has it that a boy named Jack was getting chased by some villagers from whom he had stolen, when he suddenly bumped into the Devil$NL;$NL;Jack was a clever little heister and managed to convince the devil that the loot he was carrying was worth to be shared. The Devil agreed and the two ran to the escape horses and got away.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_siltstone_fg_polymer">Lightweight Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_01_desc">Captain on the bridge! Guide your crew safely through the banks, and a favorable wind will lead you to great adventures. Strike the coast and take their treasure, then disappear over the horizon.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_galax">Professor Wrath</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_desert_twilight">Desert Twilight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_dallas">Power Patriot </string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_blue">Icy Hardtail</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_crazy_lion">Mad Lion</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_medusa">Medusa</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_quality_fair">Well-Used</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_panda">Jean-Claude</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_grayson">Masked Villain</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_02">Spirit Fox</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_punk_desc">This mask is based on the experiments of the peculiar Dr Rudolf Mastaba. A modern Prometheus, he sought to return life to the dead with the application of Industrial Revolution technology. Rumour suggests that he was partly successful - the undead rose, but had an insatiable appetite for wheat, barley and maize.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_agatha_vanguard_veteran">Agatha Vanguard Veteran</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mrm_desc">The Mega Rust mask is an evolved version of the original mask. It symbolises transcendence and catharsis.$NL;$NL;Thank you for your support.$NL;$NL;OVERKILL salutes you!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_surprise_desc">You got a war face! AAAAAAAAHH! That&apos;s a war face, let me see your war face!$NL;$NL;...$NL;$NL;Bullshit. You didn&apos;t convince me. let me see your REAL war face!$NL;$NL;...Actually, that one&apos;s pretty good...$NL;$NL;This mask is Poetry Jam mask. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ranger">Heister Sentry</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_04_desc">Combat and shooter games that simulate intense situations between players is a great way to keep up your skills in between jobs. Chains likes games that train your situational awareness and award skillfull play by gaining the upperhand in a fight.</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_first_aid_kit_desc">The first aid kit is a collection of supplies and equipment for use in giving first aid.$NL;$NL;To use the first aid kit, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed it cannot be moved, but it can be used by you and your crew by holding $BTN_INTERACT; to regain health.$NL;$NL;A deployed first aid kit can be used once and when it is consumed, it disappears.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_slimy_goat_desc">The dolphin is the most sinister and vicious heister in the animal kingdom, tricking everyone with its friendly and cute appearance. But it&apos;s all a facade! The dolphin only cares about itself and the loot, and won&apos;t hesitate a second to leave anyone behind. Caution is advised if you meet a fellow heister with this mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_happy">Happy Baby</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_molten_desc">Volcanos are usually bad news. A heister bearing these, is even badder news if you happen to be working at the place that&apos;s about to be robbed.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_coral_red_light_gray">Coral Red / Lightgray</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_01">Fancy Top Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_06_desc">It burns into your heart and tears the flesh from your skull, orange flames to contrast the color of an unquenchable need for more. How many trips back into the vault will you make until you are satisfied? How many weapons will make you happy? All of them! Maybe.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_old_hoxton_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Hoxton Reborn mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chef_hat">The Chef</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_fir_com_desc">The Incendiary Grenade is a nasty self igniting phosphorus container. It ignites after a few seconds, making it perfect for bouncing off walls towards your enemies. Upon ignition it causes serious damage - setting enemies ablaze.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bandit">Wild West Classic</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_heat">Hockey Heat</string>
	 <string id="bm_paycheck_dallas">Paycheck Dallas</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mosin_wolf">Lone Wolf</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_gloves">Gloves</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_galax_desc">Milhouse Anderson worked at a chemical plant handling dangerous chemical waste. As a prank, his friends thought it would be a good idea to lock him up in the room where they kept the dangerous chemical waste. What they didn&apos;t know was that the dangerous chemical waste was dangerous, and while being locked in for several hours, Milhouse was exposed to high levels of radiation and other bad stuff.$NL;$NL;When they finally let him out, he had become a super villain. He&apos;s been super angry ever since.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sombrero">The Sombrero</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_flames">The Inferno</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_10_desc">Prom queens ain&apos;t got nothin&apos; on the heister who wears this shiny piece of forehead decor. Rumor has it that the gemstones all came from a Perseid meteorite that fell to Earth in the 1800s.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_s_folding">Muldon Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_r93">R93 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_warm_yellow_purple">Warm Yellow / Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rabbit_desc">Graham enjoys long walks in the sun.$NL;$NL;Rabbits are small mammals that practically can be found anywhere. If confronted by a potential threat, rabbits will instantly freeze and warn others in the warren with powerful thumps on the ground.$NL;$NL;When fleeing, they hop in a zig-zag pattern, much like many Counter-Strike players do.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grendel">Rad Mutant</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_bmg">Advanced Combat Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_xpsg33_magnifier_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_yor">Fire Rooster</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_ecm_jammer_desc">To use the ECM Jammer, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed it cannot be moved and it will be active for 20 seconds.$NL;$NL;You can toggle the ECM Jammer by pressing $BTN_INTERACT;. The ECM Jammer then has a chance to incapacitate your enemies within a certain radius. When consumed, it stops working.$NL;$NL;An Electronic Countermeasure (ECM) is an electronic device designed to trick radar, sonar and other detection systems, easing your way towards your goal.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_saw_secondary">Requires the Portable Saw skill</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_saintsleather">Calling</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_microphone">Microphone</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mega_sydney_desc">The Mega Sydney mask is an evolved version of the original mask. It symbolises transcendence and catharsis.$NL;$NL;Thank you for your support.$NL;$NL;OVERKILL salutes you!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_wa2000_b_suppressed">Gedämpfter Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dripper_desc">The Dripper was made by atomization of a larger mass of liquid, somehow made into a hard material while retaining a smooth surface.$NL;$NL;Everyone who looks at it sees different things.$NL;$NL;What do you see?</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_jowi">Akimbo Chimano Compact Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_sad_seal_desc">That moment when you&apos;re going to finish off a Dozer but when you pull the trigger you&apos;re out of ammo. Or that moment when you&apos;re throwing the last bag straight into the sea. Or that moment when other robbers give you compliments about your mask but you didn&apos;t put any effort into it. Or that moment when someone is repairing the drill the same time as you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_croupier_rake_desc">An item for the sole use of pulling currency in? Perfect for you heisters! Show those pesky cops exactly why the house always wins.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_freedom">The Spear of Freedom</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_miami">The Sunny Rico</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_baka">Micro Uzi Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_serbu_s_solid_short">Police Shorty Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rudeolph">Rudelf</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_b_desc">Have you ever had that feeling when you have no mouth but feel the urge to scream?$NL;$NL;That is how you are going to feel if you are a civilian looking at a criminal wearing this mask, pointing a gun at you, shouting you to the floor.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_somber_woodland">Somber Woodland</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_set_preferred_to_slot">Set Preferred</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cloth_commander">Commander Crime</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_slayer">Slayer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_damage_control">Stoic&apos;s Hip Flask</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_mxs">Aztec</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dallas_clean_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Dallas mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_sinister">Sinister</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_model24">Potato Masher</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kawaii">Kawaii</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_infamy_lurker_desc">Teeth are scary. Big teeth are scarier. And giant sharp fang-like teeth suddenly gnashing out where they lurk in the darkness are downright shit-yourself-terrifying. With all of that in mind, can you think of a better mask to keep the civilians in line?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tall_goat_desc">The giraffe doesn&apos;t miss a thing, always in complete control of its surroundings, acting as the perfect &quot;look-out&quot; companion for heisting in the animal kingdom. Whatever it is, you&apos;ll see it coming miles away and the cops can forget to take you by surprise.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gasmask">The Gas Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_demonictender">Kenneth</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_6">Combined Tactical Vest</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_packrat">Akimbo Contractor Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_polymer_cs3">Crescent</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_wcc_not_owned">NOT OWNED$NL;To use this weapon skin you must find it in a $safe;, or purchase it from the community marketplace.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shuno_b_short">XS Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_default">DEFAULT</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_ord_cross">Cross</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45iron">Angled Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_box">Box Buddy Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_cqc_info">Knife with a poisoned tip that deals damage over time and has a chance to interrupt enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mrs_claus_desc">When Santa is flying through December skies, someone has to stay home and keep the elves in line. No-one does that better than the whip-cracking, cigar-smoking kommandant of the Claus household.</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_4">Heavy Ballistic Vest</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_mad_desc">Santa, more known as Santa Claus, Saint Nicholas, Father Christmas and Kris Kringle (?) is a man of epic proportions. Words like legendary, mythical, historical and folkloric best describe this beast of a man.$NL;$NL;This particular mask is the Furious Santa. It&apos;s worn by angry internet users and bad children who didn&apos;t get the presents they wanted. </string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_solus_clan_unlock">Join the The Solus Project Official Community Group on Steam to unlock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_boot_grunt">Ambush</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_01_desc">Interceptor model BX-99 was built to keep &quot;things in order&quot;. A mission with a lof to interpret. Roaming the streets, making sure that civilians are safe and that things are &quot;OK&quot;. This Interceptor took things too far as a situation occurred near a assembly factory. Some civilians came to harm, others destroyed, ammo slugs filled the air, and Interceptor did what it thought was absolutely necessary to not obstruct the assembly factory. Interceptor BX-99 with serial number 151010130807 was later disassembled. </string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_rota">Akimbo Goliath 12G Shotguns</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ammo_plural">Ammo Types</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_empty_weapon_slot_buy_info">Increase your reputation level to unlock new weapons.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saw_body_silent">Silent Motor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rage_demon">Flaming Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grin_desc">There once was a man and his brother. Together, they owned a successful company. One day, the man and his brother temporarily only had one client. The client got cold feet and wanted out. Rather than simply pulling out and having to pay a fine for breach of contract, the client starved the man and his brother&apos;s company to death.$NL;$NL;The man and his brother lost everything, and it is said that this mask was the very image of the man&apos;s facial expression the day that he went mad.</string>
	 <string id="bm_jar_head">Martial Law</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_xpsg33_magnifier">Riktpunkt Magnifier Gadget</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_old_hoxton_begins">Hoxton Reborn Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_winchester_b_suppressed">Outlaw&apos;s Silenced Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_7">Improved Combined Tactical Vest</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_purple_dark">Deep Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m4">CAR-4 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_05">Arcade Simian</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_falcon">The Falcon</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gentleman_marine">The Blue Swagger</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_buy_weapon_title">Buy $weapon_category;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_champion_dallas">The Champ</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_twins_desc">Used by Okinawan Law enforcers, the Sai could be offensive and defensive, and when heisting it&apos;s an perfect tool for dealing out quick blows to any opposition.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_03">Kokoshnik</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_cat_desc">Agile as a Cat, and lucky as one too, you will dare any heist and successfully breach any defenses. When the shit hits the fan, you will always dodge and land on your feet. There is no better way to spend your nine lives - a stone-cold killer is what you are and everyone knows it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_melee_weapons">Melee</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_cogs">Clockwork Gears</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ns_duck">Donald&apos;s Horizontal Leveller</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_01_desc">A good tactical game is the perfect way to prep before a big heist. Dallas prefers to kick-start his strategic mind with something difficult and calculating where you need to manage units and resources to achieve victory.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mateba">Matever .357 Revolver</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_red_crust">Crusty Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_aquired">Acquired</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_emblem4">Stripes Below</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_evil_desc">Bob Robertson worked at a purple stuff factory. The purple stuff factory was old and in need of reperations. Bob mentioned this to his supervisors but they ignored him. Bob kept on hardly working, playing pre-installed games on his operative system. One day when he was checking out early, cracks started to form in a container filled with purple stuff. Just when he went past, the container burst and Bob was drenched in purple stuff.$NL;$NL;When he got out of hospital, he had become a super villain. His face has been purple ever since.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_tecci_b_long">AML Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_mxs_01">Sangres Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_g22c">Chimano Custom Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_starvr_desc">Real life is dirty, uncomfortable, sticky, sweaty, stinky, it tastes bad and it leaves you old and broken. Screw that. The StarVR Headset lets you immerse yourself in a virtual world of incredible realism.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_doctor">The Doctor</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_sword_desc">Sharp, accurate and with high concealment, the Pen is your best friend when everything is depleted, and you want to puncture an aorta.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sydney_desc">Smirk, Grin, Sneer - call it what you want. As you see this smiling punker mask approaching it&apos;s not synonyms that&apos;ll run through your head - it&apos;s bullets. Sydney will make sure of it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled_white">Ghost Heister</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_body_conceal">Discreet Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_ns_bayonet_desc">Increases melee damage and knockdown while using weapon butt.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hog">The Hog</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tti_cs3">Frenzy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baba_yaga">Baba Yaga</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_baton_desc">Every heisters and law enforcers favorite weapon for crowd control and dispersal of non-compliant people. The advantages of a expandable baton over a fixed baton are numerous. Lightweight and effective, more versatile and looks more intimidating to any potential aggressor.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_czech_g_sport">Sicario Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_warm_yellow_light_blue">Warm Yellow / Light Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bullskull">Desert Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tiger">Tony</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_05">Pride</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goat_goat_desc">The goat doesn&apos;t get much respect in the animal kingdom, and often find themselves to be mocked by the other animals - but that works perfectly in their favor. Putting on this foolish mask might give you the same advantage and make the cops underestimate you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_uzi">Uzi Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rooster">Richard</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gentleman_veteran">Hunter&apos;s Elegance</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_m3x">Polymer Flashlight</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_hiphop">The Boom Bap</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_01">Mega Rad Mutant</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_03_desc">Most robbers choose this snug, concealing headwear to help them blend in with the night. Unfortunately, it won&apos;t do you much good to conceal yourself carrying all that equipment.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_dallas">Lafayette Hunter </string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pl14_b_comp">Prototype Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_02_desc">Look no further for a bad ass cherry to put on top of your Ice Cream of Minigun mayhem.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_reload">Reload Time</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dragan_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Dragan&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_characters">Character</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_dbd_deluxe_unlock">Buy the Dead by Daylight Deluxe Game to unlock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_andromeda">Augmentation</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_switchblade">Switchblade</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_strinch">The Strinch</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_quality">Quality</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fdm_desc">The fedora, the very height of fashion and class. Where the line is drawn between boys and men. Carry this classical headgear with the pride and resolve that it deserves. Feel the legacy and tradition of the millions of gentlemen and gangsters that wore a fedora throughout the ages.</string>
	 <string id="bm_dynamite_desc">Swedish engineer, Alfred Nobel, discovered dynamite and its effectiveness in blasting rock. But it was drunk prospector, Ol&apos; Kenneth, who discovered its effectiveness in blasting people.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_01_desc">It would be lovely to think Sterling earned the beret and badge through hard-training and combat. The truth, however, is that he saw how it impressed a couple of young fillies at the Officers Club. An invitation to step outside, a few dirty punches and a knocked out Colonel later, and Sterling had his very own red beret. And a couple of fillies. Smashing!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_solus_desc">Being a Planetary Tomb Guardian is a lonely job. But a job that must be done. Eons of time float by without a single living organism in sight. Stars and suns brighten the day and night. But solitude is a horrid thing. But then one day, a spacecraft breaks the silence and you are not alone anymore. Someone is visiting this planet you call home.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_01">Captain</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_tiger">Tiger Stripe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_old_hoxton">Hoxton Reborn</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kwm">Rhubarb</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_stick">Shepherd&apos;s Cane</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_rarity_rare">Rare</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rus_hat">Russian Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_weapon">Equip weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rubber_male_desc">The Male Mannequin.$NL;$NL;The face of an articulated doll used by tailors, dressmakers, artists, windowdressers and now bank robbers.$NL;$NL;They are most often used to display or fit clothing, but are also used to simulate how to teach first aid, CPR, tracheal intubation and now bank robbery.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_armor">Equip armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_upsdell_red_solid">Solid Upsdell Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_leupold">Theia Magnified Scope</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_male_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Ethan&apos;s mask as it looked before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tormentor_desc">A smile can hide the most murderous thought, but the eyes can never lie. Reading a person is mostly looking straight into their eyes. What&apos;s truly terrifying is people who wear their thoughts on their face and within a second it&apos;s hard for the beholder to suppress a scream.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sokol_desc">If playing as a grinder for the St Petersburg Bombers hockey team taught Sokol the value of one thing, it was the importance of a terrifying mask that protects his handsome Russian face.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_plainsrider_linked">The Link</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_miami_desc">Protection is, of course, just as much about going unnoticed as it is stopping bullets. The roomy folds of 1980s style suits offer ample concealment for weapons, and the variety of fabrics means you can adjust to the weather as needed. </string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_ballistic">Specialist Knives</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_customizable_weapon_color_desc">Add a custom color to your weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_huntsman">Mosconi 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_par_mxs">Moctezuma</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_basset_fg_short">Little Brother Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_item_amount">In stock: $amount;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_01">Retro Dallas</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_02">Co-Cop Ninja</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_ecm_jammer">ECM Jammer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp9_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_frag_desc">The frag grenade is a concept that has changed little from its inception. It is a thrown casing that explodes, sending shards and splinters away with such force they can slice through flesh, bone and light armor. Cheap and effective.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tounge">Mr. Smooth</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_punkleather">Horns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_devourer_desc">This mask, heavily inspired by the Great Old Ones that rule below the seas was recovered from a police storage where it had been kept since it was found during a raid on a murderous cult. It&apos;s monstrous look makes you wonder what beings lurk out in the dark.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_woodland_tech">Woodland Tech</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_b_e11">Heatsinked Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jake">Jake</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_water_spirit_desc">Brother of Tane, Tawhiri is the god of weather, most particularly violent storms and lightning. Bodhi experienced plenty of both, and it was during a particularly vicious explosion while reef-diving in Tuvalu that Bodhi gained a true appreciation for this powerful deity.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dallas_desc">The mask that everyone fears.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_arch_nemesis_desc">Nemesis, as defined by the dictionary$NL;$NL;Noun [ahrch nem-uh-seez]$NL;$NL;1. Something that a person cannot conquer, achieve, etc.: &quot;That Chinese buffet at lunch proved to be my arch-nemesis.&quot;$NL;2. An opponent whom a person cannot defeat.$NL;3. In classical mythology. The goddess of divine retribution.$NL;4. An agent or act of retribution or punishment.$NL;$NL;As defined by Hoxton: &quot;That fuckin&apos; dozer. He&apos;s my arch-fucking-nemesis. &apos;Orrible cunt!&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_glock_17">Chimano 88 Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_08">Mega Vlad Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ching_fg_railed">Custom Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clown_56_desc">This mask has a hideous appearance, a bony facial structure and dehydrated skin.$NL;$NL;It is the kind of mask gives you nightmares.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cursed_crown">The Cursed One</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_scrub">Scrubs</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_06_desc">Engineered to be as lethal as robotly possible. Drone was solely responsible for the Great Purge. Forever imprinted in all minds and historical dataservers. Drone had the skills needed to go beyond what was expected by a &quot;grunt&quot;. Someone who seemed disposable. but would prove invaluable. The Great Purge turned the war: sleeper cells got exposed, robots got disconnected, and the Hive Mind lost thousands of zettabytes. Drone became a statue to be gazed upon in Ming Ji Memorial Park. </string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_secondaries">Secondary</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_trip_mine_desc">To use the Trip Mine, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. The trigger laser can be toggled between explosive mode and sensor by pressing $BTN_INTERACT;.$NL;$NL;To use Shaped Charges, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed it will detonate within a few seconds. Trip Mines are basically traps that will hurt or kill enemies crossing the beam. Shaped Charges are commonly used to open safes and doors. Both are a good addition to all combat situations.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jimmy_duct">Jimmy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_butcher_desc">There are many rumours about the mad butcher from the east, one of them tells of a man who found such pleasure in butchering pigs that he slowly started to look like one.$NL;$NL;Working in a butchery as hot as hell itself his skin became disfigured with blisters and cuts, people tell of screams coming from inside... And not just the screams of pigs.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_cs4_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_05_desc">Robot Overlords from the Future rejoice! For thy leader has come, and is the bearer of many positively charged particles.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_baseballbat">Lucille Baseball Bat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lady_butcher">Lady Butcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_1">Two-piece Suit</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_detector">Metal Detector</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jake_desc">There&apos;s no such thing as a good snake, but even among the deadly serpents the cobra is bad news. The broad hood, when seen, is a display of threat - so run. Its long fangs can pierce elephant skin - so run. And just a drop of its venom can fell a dozer - so... look, basically, when you see this, just run. Because they also spit.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_happy">Happy Santa</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_trash">B.I.N.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_bananabike_desc">Scare the shit out of oncoming hornets by wearing these on any bike ride.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_clear_preferred">Clear Preferred Characters</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_msr">Rattlesnake Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jiro_begins">Jiro Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chains">Chains</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_gre_m79_same">Warpig</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hoxton_clean_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Hoxton mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_zipper">The Zipper</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goat_desc">Dolph the Goat represents natural strength and stone.$NL;$NL;It was found by a group of adventurers in a mountain cave in the most northern parts of Sweden.$NL;$NL;Legend has it that the god of thunder, Thor, had a chariot that was pulled by two goats. This mask probably has nothing to do with that legend though. That would be crazy.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_city_camo">City Camo Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_ability_chico_injector">Injector</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unic_desc">Clop Clop- who&apos;s there? It&apos;s Unic! In the dark streets of New Rush City, what could shine brighter than an honest smile? Galloping in meadows, and sharing time with his friends, Unic is dedicated to showing the world&apos;s positive side. A pink leotard and purple boots make this speedy runner truly unique!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_fg_long">JP36 Long Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bayonet">Bayonet</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_becker_desc">A machete is a large cleaver-like knife frequently used in tropical countries to cut through rain forest undergrowth, rebellions and for agricultural purposes. It is common to see people using machetes for other jobs as well, such as splitting open coconuts, skulls, yard work and robbing banks.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bonnie_begins">Bonnie Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_player_style">Equip Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_sm_wish_desc">DEMON! The Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it. This is definitely not a human skull anymore. This is what happens when you summon your demonic powers to get good.$NL;$NL;We at OVERKILL are surprised, baffled and genuinely impressed. You did it. You are among a certain few who stuck with it and actually finished the hardest difficulty we could think of. You fought, you suffered and you persevered. You have our eternal respect, you ruler of demons.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_r870">Reinfeld 880 Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_magenta">Plastic Magenta</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_asval_s_solid">Solid Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_card_king">King of Cards</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled_desc">Dressed up for stealing.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_hunter_burn">Dog Eat Dog</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_kabar">URSA Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_kidswool_desc">Joy&apos;s favorite gloves for hacking on cold, winter nights.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_akmsu_grunt">Gray Hunter</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_conquest_desc">The identity of the first horseman of the Apocalypse, and exactly what he represents is something still greatly debated to this day. Some call him Conquest, some say he was Christ himself, and some claim he was even the Antichrist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_swagger">Swagger Stick</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_microphone_desc">A microphone you ask?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robo_arnold">Robo-Arnold</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_panther_desc">Brandon has a thing for walking really, really fast.$NL;$NL;Brandon is a panther, and panthers are large cats. One funny thing is that only the tiger, lion, leopard and jaguar has the anatomical structure which enables them to roar. Poor panther.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_blackmarket_title">Blackmarket: $item;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clinton">The 42nd</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_alex">Alex</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_saintsleather_desc">It&apos;s time to bring the pain.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clowncry_desc">Is there anything sadder than a crying clown?$NL;$NL;Probably crying civilians, being shouted to the ground by a criminal wearing a horrific mask.$NL;$NL;Or maybe a bank manager with an empty vault.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_carnotaurus_desc">Alfred the Carnotaurus was a very fast dinosaur when he was alive and kicking. His distinctive horns and his muscular neck made him stand out next to all the other dinosaurs. His large head along with his horns working as shock absorbers made him particularly skilled at head butting other dinosaurs in order to show who had the largest prehistoric d-peen.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fatboy">Fatboy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_04_desc">Don&apos;t let the small frame and disheveled fur fool you. This little guy&apos;s piercing eyes can intimidate just about anyone, and woe betide any who dares steal something while he&apos;s on watch.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_wac">Knight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_02_desc">Feeder has dislodged his jaw with one sole purpose: to be able to swallow a whole, human heart. This explains why his teeth and tongue is of no use, as chewing is not important. When he roams the night he seeks out teens with strong hearts that can sustain him. So if you spot a corpse with a ripped chest - run.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_punk">Horizon Highlight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wolf_desc">The mask of Wolf.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_jail_pd2_clan">The Striped Troublemaker</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_bayonet">Bayonet Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_m_explosive_desc">Arrow with an explosive tip that detonates on impact.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_greek_tragedy_desc">A mask that symbolizes all the parts in a greek tragedy.$NL;$NL;In old Greece, masks were used to worship the gods in ceremonial rites and celebrations.$NL;$NL;This particular mask summarizes every heist in existence; the anger of someone triggering the alarm, the joy of opening the vault and the tragedy of being caught.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_green_desaturated">Emerald Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_mercury">Mercury</string>
	 <string id="bm_e_wish_desc">Your full potential is close. Embrace the change. Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it. This doesn&apos;t look like a human skull however, but you don&apos;t have to worry about it.$NL;$NL;You finished all heists on Mayhem difficulty? What are you, some kind of beast? Maybe this mask will suit you after all.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ransom_gameover">gAme OVER</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_steam_item_name">##$name;##</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_deagle">Akimbo Deagle Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_contintental_desc">Hoxton was once chased by three squad cars in New York after a nighttime hit went bad. Covered in enemy blood, he threw his mask and gun into a gutter and headed for his favorite nightclub to lay low in. (He also needed a drink, badly.) On the way, he spotted this suit in a store window. Realizing he&apos;d never be able to stay hidden looking like he did, Hox broke in and had a quick change of wardrobe. By the time the first squad car rounded the corner, Hoxton was already chatting up the women standing in line to go clubbing, suave as ever. He stared right into the searchlight as the car passed... the driver never recognizing his quarry.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_09">Mega Smiley</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_04_desc">One move, then another. Your opponent makes a move and you respond. He stands there, atop the mountain of gold, daring you to come forward and take on his challenge. By wearing this mask, you declare your defiance, with the game afoot, and the rivalry unending.</string>
	 <string id="bm_paycheck_chains">Paycheck Chains</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ipsccomp">IPSC Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_fg_railed">Railed Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_rainbowmittens">Flower Child</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_navy_blue_light_blue">Navy Blue / Light Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bullet_desc">Worried about getting shot in the face with a high powered firearm?$NL;$NL;Scared that you will get stomped by a bulldozer, cloaker and a shield at the same time?$NL;$NL;Wearing this mask will not help you, but you will get downed in style. The Bullet - out in Black Markets near you, right now!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wolf">Wolf</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_female_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Hila mask as it looked before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_crashdummy">Dummy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_g_m4_surgeon">Titanium Skeleton Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_push">Push Daggers</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m95_b_barrel_long">Tank Buster Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ak5">AK5 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_m_straight">Vintage Mag.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_docter">Surgeon Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m32_barrel_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ching_b_short">Tanker Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_bugsy">George &quot;Bugs&quot; Moran</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_orange_desc">For those California sunsets.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_07_desc">Commander Wasp sat on incredible technical capacity. Strength and intelligence was by far superior to the other side. A prototype that would have the needed circuits to outsmart the opposing forces. But an untested prototype. Something rushed. Something that was too experimental. Madness strikes circuit boards, but we refer to it as a &quot;bug&quot;. Killing his fellow troops in a rage of paranoia - Commander Wasp became a criminal of war. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cantus_desc">Whether you&apos;re on the bus or in the boardroom, when Alesso is filling your ears with heavenly tunes, it&apos;s important to show the world a suitable face. Presenting Cantus - the Angel of Music and Song. Let your spirit soar!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dawn_of_the_dead_desc">An undead is a being that is dead yet somehow behaves like it is still alive.$NL;$NL;Created in mysterious ways, this might as well be a zombie as it could be a Vampire.$NL;$NL;If you are going to rob a bank, why not scare the living hell out of people while doing so?</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_conflict">This modification is incompatible with your current $conflict;</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_starbreeze">Starbreeze Sun</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_stop_preview_weapon_cosmetic">Stop Previewing Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_aa12_barrel_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saw_buck">One Percenter</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_anonymous">Anonymous</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_x46">X-46 Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_falcon_desc">Life&apos;s not all about speed and running! With his livelihood destroyed from a speedy accident, he became the hero that New Rush City truly deserves. Falcon vows to take down SpeedRunner and get the city back. Is Falcon the only one sane in a world gone mad- or is he a man in a chicken suit?</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_baton">Telescopic Baton</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill">CREW BOOSTS</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_conquest">Conquest</string>
	 <string id="bm_lucky_luciano">Charles &quot;Lucky&quot; Luciano</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_hippie">The Altamont</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_06_desc">Oh, how you can ponder, all rich and sweary, over a quaint and curious pile of not-forgotten cash. Quote, The Heister.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_06">Black Bird</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_groucho_desc">A perfect disguise doesn&apos;t have to mean dying your hair, changing your iris and burning off your fingerprints. Sometimes looking obviously strange makes people uncomfortable enough to look away and pay you no mind.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_gray_raider">Gray Raider</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_oldbaton_desc">Can&apos;t beat the classics!</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus_damage">Damage</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_s_fold">Folding Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_lemming_b_nitride">TiN Treated Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_murky_suit_desc">A military uniform used by Murkywater mercenaries. It includes a patch with the Murkywater logo.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_event_01">Crimefest 2 Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_upper_reciever">Upper Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_erdl">Jungle Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richter_desc">Like the rat, Richter is a silent killer. It can make its way into just about anywhere - into the most secure banks and apartments. It can avoid detection when it wants, and, once there, spread death like a plague. It kills without remorse. Nothing personal.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mp9_burn">Osterberg</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tinted_love_desc">Murder, extortion, violence, destruction, drugs, guns, and theft. These are all crimes associated with Vlad, but none are as great as his fashion sense.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_police_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_brown">Dust Devil</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_04_desc">Dome was the centerpiece of a grand scheme, planned and set in motion by the other side. A simple robot, assembled to restore/reassemble/rearrange, Dome was on mission to reassemble a government building that got destroyed by the enemy. A stealth attack - to take out Commander Wasp - was taking place near the location as the Commander&apos;s car drove passed the debris. Dome saw the coming attack and sacrificed himself to protect the Commander by throwing himself in front of the car, making it steer away from the blast. Wasp survived, Dome did not. </string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_sr2">Akimbo Heather Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_speedrunner_desc">It&apos;s time for a speedy run! SpeedRunner is the people&apos;s champ in New Rush City. Running, sliding, swinging his way toward crime and those in need, he accepts no less than first place. SpeedRunner&apos;s got the need... for running!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tec9_mxs">Tijuana</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_04">Hata Mari</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_de_gaulle">The Constable</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_female_desc">Something about this mask radiates a playful malice and most who gaze upon it immediately feel a sense of unease, which is just the kind of thing you need when you&apos;re robbing a bank!</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_default">Midnight Serenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_tti_g_grippy">Contractor Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_melee_weapon">Preview melee weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_03">Classy Monocle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_s_nostock_big">Short Enough Tactical Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goggles">Cloaker-san</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_g3">Gewehr 3 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grizel_clean_desc">This is a clean version of Clover&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_03_desc">Byrne is gone. He&apos;s our koala and our &quot;pet&quot;. But we don&apos;t want him back. He&apos;s boring and tedious and all he does is eat eucalyptus leaves. And we mean like ALL day. He doesn&apos;t like when you touch him or even talk to him. So now he&apos;s gone and we wanna keep it that way. If you find him (he looks like a douchebag pet) you can keep him or whatever. Consider this a warning of boredom.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_1911_g_ergo">Ergo Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_05_desc">You are unbreakable. The ship is filling with water, but you refuse to move. Such are your principles that you would rather go into the deep with a failing institution than admit your folly and admit yourself as fallible as your peers. Justice is what you deem it to be, and damned be those who would oppose your righteous wisdom.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_aa12_mag_drum">Drum Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_driverleather">Getaway</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_cobray_ns_barrelext">Slotted Barrel Extension</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hoxton">Hoxton</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_light_brown_matte_blue">Light Brown / Matte Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goggles_desc">It&apos;s not only the American government that uses specially trained operatives for infiltration missions. Japan has their own unit called the Anbu, and while this mask is only a prototype, it&apos;s very similar to the actual thing they use.$NL;$NL;Activate Night Vision Mode by holding down the Fire Mode button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_dark_leather">Dark Leather</string>
	 <string id="bm_concussion_desc">This stunning little beauty will take everyone&apos;s breath away, giving you those couple of extra seconds you need to kill them.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_model70_iron_sight">Iron Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eggian_desc">In &apos;Xenogogs&apos;, these creatures embodied fear itself, as it tore its way from the butt of Troy Templeton during that scene.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_stech_g_luxury">Cartel Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_g_sniper">Pro Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_m_uspalm">Low Drag Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_female">Hila</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_global_event">event</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_alienware_desc">Based on the visions of a madman who thought he saw an extraterrestrial being.$NL;$NL;It is strange though, as the powerful materials are not from anywhere on Earth.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_desc">A pair of these are usually present in Rust&apos;s saddle bag. He likes them more for punching than riding, though.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_barbedwire">Barbed Wire</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_smosh_01">Community Safe 2</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mega_sydney">Mega Sydney</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_gerber">Berger Combat Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled_purple_desc">Night time is heist time.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_scoutknife">Scout Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_taser_info">Device that electrocutes and interrupts targets on touch</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus_concealment">Concealment</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r870_baaah">Cloven Hoofs</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_par">KSP 58 Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_b_midsupp">Maki Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robo_arnold_desc">Iconic, time-travelling cyborg star of the &apos;Exterminator&apos; movie series. In the first movie, he was sent to kill the mother of the leader of the future rebellion before she can steal the chip left by her son who was also her father... In the past. Noted for his deadpan delivery of the catchphrase &quot;Await my return&quot;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_02">Stoibs</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_uh">Maelstrom Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_velociraptor_desc">Vincent the Velociraptor and his best friend Andreas Häll Penninger the Protoceratops were out and about one day in the jungle when they got in a fight. It wasn&apos;t a big thing really but Vincent just wouldn&apos;t let it go. Andreas, being the stubborn Protoceratops he was, continued to mouth off to Vincent. Violent fighting ensued and to this day, no one is sure who actually won.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_mask">Equip mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_blue_teal">Ice Teal</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_cry">Cry Baby</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_utg_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_usp_cat">Cotton Candy</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_fatman">Bounty Hunter</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_pis_small">Size Doesn&apos;t Matter Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_s_standard">Standard Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_rarity_uncommon">Uncommon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_02_desc">In the woods of Okinawa, legends say there lives a spirit of a fox with a head of flame. Being seen by this fox is said to be a blessing, but being seen by a heister wearing this mask, is probably not!</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_sr2">Heather Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_white_wolf">Dennis</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_plainsrider_bloodbath">Blood Drenched</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_yggdrasil">Yggdrasil</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_gerber_desc">The Berger Combat Knife is a popular tactical knife with a folding clip point blade. Compact, light and high tech materials makes a fast and dangerous tool.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_07">Mega Biker</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_quality_poor">Battle-Worn</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_neoncity">Neon City</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biker_desc">When you&apos;re a thrill-seeker, and a risk-taker, and a live-for-the-moment kind of heister, it is important to have at least some measure of protection. That also goes if you are a meat-cleaver waving maniac.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_erma_cat">Eclipse</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_raster">The Raster</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cursed_crown_desc">His name is lost to legend. He might have been a King, or a mighty Sorceror. But even the great are undone by the Diamond.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_striker_waves">Riptide</string>
	 <string id="bm_mod_incompatibility_all">all</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_bright_yellow_solid">Solid Bright Yellow</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tam">The Great Immortal</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_cat_01">Community Safe 7</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skulloverkillplus">The Death Wish Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_legacy_b_threaded">Threaded Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_monkeybiss_desc">Worn by someone who does not take life that seriously.$NL;$NL;Because it is a mask of a monkey.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_inventory_tradable_armor_skins">Armor Skins</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus_spread">Accuracy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_jav_desc">With its origins lost in murky pre-history, the javelin is a simple weapon. After all, it&apos;s a thrown stick with a pointy end that ruins someone&apos;s day. Despite this simplicity, it still requires skill and strength to use.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_titan">Titan</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bonnie_desc">Few nations have contributed to humanity as Scotland has. In every field of endeavor - science, arts, cuisine - it is the people of this blessed land that give freely and generously. With this mask, Bonnie is determined to reverse this trend.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gladiator_helmet">Murmillo Galea Helmet</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_weapon_cosmetics">Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_tan">Tan Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rust_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Rust&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_irondoom_desc">Doctor Crime is an American fictional character, a supervillain who appears in comic books by OVERKILL Comics.$NL;$NL;The character was created by writer-editor David Goldfarb and designed by artist Max Elmberg Sjöholm.$NL;$NL;He made his first appearance in The Amazing Career Criminals: The Payday Gang meets Doctor Crime!</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_armor_skin">Preview Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_dynamite">Dynamite</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_cyan_solid">Solid Cyan</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r870_smosh">Puncture Shot</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biker">Biker</string>
	 <string id="bm_hoxton_rising_desc">This distorted face is what ghost stories are truly made of. You linger in the shadows, torn and grim. Before you step out and scare the living daylights out of anyone that crosses your path. The knowledge of true fear is gained from looking upon this horror. That fear, that delicious, pure, crispy fear is what drives this monster. It triggers an unquenchable thirst for more. Don&apos;t look, but don&apos;t close your eyes.</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_smoke_screen_grenade">Smoke Bomb</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled">Heister</string>
	 <string id="bm_mod_equip_remove">Equipping this mod will remove your equipped $mod;!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eagle">Chuck</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_firedemon">Graug</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_scrub_desc">This is the kind of protective clothing a surgeon wears on hospital duty. Scrubs tend to use soothing colors that also allows staff to easily observe any stains of blood or other body fluids.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jimmy_duct_desc">Jimmy hasn&apos;t really made that many masks before he made his signature mask - and it shows. His mask design captures his free spirit and his disregard to things as appearance, planning and such. Good is good enough for Jimmy, he doesn&apos;t get stuck on details and wants to move forward at all times.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stamina">Stamina</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_rarity_epic">Epic</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_packrat_o_expert">Tritium Sights</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_anv_02">Forest Operations</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_heat_desc">A classic hockey mask.$NL;$NL;A guy told me one time...$NL;$NL;&quot;Don&apos;t let yourself get attached to anything you are not willing to walk out on in 30 seconds flat if you feel the heat around the corner.&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mason_knight_veteran">Mason Knight Veteran</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_fancycloth">Regal</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_s552_waves">Hang Loose</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shrunken_desc">Ritually prepared, the cranium removed from the head, eyes and mouth sewn shut. Boiled in hot water, dried with hot rocks and sand and molded to keep the features of a human face.$NL;$NL;Taken by ship to the Americas by Westerners long ago, it now somehow has ended up in your possession.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_bloodbath">Danger Ahead</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_01_desc">Cold and unmoving, you watch them from above. They shall envy your majesty as your golden gaze falls on them, an undeserved blessing on these wretched soft ones. You unite the hard chill of the night with the dazzling radiance of the sun. Glorious, golden and beautiful, you shall turn their heads mad with desire - and it shall be their undoing.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_famine_desc">The third horseman of the Apocalypse is the embodiment of Famine, a force so powerful he would leave people starving to their deaths if they laid eyes upon him.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_08_desc">Rumor has it that this helmet was found in an abandoned Russian nuclear facility and that its wearer will gain super powers over time. But it&apos;s just a rumor.</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_sentry_gun">Sentry Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_olympic_sfs">Seminole </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saw_cs3">Disco</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_m3x_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus_total_ammo">Total Ammo</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_arblast">Heavy Crossbow</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_tux_desc">A traditional dinner suit for formal occasions. It has a distinctive black and white design, including the signature black tie.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_misted_grey">Misted Gray</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_wwt">Royal Order</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_sell_mask">Sell mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_rambo_desc">The Trautman Knife is a survival knife with a heavy bowie blade. The length, serrated spine and centered tip works just as well in the wilderness as it does in closed combat.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_triceratops_desc">Timothy the Triceratops is one of the most popular dinosaurs at the Jurassic High. He had a huge grudge with Teddy the Tyrannosaurus though. Even though they were massive and lived together during the last epoch of the age of dinosaurs, they couldn&apos;t find it in them to be friends. Especially not since that one time when they went to that cabin during Spring Break and Teddy and his pals pranked Timothy with that horror movie and the phone call about seven days left before the meteorite would hit. Timothy did not think that was funny at all.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_01">The Bullet</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_poker">Poker</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brutal_desc">This helmet is reserved for the top dog in a biker gang. It demands respect and authority from your brothers, and when it&apos;s time to do battle, you wear this helmet proudly and ride at the front.</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_frag">Frag Grenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_infamous">Infamous</string>
	 <string id="bm_bandana">Bloody Bandana</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_joy_desc">Bring back disco in style and confuse the hell out of your enemies when they gaze into your fabulously flashy face.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_famas_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cloth_commander_desc">Commander Crime is an American fictional character, a supervillain and the supreme leader of the criminal network C.R.I.M.E. who appears in comic books by OVERKILL Comics.$NL;$NL;The character was created by now world renowned writer-editor-artist and professional badminton player Max Elmberg Sjöholm.$NL;$NL;Commander Crime made his first appearance in The Amazing Career Criminals: The Payday Gang gets a C.R.I.M.E. offer they can&apos;t refuse!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_silverback">Steven</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_deployable">Equip deployable</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_day_of_the_dead">Calaca</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_witch_desc">A witch is someone practicing black witchcraft, often with the aid of a devil or familiar.$NL;$NL;It can be anything from an ugly old hag to a charming, alluring woman.$NL;$NL;And then you have the broom, the hat and all that. Boo.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_scorpion_cola">Tor-999</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_stech_g_tactical">Federales Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_g36_dallas">Chromed Strangler </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lcv">Le Castle Vania</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_radioactive">Radioactive</string>
	 <string id="bm_mega_clover">Mega Clover</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_orangutang">Rutger</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_red_hurricane">The Red Bear</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_wavewarning">Wave Warning</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_stech_b_long">Tirador Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grizel_clean">Clover Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_05">SKULL </string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_ak_scopemount">Scope Mount</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_coral_red_solid">Solid Coral Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_stonekisses">The Pout</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_gage_pack">Gage Weapon Pack #01</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bodhi_desc">Masks have always been used in spiritual traditions that relate to deities, the divine and those chasing the apotheosis of the self. Bodhi&apos;s mask reflects the man behind it. Strong, cunning, single-minded and centered.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_andromeda_desc">The future is now. This special mouthpiece is believed to be developed for soldiers of the future, acting not only as a gasmask but also give the wearer the ability to breath under water. Unfortunately, this one seems broken, but it still looks cool.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gentleman_father">Pious Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_bonus_team_exp_money_p3">Team Boost</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_crowgoblin_desc">For the longest time ever no one knew who the real identity behind the Crow Goblin was. Twenty years later people found out, but it was unsatisfactory so they said that that person was an imposter or something. The real Crow Goblin was someone else.$NL;$NL;I don&apos;t want to bore you with the rest of it but the mask looks pretty nice, yeah? It&apos;s got a purple hat, or maybe it&apos;s a hoodie, I don&apos;t know. It sports a pretty cool grin and some thread sewn across its face. I wonder who hides behind the mask though.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_tag_team">Requires the Tag Team Perk Deck Equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_four">Shuriken</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_akmsu">Krinkov Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_cs4_01">Community Safe 4</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_corgi">Union 5.56 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_old_hoxton_desc">The Hoxton Reborn mask is a mask that Hoxton made while in prison. For him, it&apos;s a symbol of everything he experienced in the past years while the Payday Gang kept on going without him. No one knows how his experiences in prison has changed him, and he won&apos;t talk about it when asked.$NL;$NL;All we can assume is that he has been changed forever, and that he is reborn into... Something different.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_visor">Safety First</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_concealment">Concealment</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_venomorph_desc">When you see the Venomorph, you know it&apos;s game over, man. GAME OVER!$NL;Maybe you can build a fire, try sing a couple of songs.$NL;$NL;In reality, you better go back and hide, because it will be dark soon, and these babies mostly only come at night... Mostly.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_04">Tempy</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_dodge">Dodge</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saiga_ginger">Blue Tundra</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_white">Skin of the Saint</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_02">Futuras</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mdm_desc">Death can be the end but it can also be a beginning, a transcendence and catharsis. And Mega Death has a million times the power of Death.</string>
	 <string id="bm_donald">The 45th</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_roman">Hippika</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_stech_tam">IMMORTAL PYTHON WEAPON SKIN</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_daisy_desc">They might have not known what they did and to who, but that doesn&apos;t matter. They got what they deserved and then some. John is back.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_scary_green_orange">Scary Green / Orange</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_frank_desc">Frank is a monster, but he is - contrary to popular belief - a sensitive, emotional creature whose only aim is to share his life with another monster.$NL;$NL;However, he realized from the moment of his &quot;birth&quot; that even his own creator cannot stand being around him. Knowing this, Frank decided to become a bank robber instead. The end.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ggac">The One Down Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_dbd_clan_unlock">Join the Dead by Daylight Official Community Group on Steam to unlock!</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_saw">OVE9000 Saw</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_chac_desc">Feel the beat.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_polymer">Akimbo Kross Vertex Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_02">Mega Famine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_purple_song">Dove Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nutcracker">Hans</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_doctor_bag_desc">To use the doctor bag, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed it cannot be moved, but it can be used by you and your crew by holding $BTN_INTERACT; to regain health. Using the doctor bag will reset the amount of times the player can get downed before going into custody. It can only be used twice.$NL;$NL;When the Doctor Bag is consumed, it disappears. You can see how many uses are left by looking at the Doctor Bag. $NL;$NL;The Doctor Bag is a portable bag, usually used by a physician or other medical profession to transport medical supplies and medicine.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_m_poison_desc">Arrow with a poison tip that does damage over time and has a chance to interrupt enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_bloodsplat">Incinerated Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_molotov_desc">The Molotov cocktail is perhaps the simplest weapon that can call itself a grenade. Nothing more than a breakable bottle of flammable liquid with a &apos;fuse&apos; replaced by a burning rag. It is cheap, simple and highly effective.</string>
	 <string id="bm_cloaker">Batshit Crazy</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_murky_desc">Do the chore, get the score.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tech_lion_desc">This mask is a modern interpretation of the Egyptian war-god Maahes. Known as the &quot;Wield of the Knife&quot;, &quot;Lord of Slaughter&quot; and &quot;Avenger of Wrongs&quot;, Maahes punished those who transgressed from the rules of Ma`at - the personification of order and balance. Considered the embodiment of the burning heat of the sun, he was also seen as a protective deity that defended the Pharaoh during battle.$NL;$NL;He is usually depicted as lion-headed man carrying a knife wearing the Atef crown, the Solar Disk or is pictured as a lion devouring a victim.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_12">Mega Robber Fly</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_becker">Utility Machete</string>
	 <string id="american_desc">Nationality: American$NL;Age: 31$NL;$NL;Houston could never hold a job even if his life would depend on it. His life style turned him to a life of cons and burglary. His debts grew, as did his collection of enemies from years of swindlery. He needed to gather larger and larger sums of money to keep the loan sharks at bay. He committed his first major felony at the age of 24 and the stakes have only increased since.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_00_desc">This blister stricken creature is the embodiment of true terror. All your childhood fears poured into something unfathomable and horrendous. Question is if you will even need bullets anymore.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fear">Stainless Steel Syringe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_s_solidstock">Classic Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_02_desc">Blow down the bank vaults and scare the crap out of all the little pigs while wearing this mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skulloverkill_desc">Holy shit - what is this new devilry? Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it. This doesn&apos;t look like a human skull however.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_buck">Road Rash</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g18c_g_ergo">Ergo Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_m_quick">Speed Pull Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_speedrunners_unlock">Own the Speedrunners Game on Steam to unlock!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullveryhard">The Very Hard Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_dutch">Dutch</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_with_mod">Preview weapon with mod</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_ammo_bag_desc">To use the Ammo Bag, you place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Once placed it cannot be moved, but it can be used by you and your crew by holding $BTN_INTERACT; to gain more ammunition. It can fully replenish the ammunition of one your weapons 4 times. When the Ammo Bag is depleted, it will disappear. You can see how many uses are left by looking at the Ammo Bag. $NL;$NL;The ammo bag is a portable bag, originally intended to allow soldiers to carry extra ammunition with them into combat.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_01_desc">Half a block, half a block$NL;Half a block onward$NL;Into the First World Bank$NL;Walked the four heisters$NL;Forward the Payday Gang$NL;Charge for the gold, they said$NL;Into the First World Bank$NL;Walked the four heisters</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rust_begins">Rust Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gladiator_helmet_desc">Gladiators were members of a brutal caste in Ancient Rome whose sole duty was to entertain by way of public exhibitions of horrific violence. This style of helmet with its high crest  resembles a fish. It was worn by a Murmillo - a heavy class of gladiator that fought with a sword and tower shield. They symbolize Vulcan - the roman god of fire, and they stand for strength and honor.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_spot">Reconnaissance Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r700_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpk_buck">Horsepower</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sports_utility_mask">Sports Utility Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shovel">K.L.A.S. Shovel</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_sneak_suit_desc">This is a stealth suit. It&apos;s comfortable for silent movement, and its soft, black material helps the wearer blend into the darkness during night operations. It has utility pockets for ammo and equipment.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_czech_g_luxury">Cartel Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m14_body_ebr">Abraham Body</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor4">Sherman Tank</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_tec9">Akimbo Blaster 9mm Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_upper_reciever_ballos">LW Upper Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_light_blue_bright_yellow">Light Blue / Bright Yellow</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_fg_lr300">Aftermarket Special Handguard</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_coyote_brown_solid">Solid Coyote Brown</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mmh">Mega Duke</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_butcher">The Butcher from Hell</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_mp5_cs3">Failsafe</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_dada_com_desc">The Matryoshka Grenade is a throwable explosive device. The doll&apos;s outer layers hides its inner workings. Creates substantial damage at the same time as it pays tribute to the motherland.</string>
	 <string id="bm_donald_mega_desc">Bow down before him.$NL;$NL;The Mega 45th mask is an evolved version of the original mask. It symbolises transcendence and catharsis.$NL;$NL;Thank you for your support.$NL;OVERKILL salutes you!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_wwt">Bandit Burner</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_04_desc">This supposedly &quot;three million dollar hat&quot; is either soaked in the blood of your enemies, or was just made with some red woolen material. Just wash it after each heist!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m60_fg_keymod">Modernized Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_zombie_desc">A zombie is an animated corpse that somehow has been brought to life again.$NL;$NL;Brains?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rooster_desc">Richard enjoys spending time with different personas and asking questions.$NL;$NL;Do you like hurting other people?$NL;$NL;Who is leaving messages on your answering machine?$NL;$NL;Where are you right now?$NL;$NL;Why are we having this conversation?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_surprise_desc">Santa, more known as Santa Claus, Saint Nicholas, Father Christmas and Kris Kringle (?) is a man of epic proportions. Words like legendary, mythical, historical and folkloric best describe this beast of a man.$NL;$NL;This particular mask is the Surprised Santa mask. Who knows why he&apos;s surprised? Maybe someone stole his sled? Maybe someone stole his reindeers? Maybe he just saw someone rob a bank?</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stock">Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_surprise">Surprised Santa</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_l85a2">Queen&apos;s Wrath Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mr_sinister_desc">Evil and treacherous in a haunting way, this mask is said to change the wearer in mysterious ways.$NL;$NL;Worn long enough, it is said it turns the wearers heart into a black one, filled with lust for black deeds.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_suit_variation">Preview Variation</string>
	 <string id="bm_cap_n_beard">A.W.O.L</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richter">Richter</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_04">Red Machine</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_grey">Grey Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_09_desc">See the torturously happy grin, the rotting golden teeth, and the deeply mesmerizing glare of this ultimate tribute to the Tragic Clown.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cantus">Cantus</string>
	 <string id="bm_beret_desc">Chains had this beret custom made in preparation for a mercenary operation in West Africa. What he did while wearing it is something he won&apos;t talk about, though.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mod_incompatibilities">This mod is incompatible with $quantifier; $category;!</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_mariachi">The Minstrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_uzi_s_standard">Folded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_hockey">Cross Check</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_g_standard_green">Enhanced Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_angry_desc">GRRRRRRRR GRRR grrr grr grr GRRRR Wah, wah, WAAAAAAAAAAH! GRRR! Grr.$NL;$NL;GRRRR grr GRRRR rawr GRRRRRRRRRRRRR, wahh, WAH, WAH, WAH, GRRR.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_div_perfess">Per Fess</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_03_desc">Always being referred to as &quot;Number 2&quot; the Cultist will challenge anyone that gets in his way.  Armed with with a Dart Gun, this challenger shouldn&apos;t be taken easy!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_boot_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tall_goat">Scout Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_p90">Kobus 90 Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_03_desc">When there&apos;s only one copy of something left in the world, it becomes priceless. Know what you can do, and what others can do better. Get the job done. Don&apos;t get carried away by jealousy; that&apos;s fear talking. Fear brings you down. It doesn&apos;t come from love. When you really love someone, you trust them. Trust them enough to not get mean over priceless things.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_02">Sailor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richard_returns">Richard Returns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_07_desc">More is never enough. No amount of gold or treasure can satisfy you. It&apos;s all about obtaining the next pile of needless wealth to add to your bloated coffers, be they spiritual or physical. The plights of your fellows matter are inconsequential if you can gain from their suffering.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_s_nostock">Short Enough Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_buluc_desc">He who has the most outragously hideous visage on his head, wins.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pazuzu">Pazuzu</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_clown_desc">Distraction can be the heister&apos;s best tool, and the right outfit can accomplish just that, making the enemy wonder what the hell is going on. &quot;Is the circus in town? What kind of clown carries a gun?&quot; With that in mind, there&apos;s no reason you can&apos;t do it with a little style and colorful flair. Hence this rather spiffy getup; it&apos;ll make you feel like the prince of crime.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_arbiter_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_anubis">Anubis</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghost_desc">This Ghost mask looks like it&apos;s from the future and it might as well be.$NL;$NL;Full head protection, made out of carbon fiber and genetically engineered spider-silk. People might even mistake you for a high-end Moto GP rider.$NL;$NL;Last mistake they&apos;ll make.$NL;$NL;This mask is an Infamy tree reward. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any pattern, color or material as well as the customization fee to put these together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_chains_rising">Risen Chains Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gumbo">Gumbo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_tiger">Talons</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_05">Mega Tormentor</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_striker">Street Sweeper Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_sport">Runner</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_champion_dallas_desc">This is the Champ mask. Based on a bad day for Dallas. How bad? Well, imagine being on the business end of thirteen rounds with a professional boxer. Swollen brow, broken nose, fat lip, black eye, contusions, concussions, dislocated jaw - you name it, and this mask has it. Yeah, a really bad day for Dallas.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_kampfmesser_desc">The Krieger Blade is the standard knife of the German Army. Great grip, and the Tanto blade makes it an excellent choice for combat.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_mining_pick">Gold Fever</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_chopper">Simple Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_ns_jprifles">Competitor&apos;s Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_event_red">First World Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_v6">Marmon Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dallas_clean">Dallas Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_totalammo">Total Ammo</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_mp5_buck">Torque</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pig_desc">Aubrey is a real gun lover.$NL;$NL;Large headed and long snouted Aubrey is a master of arms and knows nothing better than to kill using some fine weaponry.$NL;$NL;Pigs have pretty small lungs though so Aubrey can&apos;t run that far.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_metalhead">Metalhead</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_t800_desc">A nice set of extra hide is always a good idea. And when it looks this good, any fool would think twice before messing with you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_empty_mask_slot_buy_info">New masks can be rewarded from completing contracts.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fear_info">Syringe filled with poison that deals damage over time and has a chance to interrupt enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_vivid_raspberry_solid">Solid Vivid Raspberry</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_skf">Hot Miami</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_erma_s_folded">Folded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_winchester_sniper_scope">A5 Scope</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45rds">45 Degree Red Dot Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_road">Chain Whip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_suppression">Threat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_alienware">Alienware</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fancy_goat">Slick Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_joy_begins">Joy Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_sandsteel">Shinsakuto Katana</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_damage_control">Requires The Stoic perk deck equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mad_mask_desc">Inspired by the immensely popular anime  Zero 68, this mask is modeled after the helmet of the cyborg-ninja hero of the show. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_07">Greed</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_turquoise_pink">Turquoise / Pink</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpg7_woodland">Headline</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sydney_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Sydney&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_04">Panthera Tigris</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_04_desc">Ultimate old-school evil. Whether combined with a tail coat or body armor, this set will tell all that you mean business, in the most criminal sense.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_miami">Hot Miami</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_gentleman_desc">Some say long coats went out of style in the 1990s. But the Payday gang doesn&apos;t follow trends. They can make anything look cool.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_grenade">Equip Throwable</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_fancycloth_desc">Sydney once had a pair like this, but she got them all covered in blood during a heist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chico_desc">Scarface came to the US with nothing more than two empty hands and a bad attitude, the darkness in his heart matched only by the brilliance of his criminal mind. His mask tells the story, complete with the trail of blood that he left in his wake as he began to make his mark.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jiro_desc">Japan is a land of tradition. A land of warriors. Jiro&apos;s mask reflects this. The mask expresses Jiro&apos;s love for a traditional Japan, while the bared snarl represents his unshakable determination.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_upper_reciever_core">THRUST Upper Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_forestcamo">Forest Camouflage</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mosin_waves">Coo Coo Ca Choo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_baseballbat_desc">A baseball bat you can hit homeruns with.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_bullseye">Compact Hatchet</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_siltstone_b_silenced">Tikho Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_desert_camo">Desert Camo Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_spas12">Predator 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_c96_wac">Hakkapeliitta</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_04">Rivet&apos;s Bandana</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_monkeybiss">Monkey Business</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_11_desc">Bark like an Egyptian god and stand guard for eternity as you watch over and protect your piles of loot.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_t800_toughboy">Infamy White</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_corgi_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_armor_kit_desc">To use the Armor Bag, hold $BTN_USE_ITEM; to put on your equipped armor. Until that, you will wear the Two-piece Suit.$NL;$NL;The armor bag has only one use and when it is consumed, it disappears. The Armor Bag is a portable bag used to transport an armor of your choice, that can be used during a heist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_hot_cold">Hot and Cold</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor5">Bomber Jacket</string>
	 <string id="bm_zeal_mask">Dark Legion</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_baroness_solid">Solid Baroness</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_camohex">Greed</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fists_desc">You&apos;re no boxer, but you can still throw a pretty good punch. All it takes is some strength, speed and timing and you&apos;ll land a striking blow in no-time.$NL;$NL;You can charge your punch in order to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_g_laser">Laser Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ray">Commando 101 Rocket Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jiro_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Jiro&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_2006m">Akimbo Matever .357 Revolvers</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_skullshape">Death Paint</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biker_classic">The Classic</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_tecci_ns_special">Bootstrap Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_hypno">Breaching Owl</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_uzi_ait">Shattered Line</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_blue_ice">Glacier Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_panda_desc">Jean-Claude the Panda used to be really cool and star in all sorts of crazy stuff.$NL;$NL;Sadly, he later became a drug addict and stopped being cool. Because of training however, he managed to get back on track.$NL;$NL;Most recently, you could see him do this weird things with two trucks. That shit was fucked up. You should check it out if you haven&apos;t.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_03_desc">If only the Kings of Old had such an artifact, they would have been invincible. What enemy could withstand bowing before you, as they gaze upon your magnificence? Sun Tzu can go suck a lemon, because with a mask like this, who needs to employ art in war?</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g18c_co_1">Ventilated Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_stop_move">Cancel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_04_desc">Fight global warming with a mighty roar while wearing this magnificent face covering.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_03_desc">If only this magnificent seeing glass contained a hololens, but alas it will only help you look classically stylish while typing the correct key combo on a vault.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fireaxe">Fire Axe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_mp5_ginger">Ho-Ho-Ho</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_g_rk3">Aluminum Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_grunt">Night Chill</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lcv_desc">It&apos;s modern, dynamic and a real crowd-pleaser. It&apos;s sleek, slick and totally stylish. It&apos;s both the music of Le Castle Vania, and his mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_dss_01">Duke Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_01_desc">This fetching number will make you the talk of the town. You&apos;re guaranteed to hear things like: &quot;SEND IN THE TAZERS!&quot;, &quot;THIS IS THE POLICE, COME OUT WITH YOUR HANDS UP!&quot;, or &quot;WHO ARE THESE GUYS, EX-MILITARY?!&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_packrat_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_king_mask_desc">Mercy! Are you bad enough of a dude or dudette to rock the royal trifecta of slick aviators ,bad-ass pompadour and tactical sideburns? Summon forth the indomitable spirit of various used-car dealers and shotgun-wedding ministers all around Vegas who wore this thing all the way to success. Or at least mild public awkwardness. Hail to the king!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mmj_desc">Classic gear can be a wonderful thing. The mindset of a heroic thrill-seeker riding a 200BHP steel horse has many things in common with a heister that are not obvious at first glance- the aesthetic value of a piece of custom headgear being one of them!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_c96_css">Rhetoric</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_speed_demon_desc">What better way to symbolize the do-not-give-a-fuck attitude of the biker lifestyle, than by wearing the face of the Devil. The ultimate symbol for breaking the law.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_cake">Piece of Cake</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_blue_dark">Midnight Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_02_desc">Sail on the treasure fleet - climb the rigging and keep an eye out for pursuing ships as you scour the sea for sunken gold. If they catch up with you, abandon ship like the rat you are - but don&apos;t forget to bring the gold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_02">Matryoshka</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_02_desc">The Robot was an honored member of the killbot army. When commanded by his master, EMP-R0R to kill the leader of the human resistance, he broke protocol, failing to eliminate humanity.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_04_desc">No one can stop the Red Machine! It&apos;s fast, ice-cold and merciless. With swift moves, lightning strikes and flawless tactics it humiliates the opposition, leaving them crying in desperation. Just like the Payday Gang.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_yellow_red">Yellow / Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_01">Alces</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fatboy_desc">It&apos;s the full-cheeked, pink, healthy face that represents the wonderful, magical alchemy of deep-fried dough and sugar found in the lobby of theaters across the States.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_titan_desc">Once, they strode among us. Cyclopean beings, tall as towers. They were old, even when our primate ancestors howled at fire. Now, they are gone, and only their shades come to us in half-dreamt race memories.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_03">Poly Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_tlr1_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gcm_desc">It&apos;s been four years. Four years of hard work, meth cooked, shots fired and loot hauled. But we&apos;ve only just began. We do feel a bit nostalgic. It&apos;s been four years since we came to Washington and took on our first heist here and now we&apos;re pros. And when it&apos;s someone&apos;s birthday, you need to get them a gift. Therefore we&apos;ve poured 24k hot, luscious gold all over Chains mask. Happy Birthday PAYDAY 2!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_breech_b_reinforced">Reinforced Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_03_desc">Satanic worshippers from a video game in the 1990s called and want their low-poly goat back. Are you gonna give it, or just stick it to &apos;em?</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_siltstone_ns_variation_b">Grievky Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_fire_rate">Rate of fire</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_desertfox_wac">Crusader</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gwm">Golden Wolf</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_corgi_nin">Hyena</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stock_plural">Stocks</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_frag_com">HEF Grenade</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_copper">Copper</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_uzi">Akimbo Uzi Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_02">Feeder</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_orange_purple">Orange / Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wayfarer">Reservoir Dog</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unicorn">Peter</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_optimist_prime">The Optimist</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rubber_female_desc">The Female Mannequin.$NL;$NL;The face of an articulated doll used by tailors, dressmakers, artists, windowdressers and now bank robbers.$NL;$NL;They are most often used to display or fit clothing, but are also used to simulate how to teach first aid, CPR, tracheal intubation and now bank robbery.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m249">KSP Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_vivid_sky_blue_solid">Solid Vivid Sky Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shrew_sl_milled">Milled Slide</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_frank">Frank</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpg7_bloodsplat">Dinomageddon</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_detection">Detection Risk</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oro_desc">It was exploring the Islands of French Polynesia, Bodhi encountered the disciples of the war-god Oro. The young adventurer quickly became enamored of this god, who valued the appreciation of beautiful crafts as much as the art of struggle.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_character_locked">Character&apos;s Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_02_desc">Stoibs is a bit frantic and &quot;speedy&quot;. He ran away last tuesday night and we would be glad to get him back. We have had a hard time finding a chinchilla with a good pedigree. So for us to start all over again with a new one, feeding him corn to get him fat and tender will be tedious. If you find him, we&apos;ll invite you to the dinner where we enjoy Stoibs!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_laser">Compact Laser Module</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_doctor_bag">Doctor Bag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_pis_ns_flash">Flash Hider</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_04">DOME </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_patton_desc">One of the bravest men I saw in the African campaign was on a telegraph pole in the midst of furious fire while we were moving toward Tunis. I stopped and asked him what the hell he was doing up there. He answered, &apos;Fixing the wire, sir.&apos; &apos;Isn&apos;t it a little unhealthy up there right now?&apos; I asked. &apos;Yes sir, but this goddamn wire has got to be fixed.&apos; I asked, &apos;Don&apos;t those planes strafing the road bother you?&apos; And he answered, &apos;No sir, but you sure as hell do.&apos;$NL;$NL;Now, there was a real soldier. A real man. A man who devoted all he had to his duty, no matter how great the odds, no matter how seemingly insignificant his duty appeared at the time.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_03_desc">Kurgan doesn&apos;t wear the gas-mask to keep the fumes of war out. He wears it to keep the flames of fury in. Betrayed by his own side, Kurgan barely survived an ambush by armored flamers. Inside the mask, there is only the smell of his own immolated flesh, a constant reminder to trust no-one.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_corey">Corey</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cthulhu_desc">A mask with a hideous appearance, the very face of terror.$NL;$NL;They say that an evil beast has many names. That must be why this beast is known as Tulu, Clulu, Clooloo, Cthulu, Cthullu, C&apos;thulhu, Cighulu, Cathulu, C&apos;thlu among other names.$NL;$NL;Part human, part octopus and part dragon, this is one of the greatest evils known to man.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_male_desc">This mask exudes power and brute force, in stark contrast to the man who wears it. Equal parts clown-like sadness and begrudging anger, it perfectly captures the mood of someone who has somewhat reluctantly chosen to become a heister.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_lones">G-Toxin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_anubis_desc">The Egyptian jackal-headed god of the afterlife, Anubis sought to protect graves rather than fill them.</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_character_pack_clover">Clover Character Pack</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saiga_wolf">Hagelbrak</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_preferred">Selected</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_branch_green_solid">Solid Branch Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ak5_s_ak5c">Caesar Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_croupier_hat_desc">Spruce up your glamorous neon 80&apos;s look! This kind of mint-green headwear has been in use since the 19th century as a method of preventing eyestrain from intense light sources. Coked out gamblers and gonzo journalists have propelled the croupier&apos;s hat into the focus of the mainstream. They are also perfect for beach-front raves, picking up hotties on the beach, signing a contract on the 18th hole of your nearest country club and generally looking like an octogenarian.</string>
	 <string id="bm_bandana_desc">The identity of the soldier that wore this red headband is classified information. Leaked reports speak of a war veteran and former U.S. Army Special Forces soldier that was an expert in guerrilla tactics. His military comrades described him as tough, reckless and over the top aggressive. Based on how many high-ranking officers he tracked down and slaughtered, he may have major problem with authorities...</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_branding_iron">You&apos;re Mine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_cs3">Greed</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_bat">Baseball Bat</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_siltstone_mxs">Toltec</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_01">Dallas, The Chief</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_viking">The Dragon Head</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_03">Thorntail</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_cola_01">Jimmy Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_dirty_russian">Zashchita</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_anv_03">City Operations</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_myh">Duke</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_04_desc">Even stark raving mad Killers need cash. It&apos;s a fact. So sometimes you simply must take a break from slashing teens and hang up the blood stained machete. But killing can be done in so many ways and it&apos;s real important with a hobby - and remember that cops bleed too.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_war_desc">The second horseman of the Apocalypse is War and the violent spirit of mankind.  War believes humans are naturally vicious, and that they don&apos;t require a real reason to fight or kill. He rode a fiery red horse, suggesting that blood would flow wherever he went.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_puzzle">The Puzzle</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_mariachi_desc">The complexities of constructing a proper mariachi suit should not be overlooked. Some are deceptively simple, but underneath, there often lies an intricate level of craftsmanship handed down through generations.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_deagle">Deagle Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_cash">Cash Money</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_akmsu_fg_rail">Moscow Special Rail</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_tam">Immortal Python Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_band">Trek</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sombrero_desc">He who laughs at the heister wearing this may soon realize he has laughed his last, unless you can laugh with a big damn bullet hole in your face.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shawn">Shawn&apos;s Shears</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_smg_m45_body_green">Swedish Body</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_g22c">Akimbo Chimano Custom Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_dingdong">Ding Dong Breaching Tool</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghm">Golden Houston</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skulloverkill">The OVERKILL Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_firemask_desc">The crew may show scant respect to the police authorities, but they have huge respect for the men and women that clean up the burning messes left in their wake. This mask is a tribute to their efforts.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_g_pgrip">AK Plastic Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_crazy_lion_desc">A horrifying mask shaped like the head of a lion.$NL;$NL;Little is known about this mask. It is said it was made by a crazy Balkan scientist who had a sick fascination for lions. Only he could see the beauty in this mask.$NL;$NL;The mask was given to you by someone who wishes you well.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_damage_shake">Steadiness</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_slug_desc">Fires a single lead slug that penetrates body armor, enemies, shields and walls.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_p226">Akimbo Signature .40 Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_madame_st_claire_desc">This is one tough cookie. The criminal part of St. Clair was born as she went through hell one dark night. After that, she dove deep into the shady world of illegality. But she was also an advocate for civil rights and police corruption. Like a modern day, twisted version of Robin Hood one might say.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_crew_characters">CREW CHARACTERS</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dgm_desc">To commemorate the day PAYDAY became the most played co-op game in a single day - 10th of June 2017. Some 221k heisters per hour were robbing banks together in style. Earning us the Top 5 Position among Most Played Games in a day of all time - PAYDAY leaves its golden mark on history. Dallas is pleased.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullhard_desc">A strange thing, the human skull. Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_green">Green Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_frankish">Light Crossbow</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_primary_deployable">Equip Primary</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_mac">Mac</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp7_s_long">Unfolded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_pocket_ecm_jammer">Pocket ECM Device</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_stunner">Carpet Bombing</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_male">Ethan</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_g_laser_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_pattern_warpaint_darkness_eyes">Warriors Eyes</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oni">Oni</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_boot_dss">Bonnie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullmonkey_desc">Clint the black-capped squirrel monkey. Not really a monkey without a name. Just like the real Clint, this monkey doesn&apos;t fuck around. It minds its own business. Doesn&apos;t talk unless talked to, knowing that the less it says the stronger it becomes. When it actually tries to say something it ends up screeching because it&apos;s a FUCKING MONKEY.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_03_desc">Soar high, swoop down and strike your prey with merciless, deadly claws. Then fly home to your lofty nest, enjoying the spoils of your hunt. You are the apex predator and you shall devour it all.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_maui_desc">Exploring the Pacific &quot;Ring of Fire&quot; in his youth, Bodhi came to the following revelation: honoring oneself means honoring the myths. A myth that stuck with him was that of Maui. Like Bodhi, Maui was a dauntless champion of humankind, a trickster and adventurer.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_craft_mod">Craft modification</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_armored_transport">Armored Transport</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_molecule">The Molecule</string>
	 <string id="bm_jar_head_desc">This is an old souvenir that Chains keeps as a memory of two long, boring months spent in Central America doing VIP security after an armed coup. Effectively, it reminds him of the kind of military monotony that made him leave mercenary life behind.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_t800_default">Infamy Dark</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_hockey_desc">A heister needs to protect his fingers from ice, both the frozen kind and that of the carbon variety.</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_mwm">Cartel Optics Mod Pack</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_masks">Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saw_m_blade_durable">Durable Blade</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_sportsbike">Windriders</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_g_ergo">Ergo Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_b_smallsupp">Spring Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_golddigger">Golden Flakes</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_holding_item">Moving</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_02_desc">Timothy Miller dreamt of working with movie lightning when he grew up. For a Halloween-party, he created the Golden Hour mask. But when he put it on and looked in the mirror, his eyes stared back surrounded by the perfect soft, red glow of the sunset. In that moment, a new dream was born. He wanted people to view the serenity of the sunset close-up, wanted it imprinted on their retina forever. The only thing the coroner could confirm was that all victims were killed shortly before sunset, their eyes always left wide open.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_04_desc">The Marine was a guard stationed at Primerdyne R&amp;D when an experiment went awry and unleashing an Interdimensional Horror into the facility. Some say he left everyone behind to die, others celebrate him as a hero who saved everyone!</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_weapon_color_skins">Weapon Color</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_ast_01">Armor Safe 2: WW2</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_05_desc">When wearing this mask, you can always pretend that the grenades you&apos;re lobbing at the cops are barrels. They won&apos;t appreciate it, but it might break up the monotony of blowing things up!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_cat">The Cat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tech_lion">Tech Lion</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_cosmos">Cosmos</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_polymer_barrel_precision">Precision Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_mp7">Akimbo SpecOps Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pain_desc">Based on the crazed leader of the League of Darkness. It&apos;s unclear if this was a breathing apparatus or a vocabulator. Some speculate that it was a delivery system, designed to provide Nemesis with the narcotics that gave him both his superhuman strength and psychotic rage.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m32_smosh_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shock_desc">The boss threw a monkey wrench into our plans when he said we&apos;d have to work Saturday.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_forest">Purple Haze</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skirmish_content_reward">Can be unlocked by playing the Holdout gamemode</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ransom_bangbang">bANg! BaNG!</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_pitchfork">Pitchfork</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_colors">Color</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_starvr">StarVR</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_x400v_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m16_waves">Charlie Don&apos;t Surf</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unic">Unic</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_movement">Speed</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_04">The Killer</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_boltcutter">Bolt Cutters</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_twitch_orc_desc">Brutish, aggressive and generally repulsive, the orcs have always been a hated race. Orcs are larger and stronger than their goblin cousins but smaller and less powerful than their ogre brethren. This particular purple-skinned orc came from the Stonetremble clan who were known for their fierce warriors and overpowered, hybrid shamans.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_b_comp">Custom Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wolf_rising_desc">The sheer sight is enough to drive an opponent into madness. As if made of blood and old bones, it&apos;s like a second skin on your face. Always listen to choir of voices in the back of your head. The ones that keep telling you of all the destructive things you should be doing. Succumb to the temptation, relish in your own insanity. This time, do not hold back. Not for anything. This time, drive any foes into your own roaming and frothing madness. Become the demon you truly are, cause you&apos;ve been to hell and you liked it. It&apos;s pointless to hold back, the only soothing is to feel an enemy&apos;s blood gently trickle down your lips.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_strinch_desc">A seasoned heister over the festival period, the Strinch has been stealing Christmases since 1957. Also linked with the Halloween Heist of 1972.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ancient">The Crossbreed</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_visor_desc">A scientist inspired by the virtual-reality sex scene in Demolition Man made his own attempt at building a device where no physical contact would actually be needed when performing intercourse. The experiment was an utter failure but a few of the early prototypes still exist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_sea_blue_black">Seagrass Green / Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_fox">The Fox</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gasmask_desc">The gas mask may seem like it belongs to the wars of an older era, but it is a crucial piece of equipment on the urban battlefield, where gas can still be deployed. Also, gives you a cool, wheezy breathing sound.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_ace_desc">Throwing cards are generally associated with magicians splitting watermelons across a stage, but add weight and razor edges and you have a silent killer. Have one of these steel aces in your sleeves and you will always be ready to deal yourself into the game, regardless of the circumstances.$NL;$NL;The Ace of Spades is a free throwable given to the community to celebrate two years of PAYDAY 2!</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_raincoat">Raincoat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_babyrhino_desc">Who would not want to wear the head of a baby rhino. Is it not cute? Putting it on makes you feel a little stupid, maybe because how it looks.$NL;$NL;While wearing it, you are worried that it is a bit hard seeing through the mask. You will do fine as long as you do not wander off with your pig-headed friends.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_gensec">Gensec</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_customizable_weapon_color">Custom Color</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_quality_fine">Lightly-Marked</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_medium">Medium Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_dlc_locked">No Access</string>
	 <string id="bm_hoxton_rising">Risen Houston Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_pocket_ecm_jammer">Requires the Hacker perk deck equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jimmy">The White Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chico_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Scarface mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_breech_wwt">Little Georg</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_hauteur">Kento&apos;s Tanto</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_judge_body_modern">Custom Reinforced Frame</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_plainsrider_skullimov">Hypno Scalp</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_chinchilla">Akimbo Castigo .44 Revolvers</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_akmsu">Akimbo Krinkov Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_slide">Slide</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_jumpsuit">The Classic</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_infamy_hood_desc">There are things older and fouler than heisters in the dark places of the world. And one of them is Kamul. We do not know if he is the lingering spirit of a long dead man, or something that has crossed from the realm of shade. All we know is that few look into this face and live to tell of it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_samurai_desc">In ancient Japan, samurai warriors wore somen masks to protect themselves in war and to incite fear in their enemies. Somen masks were made from iron and leather and were tied to the large kabuto helmets, making the samurai look like demons from jigoku.$NL;$NL;No one knows what fierce and ruthless warrior wore this intimidating mask in the past. Now however, it is ready for battle once more.$NL;$NL;&quot;Boku no ikari wo osoreru&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_bonemittens_desc">Wear your insides on your sleeve.</string>
	 <string id="bm_cap_n_beard_desc">Highly classified reports mentions this soldier from an elite special operations force. Engaged in high profile military operations and on constant alert, he was living his life under extreme pressure and constant adrenaline highs. During a sensitive strategic operation, the evidence suggest that he turned on his own unit. But no one knows certain, since the massacre left no witnesses. The soldier went A.W.O.L. and has not been seen since that day.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sparkle_party">Party Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_01_desc">Some people expect a free ride through life, cruising on good looks and luck. The world doesn&apos;t work that way, even if it sometimes looks like it. Talent is just the start; it takes education, dedication, determination. As a leader, you gotta make up your own mind. Respect your decisions, and others will too.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_coach">Claire 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_02_desc">In the small village of Pomtsburg, you can find a small monument. Few read the plaque covered with moss, but it holds the tale of a young boy. As the Germans came marching into Pomtsburg he lead the resistance with bravery and determination. Pomtsburg was his birthplace and no one were to destroy it. The Battle of Pomtsburg never reached the history books, and few even remember how it ended. But the boy managed to steal this souvenir. Something to remind him and others that you shall always stand up to oppression.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spider_desc">Eight legs strong, tarantula sizes range from as small as a fingernail to as large as a handgun when the legs are fully extended. The name originally comes from the name Lycosa tarantula, a species of wolf spider. Tarantulas generally hunt in trees, on or near the ground. They&apos;re also popular as pets.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_inventory_tradable_all">All</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robo_santa">Mechanical Santa</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_concert_female">Female Concert Goer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_boot_buck">Apex</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ak12">AK17 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_02">The Robot</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_bowie">Arkansas Toothpick</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_01">War Balaclava</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_skill">Skill</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_hotelier">Hotelier</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_damage_control_desc">An antique flask from 1882 bearing the inscription &quot;Stoic&quot; and &quot;JW Spirits&quot;, given to Duke in his youth when he trained with Buddhist monks. Duke keeps it filled with his favorite whiskey; taking a swig is a symbolic gesture of calming and gives the bearer a moment of zen-like focus, easing away damage.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hog_desc">You have a new message! *BEEP*$NL;$NL;Salutations, this is &apos;Almir&apos; at OVERKILL. The mask that you ordered should be delivered by now...$NL;$NL;A list of instructions are included...$NL;$NL;Make sure that you read them carefully!$NL;$NL;Do you like hurting other people? Then this mask is for you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_speed_demon">Speed Devil</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_sterling">Akimbo Patchett L2A1 Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_midnight_camo">Midnight Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sydney_begins">Sydney Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_tag_team">Gas Dispenser</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fg_jp">Competition Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_grunt_01">Chains</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_buy_selected_weapon">Buy weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_04_desc">This item popped up at an auction in North France during the 1990s. Among the auction goers sat a woman in her 50s. She recognized it and even though she could not remember the name of the officer who wore it, she paid a hefty sum for it. As a young girl she visited a square to buy vegetables when paratroopers came dropping down. Gunfire, explosions and screams of fear and pain filled the air. The officer took her to a shelter in a government building. He had no reason but kindness to save her. But even as his life was on stake, he risked it to save hers. She was just a young girl, but still recognized the hat.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_sight_plural">Sights</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_rota_b_silenced">Silenced Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_cordovan_solid">Solid Cordovan</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_yor_desc">You&apos;re a reliable firestarter, always on time and always on target. As the new year begins, you will set your sights on that shining gold, the most noble metal of them all. Your motives may be shady, but seven is magnificent and before you know it you&apos;ll be high-fiving to celebrate that perfect heist. Maybe you&apos;ll finally get that eight-ball tattoo.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_dark_red_solid">Solid Dark Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_03_desc">Nilam grew up among buccaneers, pirates and corsairs. She knew rum before she could speak, and held a sword before she could walk. Nilam was without family, and instead she found the nomadic lifestyle of a pirate her destiny. She was swift with a blade and few could match her in combat. All she sought was the same respect her peers got, but this was a world ruled by men. Finally Nilam had reached her limit. Those who wronged her were &quot;sentenced&quot; by getting their throats slit. Her reputation preceded her, and harbours feared the bloodshed she brought with her as her ship &quot;Verdict&quot; came sailing in.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_xp">Experience bonus</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_meter">Two Handed Great Ruler</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ak74">AK Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ability">CREW ABILITIES</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_fg_flash">Enlighted Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_fla_mk2_mag_rare">Rare</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_o_vintage">JP36 Original Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nutcracker_desc">Hans hates people and will crack the skull of anyone who opposes him. But under his frightening appearance, Hans is a good boy. You could almost say he&apos;s a prince in disguise. Treat him well and he might take you to the Land of Sweets.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_event_flake">Christmas Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_akmsu_buck">Chopper</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_desertfox_b_silenced">Silenced Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tormentor">Tormentor</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_sportsbike_desc">For going fast down the country road, and to protect those knuckles when you smash the teller window at the bank.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_morning">Morning Star</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_skf_01">Community Safe 5</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_05">Mesoamerican Dallas Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_armor">Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unborn">Unborn</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_zombie">The Zombie</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_amcar">AMCAR Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_sneak">Shadow</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_steam_item_quality">Quality: ##$quality;##</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_armor_kit">Armor Bag</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lincoln_desc">Lawyer, Commander-In-Chief, father. Had an ambition to serve this great nation for 8 years.$NL;$NL;Consistently ranked by scholars and the public as one of the greatest U.S. presidents of all time.$NL;$NL;The 16th is one of the most beloved presidents in history. Among criminals, he remains well respected.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rota_mxs">Olmec</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_golddigger">Fleur de Lis</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_sparrow_lones">Magic</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saiga_grunt">Legionnaire</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m16_baaah">Satyr</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_m_l5">L5 Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_01">The Survivor&apos;s Pilot Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_lovehate">Love Hate</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_05_desc">Torturer or tortured? Perhaps both, as the seething glow from your eyes sends chills of terror into the souls of the Law. Hear the lamentations of the Uniformed Blue as you evade them skillfully, with evil glee flowing through your veins as you foil every one of their attempts to apprehend you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shuno_b_heat_short">XS Heat Sink Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_overkill_mask">General OVERKILL</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_01_desc">Equipped with his Blasphemy sword of infinite ammo the Bullet unleashes his full power when fighting with all his heart.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_bananabike">Banana Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baitface">Funnyman</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_headshot">The Headshot</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_day_of_the_dead_desc">A skeleton mask connected to the Mexican Day of the Dead festival.$NL;$NL;Origins have been traced back to Aztec imagery, but no one is really sure.$NL;$NL;Wearing the Calaca is all about finding the joy in death happening all around you. The death of others should be a joyous occasion!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_03">A Proud Pilotka</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_toothbrush">Nova&apos;s Shank</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_pink">Plastic Pink</string>
	 <string id="bm_ace">Dawn Patrol</string>
	 <string id="bm_bugsy_desc">The rival of Al Capone. Two men battling it out as the prohibition era turned booze into gold for anyone who could get their hands on some bottles of whiskey. Capone even tried gunning him down in the infamous Saint Valentine&apos;s Day Massacre. But he failed.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_deltaforce">Alpha Force</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dragan_desc">With a background like the one Dragan has, there&apos;s no surprise he aspires to greatness in the criminal underworld.$NL;$NL;His mask represents a lot of his own characteristics, with the clear resemblance to some of the original crew&apos;s masks that tells of his ability to infiltrate and blend in while still having some features that tells of his unending ruthlessness.$NL;$NL;The Croatian checker on the forehead serves as a reminder for both himself and his enemies to be aware that he is not your common western street thug.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_07">Summerian Chains Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_foregrip">Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_custom">Custom</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_beardy">Bearded Axe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_01_desc">Make the hunted become the hunter just like the legendary Thomoose who could stagger his way through any heist with these impressive horns.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_catch">Hook</string>
	 <string id="bm_ace_desc">Way back in the day, on a secret and highly dangerous mercenary mission in Southeast Asia, Chains acquired this old US Army helmet. No one knows who the previous owner was.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_triceratops">Timothy</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_cvc_01">Armor Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_paydayblue_desaturated">Bermuda Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bullskull_desc">When staggering through desolate barrancas, with only thoughts for company, the last thing you want to see is the parched bones of those who went before you. Suddenly those thoughts are screams.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_03_desc">With her charming, floppy ears, Frou Frou is no timid Afghan Hound. Sharp and witty, she&apos;s the ideal companion to cover your face with on those heists that require brains as well as cunning.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_06_desc">Viciousness, denial of death, and gold- all aspects of how the ancient Egyptians prospered and conquered, in defiance of all. So it is somehow fitting that Wolf should don a mask honoring that ancient culture.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_kabar_desc">The URSA Knife is a hard wearing, indestructible fighting/utility knife dating back to 1942. Bowie blade, serrated edge, no nonsense. A Classic.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_level_req">Locked to reputation level $level;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biglips">The Big lips</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_oldbaton">Classic Baton</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_weapon_cosmetic">Preview Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_04_desc">With two eyes, Jessicah would never have been famous. After a shipwreck, she managed to swim to a small islet. Circled by a shark, with no rescue in sight, she was caught. With nothing more than a broken knife, her only option was to kill the shark, so that she could safely swim to shore. But she needed a decoy, a lure so she could surprise the shark. The loss of a finger or toe would make swimming difficult, so instead, she scooped out one of her eyeballs and threw the bloody mess in the water. Then she dove in.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_taser">Buzzer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_mp5_grunt">Nightstalker</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heatleather_desc">No one knows this business better than you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_alien_maul">Alpha Mauler</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_grunt_01">Chains Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shorty_m_extended_short">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_troll_desc">Now here is a troll that is tired of hiding under the bridge.$NL;$NL;Why not see the world, pillage a village, take the local inhabitants gold treasures and flee from the the angry mobs instead? </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dawn_of_the_dead">The Undead</string>
	 <string id="bm_sm_wish">The Death Sentence Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_cosmos_desc">What is a heister, but stardust. The infinite cosmos, what do they contain? Who knows how many banks are out there on alien planets, just waiting for the right heister to come rob them.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_brass_knuckles">350K Brass Knuckles</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mdm">Mega Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_03">Nilam</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_alligator">Alligator Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nomegusta">No Me Gusta</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_same_01">Community Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_slicer">Slicer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sbl_b_long">Deep Range Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_laser_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_neon_red_solid">Solid Neon Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_greyscale10">Plastic Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_piro">The Ostentatious</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_maw_01">Omen</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_washington_desc">General of the Armies, Commander-In-Chief, Founding Father. Served this great nation for 8 years.$NL;$NL;The first ever president, and a great one at that.$NL;$NL;The 1st was one of the most popular presidents in history and the face of the $1 bill. Among criminals, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_usp_baaah">Ram Petite</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_judge_cat">BUFF</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bush_desc">Politician, Commander-In-Chief, father. Served this great nation for 8 years.$NL;$NL;A wordsmith, no doubt.$NL;$NL;The 43rd was one of the most unpopular presidents in history. Among criminals however, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_place_weapon">Place Weapon</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_cs4_01">Community 4</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp9_b_suppressed">Tactical Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_move_mask">Move Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_hockey">Hockey Stick</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rabbit">Graham</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_lones_01">Hoxton Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_contintental">The Prime</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_detector_desc">You&apos;ll never lose your keys again!</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_equipped">Equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_death_rider_desc">The fourth and final horseman of the Apocalypse is Death himself. Wherever Death went, Hades always followed with jaws wide open, ready to devour the souls of the victims slain by Death.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_denim">Denim</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_s_nostock">No Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_eye_stripes">Stripes</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_02">Boxey</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_03">Barrori Flex</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_move_weapon">Move Weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_t800_red">Infamy Red</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus_recoil">Stability</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_02">VIZOR </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mantis_desc">The common name for these lovely little fellows is &quot;praying mantis&quot;. The reason? It refers to the prayer-like posture where it folds its fore-limbs. More commonly however it&apos;s refered to as the preying mantis, because of it&apos;s nature.$NL;$NL;Basically, they eat anything they can successfully capture and devour.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_franklin_desc">World-renowned polymath, author, printer, political theorist, postmaster, scientist, inventor, civic activist, statesman, diplomat, Founding Father.$NL;$NL;Titulated as &quot;The First American&quot; and the face of the $100 bill.$NL;$NL;Among criminals, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_navy_breeze">Navy Breeze</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baby_cry_desc">Waaaah, waah, wah, WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH, wah, WAAAAAAAAH, WAAAAAAH!$NL;$NL;WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH, wah, WAAAAAAAAH, WAAAAAAH, Waaaah, waah, wah. Wah. WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hockey">Hockey Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_patton">Old Blood and Guts</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_almirs_beard_desc">Some say that real men don&apos;t shave, but the truth is that real men can&apos;t shave. Ordinary razors simply bounce off the dense, magnificent foliage that is a truly full Almir beard.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_baka_same">Royal</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45rds_v2">Riktpunkt 45 Degree Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_05_desc">As a leader, he has had to sacrifice much throughout his career. Jobs, team members, personal goals- whatever it takes to get the job done. As Mesoamerican cultures sacrificed to the gods to appease them, so has Dallas sacrificed to the gods of heisting- the contractors. </string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_micstand_desc">Turn stage fright into stage domination!</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_bloodred">Blood Red</string>
	 <string id="steam_inventory_collection_lones_01">Hoxtons Collection</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_mouse">The Mouse</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ggac_desc">So arrives the Harbinger! Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The brain even has a special region for it. This is definitely not a human skull, it belongs to a demon of carnage.$NL;$NL;Look ye into the sky, as fire rains down from the heavens, followed by molten gold, to cover the land in a glittering metal blanket of awesome to illuminate your greatness as a heister. With every bar that is raised, you step up to the challenge, and have so done yet again. Construction of a throne is underway here at the OVERKILL office, so that we may bow to and worship your utterly divine skills at not getting beaten by anything we throw at you.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bandit_desc">The wide-brimmed hat, the steely gaze and the scarf pulled up over the mouth. A combination so iconic, so classic and so effective that it remains the staple for gangsters and heisters everywhere.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_mod">Modify weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_03">Producers</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_baba_yaga_desc">Occasionally villainous, always mysterious. The Baba Yaga stalks the dark forests of Slavic myth. She flies around in a mortar, wields a pestle and lives in a hut that stomps about on giant chicken legs.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_gator">Machete</string>
	 <string id="bm_e_wish">The Mayhem Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pokachu">Electarodent</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_owl">Rasmus</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_category">Type</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_simpson_desc">Some say his racing leathers are made from bleached dolphin skin, and that his oily secretions are prized in Chinese medicine. All we know is... he&apos;s called The Tids.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_recoil">Stability</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_pack_01">Wolf Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_gunslinger">Duelist</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_1_desc">No movement penalty, no visibility.$NL;$NL;This is the standard two-piece suit that any self-respecting criminal should wear.$NL;$NL;It provides no extra protection but has the highest concealment factor, making it the best choice for a heist where you want to go undetected and blend into the crowd.$NL;$NL;Suits are usually reserved for special occasions, such as weddings, funerals and bank robberies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wayfarer_desc">These shades belonged to five strangers. John was hired to kill a group of people who were about to commit the perfect crime. They all dressed the same and had code names so they were easy to identify.$NL;$NL;However, John arrived too late to the scene. The police were already there. He made sure the strangers were all dead before he left the scene.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_desert_tech">Desert Tech</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_devourer">Devourer</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_erma">MP40 Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_textures">Pattern</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clinton_desc">Politician, Commander-In-Chief, father. Served this great nation for 8 years.$NL;$NL;A ladies man, no doubt.$NL;$NL;The 42nd was one of the most peaceful presidents in history. Among criminals however, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_04">The Marine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_07_desc">Skulltooth the Terrible, ye most mystical of Pirate Kings, will shiver the timbers of any law enforcement officers present. Yarr!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_s_unfolded">Unfolded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_surprise">War Face</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_tlr1">Tactical Pistol Light</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_01">Ameonna</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dnm_desc">A strange thing, the human skull. It&apos;s both simple and beautiful. Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a special region for it.$NL;$NL;You finished all heists on the Normal difficulty? What are you, some kind of gangster? Maybe this mask will suit you after all.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_rarity_common">Common</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_s_solid">Solid Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_haven_solid">Solid Haven</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ching">Galant Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_red_hurricane_desc">&quot;In Soviet Russia, Red Bear kills you.&quot; No one knows exactly who the Red Bear was; some say he was just a myth, a symbol of the motherland and everything that was strong, combined into one being. Only the stories are known and told again and again. Like that one time, when he killed a bunch of bears and came back home all in red, drenched in blood.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_kampfmesser">Krieger Blade</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_buy_new_weapon">Buy new weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_winchester_b_long">Long Range Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_dallas_rising_desc">There needs to be a harsh statement made about the rotting corruption penetrating every sinew of today&apos;s society. The self-deception, the scrambling for a false sense of a security. But you&apos;re not safe, not now and not ever. The American Dream is a brutally scarred nightmare disguised to lead poor souls astray. Take what you need; grab your future by the throat and force down your ambition until it chokes on it. Mark where you tread with the bodies you leave in your wake.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_zipper_desc">The zipper mask consists of two parallel tracks of teeth that can be interlocked or separated by the pulling of a slide between them.$NL;$NL;Separate the zipper when you need to communicate.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dragan_begins">Dragan Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ninja_hood">Kuro Zukin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_olympic_cola">Novus Paradox</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fairbair">Trench Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_yellow">Plastic Yellow</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_02">Sloth</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_daft_desc">For the truly detached and impassive, we provide the Android mask. Lightweight alloys, chromium finish and really cool LED lights means this mask is ready for the bank job or the dancefloor. Alas, it does not make you fluent in six million languages.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_03_desc">It isn&apos;t fair, is it? There you stand, deserving of everything in life and the cosmos refuse to give unto you. The Others smile and dance, while you twist inward, wondering why no one has gifted you with whatever success everyone else has been given for free. Oh, you want it so, but how could you ever dare to take it?</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_health">Health</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clown_56">The Starved</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_cmore">See More Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ak_s_skfoldable">Skeletal Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_topaz">Ice Pick</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_crowgoblin">Crow Goblin</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_div_perbend">Per Bend</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pumpkin_king">Pumpkin King</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_rx01">Trigonom Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_iron_sight">Iron Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_brick">Hotline 8000x</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tinted_love">Tinted Love</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_sfs_01">Scarface Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_10">Mega Tiara</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richard_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Richard Returns mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_03">Kurgan&apos;s Gas Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_ability_chico_injector_desc">When consumed  the user cease to feel pain and become fearless. The lack of pain let the user rampage through the heart of battles longer than any other and the lack of fear make him a frightening and obvious threat for his enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_g26">Chimano Compact Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mmj">Z.A.M.S Helmet</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spider">Tarantula</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_balaclava">Balaclava</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_divided_desc">The Trickster Demon is a mischievous being, who thrives on creating chaos and spreading mayhem. It might not look that scary, but don&apos;t let that smirk fool you; its idea of &quot;fun&quot; differ greatly from what you or me would enjoy. Trust me on this.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_moneybundle">Money Bundle</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_poolrepair">Repairman</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_mariachi_black">Calavera</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_deagle_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_red_desc">For those October bike rides.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_stech_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_same_01">Community 1</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_purple_desaturated">Amethyst Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_02_desc">A murky green that adds a touch of subtle mystery to your profile. The FBI will appreciate your fondness for their own green uniformed team. Not that it won&apos;t stop them firing on you openly anyway!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_optimist_prime_desc">&quot;Be the change you want to see in the world.&quot;$NL;$NL;That&apos;s what the Optimist believes.$NL;$NL;As the leader of a peaceful group of robots, he feels it is his responsibility to combat rival bands of robots obsessed with negativity and extermination. His prime weapon: rolling out positivity through constructive reasoning and unbiased logic.$NL;$NL;Or through forced upgrades. Which are compulsory.$NL;$NL;This mask is Poetry Jam mask. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nixon">The 37th</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_khaki_eclipse_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_quality_good">Broken-In</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_bonus">Boost</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m32_smosh">Homewrecker</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_judge">The Judge Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shrew_g_ergo">Ergonomic Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_weapon_desc">In armed robberies, beating the victims with firearms is usually more common than to shoot or stab them. You usually either Buttstroke someone with a rifle or Pistol-whip them with a handgun.$NL;$NL;This is the quickest melee attack.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_cqc">Kunai Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_vhs">Lion&apos;s Roar Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_damage_effect">Knockdown</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_first_aid_kit">First Aid Kit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rageface_desc">Dodging a cloaker kick and your buddy gets hit. Lol.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_locked_breech">Complete the &quot;Knife Legislation&quot; Aldstone&apos;s Heritage Job to unlock.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_barrel">Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_mp5">Akimbo Compact-5 Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_cracks1">Crackled</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_max">Sangres</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_m90">M90 Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shovel_desc">The K.L.A.S. shovel is used by military forces for a variety of purposes. The shovel can be found among survivalists, freedivers, campers, hikers, gardeners and war re-enactment groups. It can also be used as a weapon - sharpen the edges and you&apos;ll be cutting through flesh and bone. If you use it correctly, that is. Which you don&apos;t.$NL;$NL;This weapon can be charged to deal more damage by holding the melee button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hothead">Hothead</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_troll">The Troll</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_05">Mega Optimist Prime</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sports_utility_mask_desc">Forget bulky and unfashionable helmets, this glorious sucker is the best friend of every adrenaline junkie. The face-guard is made out of tough ABS plastic and it provides solid protection against snow, sand blasts and hail drops. Just avoid heavy blows to the head. Be the envy of your airboarding friends, brah!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_00">Blister Head</string>
	 <string id="bm_chains_rising_desc">Go darker, hear the calling and become the daredevil of nightmares with an itchy trigger finger. This is a tribute to all the moments you have cheated death out on the field. You are a soldier from an army of darkness. Your veins are pumping of adrenaline and you have enough ammo packed to take on hell itself. Invincible in the darkness and ready to challenge death. All chains will break this time around and anyone in your path will meet their maker.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ribcage">Ribcage</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_cs">Lumber Lite L2</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tiara">Tiara</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_doctor_desc">A naso-buccal mask usually associated with hospitals and ambulances. This mask disables the host from spreading airborne viruses by catching the bacteria-laden saliva and mucus that is discharged upon sneezing or coughing. Both doctors and patients wear this, so you should ask yourself: am I the sick or the healthy one? The disease or the cure?$NL;$NL;In any case - it&apos;s fever season, and the only prescription is dead Bulldozers.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_overkill_mask_desc">Ten-shun! Right, listen up, you heisting bastards. You&apos;re heading into war. You&apos;re gonna feel the sting of battle. And in war you need a leader. Meet General OVERKILL. He&apos;ll be there to make sure you go through those cop bastards like crap through a goose. Dismissed!</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_army_deep_green">Deep Army Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_m45">Akimbo Swedish K Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_akmsu_ginger">Wintry Wonder</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_demon">The Horned Beast</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_briefcase">50 Blessings Briefcase</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bear">Mark</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_billy">Billy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_g_ergo">Ergonomic Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_aa12_barrel_silenced">Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_aug">UAR Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_p226_skf">Insomnia</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_sentry_gun_silent">Suppressed Sentry Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_sig">Signature Magnifier Gadget</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_agatha_vanguard_veteran_desc">When you&apos;re trying to reclaim your homeland and King&apos;s law from the upstart Masons, you need strength, support and a fearsome visage. This Vanguard helm provides all three.</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_normal">Normal</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_02_desc">Knowing when not to quit is harder than knowing when to throw in the towel. Don&apos;t get sidetracked by vanity or foolish pride. Sometimes, you get so wrapped up in a problem that you don&apos;t see what the problem really is. It gets everyone in a lot of trouble. Bad trouble. So do what&apos;s right, and you can&apos;t go wrong.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_lemming_css">The Master</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_smoke_screen_grenade_desc">Drop one of these and you&apos;ll vanish in a cloud of smoke, leaving your enemies struggling to take aim at you. Dodging bullets is a piece of cake when they can&apos;t see you properly.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ching_css">This Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ammo">Ammunition</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fight_desc">Secret fighting style found far in offshore territories</string>
	 <string id="bm_mod_incompatibility_some">some</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_02_desc">Things are not always what they seem. Behind the mask there is a face, true. But what&apos;s behind the face? Another face, perhaps. How do you know where the real person is, and how many layers must be removed before you reach the core - the inner self?</string>
	 <string id="bm_mega_clover_desc">The Mega Clover mask is an evolved version of the original mask. It symbolises transcendence and catharsis.$NL;$NL;Thank you for your support.$NL;$NL;OVERKILL salutes you!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shirai">Shirai</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fork">The Motherforker</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_grip">Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_red">Fiery Hardtail</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_richard_begins">Richard Returns Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ching_wwt">Freedom Fighter</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_pocket_ecm_jammer_desc">A small device for intercepting and overriding nearby encrypted signals. With sophisticated algorithms for sniffing out and disrupting wireless data, the Pocket ECM Device gives the user an edge both while hiding in the shadows and in the heat of combat.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hockey_desc">A hockey mask is a mask worn by hockey goaltenders to protect their heads from injury.$NL;$NL;It is also the iconic robber mask, hand-crafted using only high-quality materials. Instead of protecting you from pucks, it protects you from being recognized while going about, doing your thing.$NL;$NL;You know, the thing you do so well. Stealing.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_buy_selected_mask">Assemble mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eng_03">The Cultist</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_eggian">Eggian</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saiga_buck">Brain Bucket</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_01_desc">If a heister walks down the street wearing this mask, the world knows he&apos;s not afraid of anything, nine lives be damned!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_max_desc">The skull is Death, Sangres&apos; faithful companion throughout his career. The gold tooth is the coin that has been paid. The kill counter represents his past as a hitman, the blood-red ruby the new wealth he&apos;s seeking in the US. Sangres&apos; name speaks of the many bloody episodes in his life, and that red blood is also present on his mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_scorpion_burn">Angry Silence</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_taser_desc">This is the one you have been waiting for. Exact sweet, electrifying revenge against those smug tasers. Eat it, lightning bolt!</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_wing">Wing Butterfly Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_fg_discrete">Discreet Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_shock">Monkey Wrench</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_fg_wood">Zombie Hunter Pump</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_kidswool">Rookie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dallas">Dallas</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_czech">Akimbo Czech 92 Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bodhi">Bodhi</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_skf">Special Force</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_bloodsplat">Commemore</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_welder_desc">A truly legendary Enforcer mask.$NL;$NL;The story goes it was made for one of the premier hitters in the Pink Panther crew years back but he didn&apos;t have the guts to wear it. It&apos;d draw too much attention.$NL;$NL;Not your concern.$NL;$NL;This mask is an Infamy tree reward. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_benelli_cs4">Nutshell</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gentleman_default">Moody Longcoat</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_tactical">Frontline</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mp9">CMP Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_aviator">The Heat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robberfly_desc">The Asilidae, also known as robber fly or assassin fly, are powerfully built, bristly flies who are known for their notoriously aggressive predatory habits. They feed on other insects and as a rule, they wait in ambush and catch their prey in flight.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_s_nostock">QD Sling Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_base">Base</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_b">The Outlander</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_06">DRONE </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rubber_male">Mr. Mannequin</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_fal">Falcon Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_rage_b_long">Overcompensating Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_scorpion">Akimbo Cobra Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_combusto">Firestarter</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_fg_mp5sd">The Ninja Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_pd2_clan">Community</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_01">Fluffedup</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_nuclear">Radioactive</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dillinger_death_mask_desc">John Herbert Dillinger was a famous American bank robber.$NL;$NL;His gang robbed two dozen banks and even four police stations.$NL;$NL;Dillinger himself escaped jail twice and was widely known as one of the meanest motherfuckers in the depression-era United States.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_dark_red_black">Dark Red / Black</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gage_blade_desc">The Gage Blade is one of Gage&apos;s own personal favorite ballistic face masks. It will protect your face from one or two 9mm bullets before your head explodes.$NL;$NL;Without this mask, Gage wouldn&apos;t be the wonderful human being he is today.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heistwrinkled_purple">Night Heister</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_continental">Lucky</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghost">The Spectre</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_gunslinger_desc">The ensemble is perfect for the heister who feels the need to face off at twenty paces.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fists">Fists</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_speedrunner">SpeedRunner</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nixon_desc">Politician, Commander-In-Chief, father. Had an ambition to serve this great nation for 8 years.$NL;$NL;He wasn&apos;t a crook, for sure.$NL;$NL;The 37th was the only president who resigned from office. Among criminals however, he remains extremely popular.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_no_items">Not available</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_a">The Cannula</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biker_classic_desc">This old school motorcycle helmet is part of a legacy that all bikers around the world cherish. And it&apos;s more about nostalgia rather than style. This helmet transports you back to the golden biker days of the 1940&apos;s.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_mod">Mod</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_msk_grizel">Clover</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brainiack">The Brainiac</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_event_bah">Goat Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_olympic_s_short">Shorter Than Short Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smiley">Smiley</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nomegusta_desc">When you&apos;re robbing a bank and there&apos;s only a toast in the deposit box.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_p90_same">PIXELWAR</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_panther">Brandon</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_clown">The Showman</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_charge_time">Charge time</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_gre_m79_cola">AtomAtom</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_01">INTERCEPTOR </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_grunt">Desert Commando</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_03">Envy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_ns_linear">Funnel of Fun Nozzle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lone_desc">Whether you&apos;re a murderous desperado or a lone, brooding ranger, sometimes you need to hide your identity. What does that better than a slender black eye-mask, covering a third of your face?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cthulhu">Cthulhu</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_twins">Okinawan Style Sai</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_04">The Classically Fancy Super Villain</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_locked_ching">Complete the &quot;Rapid Retribution&quot; Aldstone&apos;s Heritage Job to unlock.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_shutter">Shutters</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_03">Black Beanie</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ppk">Gruber Kurz Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_pink_gray">Pink / Gray</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_no_mod">No Modification</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tam_desc">For a thousand years, the traveller slept, biding his time until the stars did align and a mortal of sufficient ability would unlock him from his unholy prison. Rejoice! For that day has come. Wield this power... wisely.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_avenger">Skull Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_cs4">DEVA</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g18c_m_mag_33rnd">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_flm_desc">On the one-thousand-and-first night, there was no light. But neither was it needed, for legends tell of an unruly rogue, who donned a visage that would allow all to be seen.$NL;$NL;Activate Night Vision Mode by holding down the Fire Mode button.</string>
	 <string id="bm_lucky_luciano_desc">Considered the &quot;father of modernized crime&quot;. Not clear why he&apos;s nicknamed &quot;Lucky&quot;, but he managed to get arrested 25 times and never spent a day in jail. And he survived a throat slashing as he refused to join another mob. Either way, a true inspiration.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mr_pickle_desc">Lean, mean, green killing machine. The perfect mask to wear when you&apos;re in a pickle and need to make like a banana and split. Be water, my friend.</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_congo_pink_solid">Solid Congo Pink</string>
	 <string id="german_desc">Nationality: Swedish$NL;Age: 34$NL;$NL;Wolf was a law abiding citizen for most of his life. During the worldwide economic slump of the late 2000&apos;s, Wolf&apos;s company temporarily had only one client that got cold feet and wanted out. His company went bankrupt.$NL;$NL;He now pursues a criminal career with the same determination that drove him when he used to run his company.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_krampus_desc">Been a bad boy or girl this year? Then you can expect a visit from Krampus. Or a phone-call from Bain.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_biglips_desc">Throw someone a lip by wearing this mask.$NL;$NL;The thing that gets people is the two fleshy folds that surround the mouth of this mask, the biggest lips you ever saw.$NL;$NL;Open your mouth and say &apos;aaah&apos;, directed the bank robber.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_01_desc">Klaus isn&apos;t a particularly smart dog, but what he lacks in brains, he makes up for in heart, and is always ready to share his bones with the rest of the pack.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_mod_preview">Mod Preview</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_frag_com_desc">This is an updated version of the classic hand grenade. Even though the original frag grenade is still in use, this new sleek design will provide that OVERKILL touch to each blast. Still as cheap and still as effective.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lincoln">The 16th</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_navy_blue">Navy Blue Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_orchish">Orcish</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_barrel_plural">Barrels</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_hypnotic">The Hypnotica</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_illuminati">The Illuminati</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mmh_desc">Aristotle, Plato, Confucius, Michelangelo, DaVinci, Newton, Galileo... artists and thinkers forever engraved in history. And somewhere in that history, the place of a heister is assured. Contained herein is their essence, so magnificent in combination that the very surface of the mask can barely contain it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_gadget_plural">Gadgets</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_arblast_explosion_desc">Bolt with an explosive tip that detonates on impact.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ppk_skf">Under the Radar</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rubber_female">Mrs. Mannequin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_same">Admiral</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_slot_lever_desc">A sad (and hilarious) remnant of a week-long Vegas binge gone too far. Bludgeon cops with the power of poor luck and poor life decisions.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_tenderizer">Tenderizer</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_03">Byrne</string>
	 <string id="bm_beret">Commando</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_04">One-Eyed Jessicah</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_default_desc">Use the heisters default gloves</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_buck">Buckler Shield</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_spread">Accuracy</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_disables_cosmetic_bonus">Boosts from this mod overwrite boosts from weapon skins.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_demonictender_desc">A horrifying mask shaped like the head of a demon.$NL;$NL;Not much is known about it other than the name - Kenneth.$NL;$NL;Now, this vengeful spirit has returned to earth to haunt mankind once more.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_unselect">Unselect</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_cobray_ns_silencer">Werbell&apos;s Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_event_red">First World</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_happy_desc">Santa, more known as Santa Claus, Saint Nicholas, Father Christmas and Kris Kringle (?) is a man of epic proportions. Words like legendary, mythical, historical and folkloric best describe this beast of a man.$NL;$NL;This particular mask is the Happy Santa mask. Big smile and super jolly with red cheeks and all, wearing this you&apos;ll even bring the most negative of Bulldozers into a joyous smile.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grendel_desc">Genetic mutation is the key to our evolution. Assuming that our evolution is of the green, scaly, homicidal, irradiated kind.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_hippie_desc">Back when this was in style, heisting was a much simpler affair. Hacking was carried out with a blade, and the raw skill of a gunman, safecracker or getaway driver was all the more important.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_t800_default_desc">Be you a time-traveling killing machine, or just some guy trying to keep the spirits of 1950s greasers alive while you pull your next heist, this set has got you covered.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_01_desc">True class is eternal when accepted by scoundrels and heroes alike.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_joy">Joy</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_bodybags_bag">Body Bag Case</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_p226_grunt">Ghurka</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_alex_desc">One half of a brother and sister duo, Alex. Like swans, they are fierce. Unlike swans, they wield chainsaws and SMGs. Like swans, they are closely bonded. Unlike swans, they have a penchant for slaughter.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_bonus">Has Bonus</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_div_perpale">Per Pale</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_simpson">The Tids</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_min_detection">Minimum Detection Risk!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_camohex">Greed</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_combusto_desc">This clown used to be a master of pyrotechnics, having a fire breathing number that no one could top. His competitors in the not-so-known-firebreathing-clown-scene were unhappy with his success... And spiked his cocktail.$NL;$NL;With third degree burns on his face and an evil look in his eyes he fought fire with fire and set the other clowns ablaze. But he didn&apos;t stop there, the fiery hatred in him burned too bright. Now he seeks to set the world on fire.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_burn_01">Sydney Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chains_desc">The mask of Chains.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brazil_baby">Brazil Baby</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sokol_begins_desc">This is a clean version of Sokol&apos;s iconic mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_03">Mega Conquest</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mandril_desc">John the mandrill monkey. Mandrill&apos;s are closely related to baboons and even more to the drill. Not the kind of drill you use in a bank robbery, but the monkey drill, silly you! John is a monkey known for his sardonic one-liners, including the catch phrase &quot;unidentified monkey screech&quot;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_pugio">Diving Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_max_begins">Sangres Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_04">Retro Chains</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shuno_b_heat_long">Heat Sink Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_legacy">Akimbo M13 9mm Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_warm_yellow_olive_green">Warm Yellow / Olive Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_elastic_tam_desc">This weapon skin is an Achievement Reward, it cannot be traded or sold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_invader_desc">I want to belie... ZAP! May the fo... ZAP! Live long a.. ZAP! Why can&apos;t we all just get along? Because ZAP! That&apos;s why.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bear_desc">hello from Russia.$NL;$NL;I think it will be the best game in the world.$NL;$NL;It&apos;s just a bear.$NL;$NL;Just before there was an empty.$NL;$NL;Thank you$NL;$NL;- Vasiliy</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_player_styles">Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_max_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Sangres mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_bullets">Bullets</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_buha_desc">Probably one of the angriest looking clown masks you have ever seen.$NL;$NL;It almost puts Wolf&apos;s mask to shame.$NL;$NL;Almost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_02">Green Beanie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_02">Retro Hoxton</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_polymer_cs4">MURICA</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_customize_armor">Customize Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_butch_pack_free">Butcher Mod Pack</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_item_unlocked">Available</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_b_short">Stubby barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_death_rider">Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_chico_injector">Requires the Kingpin perk deck equipped</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dnm">The Normal Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_m_pmag">Tactical Mag.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_the_king_mask">The King</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_vlad_armor">Vlad Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_desperadoleather_desc">Quick on the draw, always on target.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hoxton_clean">Hoxton Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_02_desc">That loaf of bread you wanted. Imagine that hunger one thousandfold. More than just a lack of food, your very soul is deprived of sustenance until it&apos;s as empty on nourishment as your belly. If starvation could continue beyond death, this is the visage it would take. But such a plight can be a mighty motivator for heisting.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_raincoat_desc">A classic yellow raincoat that helps keep its wearer dry. The bright color also improves traffic safety when heavy rain impairs visibility.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spackle">Spackle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_churchill_desc">Politician, prize winner, owner of many medals and the first honorary citizen of the United States of America. By some it was said that he had a flawed character, saying; &quot;never had people admired and despised a man simultaneously to the same extent; never had such opposite extremes been combined in the same human being.&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_basset">Grimm 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_hs2000">Akimbo LEO Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_08_desc">Where did they come from, the ones who gifted mankind with the greatest gift, the ones whose civilization may lie beneath the surface of earth and water? Whoever they were, most traces of their existence has been wiped away by the passage of time. Hoxton, the traveler in search of a new future, may not know the truth, but he bears their mask nonetheless in honor of the origin of the Secret.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_g_hgrip">Rubber Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ns_battle">Ported Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cas_police">Police</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_usp_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_black">Black Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r93_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_weapon_cosmetic">Apply skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mummy_desc">The face of a mummy that has had its skin and organs preserved. Either intentional or incidental exposure to extreme cold (ice mummies!), low humidity, lack of air or chemicals might have caused this.$NL;$NL;Who knows what part of the world it is from? Having been preserved for the longest time, its ready to be exposed to the world again.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_model70_baaah">Don Pastrami</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_plainsrider_woodland">Arctic Plains</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_matcap_solid_magenta_desaturated">Royal Ruby Purple</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_mods">Modifications</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_grenades">Throwable</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ranger_desc">This mask was originally designed to be part of a complete head-to-toe heisting outfit. However, field testing revealed that the gaudy spandex suit offered no protection against bullets, knives or grenades. The mask, however, was found to be lightweight, durable and stylish. It&apos;s heistin&apos; time!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_tan_khaki">Khaki</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_volt">Volt</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_xmas_tuxedo_desc">T&apos;was the heist before Christmas, and all through the vault. Not a tumbler was stirring, and it was all Locke&apos;s fault.  He forgot to pack the drills in the bags with care, but didn&apos;t notice until the heisters were already there. While Twitch sat a&apos;waiting, all snug in the van, Jimmy smashed in a window, just because he can. On Clover! On Sangres! On Jacket and Wick! Not a single heister truly believed, that Vlad&apos;s brother-in-law was really Saint Nick.</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_bone">Bone Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_sight">Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_poolrepair_desc">When in doubt, always go the repairman route. It may be the most braindead setup in countless sleazy movies, and a generator of trashy innuendos, but it&apos;ll get you in just about anywhere. Most folks will go nuts if they can&apos;t use their toilet or TV, and the rich just gotta have their pools in tip-top shape. The Pool Guy (or Gal) is usually a welcome visitor. It&apos;s a rather practical outfit too, with plenty of pockets, and flexibility for maneuvering in tight spaces. And in those cases when you need to draw in water to crack a safe, who&apos;s going to argue?</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_driverleather_desc">A favorite of Twitch&apos;s. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_mustang">Mustang</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_agatha_knight_desc">Excavated from the arid wastelands of Tenosia, the helmet of this Agathian Knight could protect him from swords and arrows, but not from the bloody ambitions of a leader as delusional as King Alphonso.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_gold_clean">Golden</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_s_kv">Solid Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_hiphop_desc">The rhythm of the oppressed, a savage rage that brews from the intellectual musings of urban street poets, trying to be heard about the noise of the inner city. The voices of the ghetto will echo forever, and the walls of the social prison will crumble, to open the floodgates of a new day.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_twitch_orc">The Orc</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_01">The Clawer</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_buluc">Undead Peacock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pain">Venger</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_cola">AdHoc Mono</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_b_beowulf">DMR Kit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shirai_desc">Get over here! And let me tell you about the most badass ninjas you ever heard about. They are the protectors of our world and they only accept the best warriors. They are given the most kickass mask to show that they are better than everyone else. Here is your mask, welcome to the clan.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_s_pts">Tactical Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_08">RAPTOR </string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_desperadoleather">Pistolero</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_sneak_desc">Wealth through stealth.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_04_desc">Some Voodoo priests claim to know the secret of eternal life. There&apos;s no guarantee that wearing this mask will grant it, but it&apos;ll likely scare the crap out of your enemies. And it might get you invited to a Jamaican barbecue.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_b_suppressed">Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_meat_cleaver">Dragan&apos;s Cleaver Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_quality_mint">Mint-Condition</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_none">No Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_lower_reciever">Lower Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_wa2000_baaah">Long Horn</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fear_desc">Do not worry, the staff looking after you will not be annoyed or think you are a wimp when you tell them you don&apos;t like needles.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_04">Lady Liberty</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_04">Hoxton, The Infiltrator</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tiger_desc">Tony uses his fists of fury to beat the crap of anyone who messes with him.$NL;$NL;Tony was born in the 1970s and was of Italian-American nationality. Many people easily recognize Tony. Probably in part because of his Tiger mask, and in part because of his physical brutality when dealing with people he don&apos;t like.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_upper_reciever_edge">Exotique Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hothead_desc">With the rage of a fearsome volcano, the hostile Hothead lights up the night with blazing speed! What ignites his frenzied flame? From what does the raging bull run? Very few have caught up close enough to ask, and even fewer have gotten a coherent response!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grin">The Grin</string>
	 <string id="bm_mr_pickle">Pickle Face</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_preview_mods">Preview Mods</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_mustang_desc">Do you think you&apos;re a car? Oh? But do you think you&apos;re a MUSCLE car? No? Heisting isn&apos;t about looking fast and sleek, it&apos;s about looking furious and dangerous. Vroom, vroom motherfuckers!</string>
	 <string id="bm_paycheck_chains_desc">Paycheck Chains longs to be completely bonkers. But truth to be told, behind that mask he&apos;s just a regular guy trying to make an indecent living. When trying to push his normal self into craziness, he took a poodle hostage during a robbery when a police showed up. What crazy person would do that, right? But he picked the wrong vicious mongrel to mess with. The dog ended up biting everyone in the crew before they managed to escape the beast. News report after the robbery claimed the dog showed symptoms of rabies. Maybe Paycheck Chains will finally become as crazy as he wants to be...</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_switchblade_desc">Commonly used for settling the score between two New York teenage street gangs in the fifties. You can even sing along.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_04_desc">The rage of the tiger is legendary, and the king of the jungle will not be contained willingly. They may think they have you under control, but hell hath no fury like a caged tiger. As you break out, they will come to know this. Claws will rip and teeth will tear, flesh from bone, as you claim your kingdom.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_sword">The Pen</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_plague">The Plague Doctor</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chains_clean_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Chains mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mason_knight_veteran_desc">The helmet of the Knight Veterans of the Masons were effectively symbols of this powerful, upstart order. When peasants saw this helm, they knew that Malric&apos;s new order was close behind.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_de_gaulle_desc">For much between 1940-1969, the Constable was the dominant military and political leader of France. Refusing to accept his government&apos;s armistice with the German invaders in 1940, he set up his base in London, proclaimed himself the incarnation of France, and created the Free French movement. During the war he rallied the overseas colonies, especially those in Africa, organized the Resistance from abroad, and struggled to gain full recognition from the British and Americans.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_select">Select</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_sentry_gun_desc">To use the Sentry Gun, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Upon deployment it will use up 30% of your weapons&apos; total ammo. It can be destroyed by firing at it, but as long as it is not completely destroyed, picking it up will automatically repair it and return the remaining Sentry Gun ammo. As it runs out of ammo it will stop firing but it can be reloaded by re-deploying it after pick up.$NL;$NL;The Sentry Gun automatically aims and fires at targets that are detected by its sensors. It&apos;s commonly used as a distraction, drawing attention from you and your team.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_03_desc">This pilotka was found on a corpse near Lake Müritz in Germany. It was attached with a string around the poor, dead soldier&apos;s head. There were no other bodies next to unnamed fellow, and as the origin of the pilotka was russian, it&apos;s fair to assume that he stemmed from the same country. Speculations were many, none were true, but the most inspiring story was the one about a soldier so proud of the motherland that he tied his pilotka to his head before he died.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mrs_claus">Mrs. Claus</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_same">Throwback</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_geo_bendy">Bendy</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_stech">Igor Automatik Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_02_desc">Strike fast, strike hard, strike silently. You will leave even the cloakers sulking in shame.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_customize_gadget">Customize Gadget</string>
	 <string id="bm_donald_mega">God Emperor</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_suit_variations">Customize Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_msk_grizel_desc">Clover&apos;s mask represents what Clover both fears and hates most of all - wearing a mask as your normal face. The surgically-shrunken nose, the botox&apos;d lips and the expression of all-consuming vanity and self-obsession - all are symbols of fear and weakness, twisted into a horrifying parody.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_weapon">Weapon Butt</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_fg_moe">E.M.O. Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_g36">JP36 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_stoneface">Terminator</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_jade">Jade</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rudeolph_desc">Houston wore these at the Payday crews&apos; Christmas party until Hoxton told him he &quot;looked a proper tit&quot;. Ignore Hox. Embrace the spirit of Christmas.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unborn_desc">A once great actor who claimed to have become possessed by a demonic spirit started to wear a mask to hide his deformed appearance. The mask one day broke and what was hiding underneath could never be sealed again.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_02_desc">Why bother? Let the universe expand, die and grow dark. You have endless time to lift your fingers in protest at whatever mindless chore that demands you exert yourself in the slightest. Your life energy oozes from your soul, wasted and dissolved in the emptiness as you remain perpetually drained of ambition.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_sneak_suit">Tactical BDU</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_08">Mega Krampus</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lady_butcher_desc">If you received a dollar every time the Butcher was called a &quot;witch&quot;, a &quot;harlot&quot; or a &quot;banshee&quot; by her peers you could earn enough money to buy the entirety of Croatia. Cynical men around her bemoaned the fact that she was female, and felt endangered and distressed at the sight of her meteoric rise in the criminal underground. Keep in mind that the Balkans are not exactly known for their capacity to tolerate anybody who is in any way different, and one can only image the flat-out chauvinism and misogyny she must have dealt with while working with some of the most ruthless criminals every day of her existence. This mask shows how she is seen by both her rivals and her associates. It makes people feel afraid. As they should be.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mr_sinister">Blackhearted</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_biker_orange">Sunset Hardtail</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_eye">Eye</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dillinger_death_mask">The Dillinger Death Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_steam_item_rarity">Rarity: ##$rarity;##</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_surf_01">Bodhi Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rage_demon_desc">The skull as a symbol can either mean death or mortality, and we humans have always had a fascination for it. Wearing this motorcycle helmet looks powerful and intimidating.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_02">Wolf, The Maniac</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_king_of_jesters_desc">Wearing brightly coloured clothes and eccentric hats in a motley pattern, jesters have always had a place in these parts.$NL;$NL;Whether walking on stilts, performing with fire or telling jokes; their sole purpose is to spread joy in our hearts.$NL;$NL;However, this is your time to shine so why not put on the mask and spread some joy.$NL;$NL;So, pull out your gun, rob your guests and tell them it was all a big ploy.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tcn_desc">A mask only for the most ambitious heister.$NL;$NL;Take all the loot, leave nothing behind.$NL;This is the sign of a true criminal mind.$NL;Grab all the diamonds and small additions.$NL;Now you&apos;re a person with criminal ambitions.$NL;$NL;This mask is Poetry Jam mask. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any customization and the fee to put that together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chef_hat_desc">Whether you&apos;re a line cook flipping patties at a roadside diner, or an itamae dissecting toadfish at a $1000-a-table joint, this hat means one thing: you&apos;re the chef.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_bismuth">Bismuth</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_clear_mod_preview">Clear Preview</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shogun">The Shogun</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_barrel_ext_plural">Barrel Extensions</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_khaki_eclipse">Khaki Eclipse</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_gloves">Equip Gloves</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_tiger_desc">Why settle with one blade when you can have multiple?</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_agatha_knight">Agatha Knight Veteran</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_black_gray">Black / Gray</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_punkleather_desc">Not a chickenshit conformist.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pachy">Pachy</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_swap_preferred_slots">Swap Preferred</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bonnie">Bonnie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kage">Kage</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_03_desc">These frames harken back to a time when moon-landings were envisioned, all dreams were possible and people all dressed a little nicer.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_buha">The Rage</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_skin">Edit skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_remove_weapon_cosmetic">Remove skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_almirs_beard">Almir&apos;s Beard</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jw_shades">Collateral</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fancy_goat_desc">The penguin is the slickest heister in the animal kingdom, walking around with a &quot;know-it-all&quot; attitude, taking their time and taking what they want - when they want, not giving a damn. Put on this mask and show everyone you&apos;re the boss of things.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ancient_desc">A powerful alien race, described by some as the most advanced beings in the universe. Different races that have come in contact with them have different names for the Crossbreed.$NL;$NL;Strong, lean and intelligent, the Crossbreed takes the best from the DNA of each alien race that it meets, always making sure it evolves in the right direction.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_horned_king">The Viking</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_mod_mask">Customize mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_toon_03">Chains, The Weapons Expert</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_red">The Red Gunman</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_dallas_01">Dallas Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_unicorn_desc">Peter is a true legend and has been so for like, forever. A beast with a large, pointed, spiraling horn projected from its forehead, Peter is known by all of mankind as the go-to guy whenever you need to touch the rainbow. No, touch it. Touch the motherfucking rainbow. Now taste it.$NL;$NL;Shh. It&apos;s OK. You did good.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_celtic1">Celtic Cross</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_magazine">Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_slicer_desc">After his brother&apos;s murder, Ikas joined an underground clan of ninjas to train and become their deadliest warrior. Ikas quickly proved himself and was put in charge of the whole American branch of the clan. His signature mask now inspires fear and respect and anyone who wears a mask like this will be seen as a brother of the Achilles Clan.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_buy_tradable">Purchase On Community Market</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_greedy_the_elf">Greedy The Elf</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_dark_gray_yellow">Dark Gray / Yellow</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smoker">The Specialist</string>
	 <string id="bm_mod_incompatibility_most">most</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_digital_camo">Digital Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_event_dinner">Slaughter Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_jumpsuit_desc">Certain career-making heists demand a lot extra from the gear you bring to the job. Mobility and durability can be the things that keep a heister from landing in handcuffs and this outfit was made to stop that from happening. A one-piece base, with a reinforced utility vest, it lets the wearer tackle a variety of terrain and movement while supplying ample carrying aids.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_babyrhino">Baby Rhino</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_secondary_deployable">Equip Secondary</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_03_desc">Never come between a cat and his prey, or a heister and his loot!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_concert_female_desc">When you descend into the roiling whirlpool that is the ecstasy of an Alesso concert, you better be wearing your best face. The Female Concert Goer is impassive and detached, because nothing matters but the music.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_croupier_hat">Wheeler Dealer</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_scarecrow_desc">Discourage crows, sparrows and law enforcers from entering your field of terror.$NL;$NL;The legend goes that in distant lands, there lived a god who knew everything yet could not walk. The greed of man found the god and beheaded it, thinking they could gain its wisdom.$NL;$NL;Instead, they were cursed with terror.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_chosen">Selected</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_find_in_crime_spree">This armor can be earned in the ##Crime Spree## gamemode. The skin cannot be traded or sold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_slimy_goat">Mastermind Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_global_value_collaboration">Collaboration</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_stats_max_detection">Maximum Detection Risk!</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_damage">Damage</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_cvc_woodland_camo">Woodland Camo Armor</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_happy">Hackaton</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_02">Keelhauled Alex</string>
	 <string id="bm_al_pacino">Al Capone</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mandril">John</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_page">Page $page;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_03">Felis Lynx</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mummy">The Mummy</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_whiskey">Rivertown Glen Bottle</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_molten">Molten</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_witch">Witch</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_jail_pd2_clan_desc">You know the deal. Say it once, say it twice, third time&apos;s the charm. And remember... he&apos;ll steal anything you want him to steal, he&apos;ll hack anything you want him to hack. So say his name, and he&apos;ll trade you from custody. Bain! Bain! B...</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_7_desc">Large movement penalty, high visibility.$NL;$NL;The improved combined tactical vest is a stolen experimental prototype made by Gensec Security Industries.$NL;$NL;Based on White Mesa technology it uses both soft and hard armor solutions. The perfectly fitted interlocking fiber layers tightly woven together with metal plates are specially angled to deflect projectiles and shield from explosions. In short, it provides complete protection.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_barf">Candy</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_sentry_gun_silent_desc">To use the Suppressed Sentry Gun, you need to place it by holding $BTN_USE_ITEM;. Upon deployment it will use up 30% of your weapons&apos; total ammo. It can be destroyed by firing at it, but as long as it is not completely destroyed, picking it up will automatically repair it and return the remaining Sentry Gun ammo. As it runs out of ammo it will stop firing but it can be reloaded by re-deploying it after pick up.$NL;$NL;The Suppressed Sentry Gun is the counterpart to the regular, louder Sentry Gun as it&apos;s more used to take out enemies than a classic distraction.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_01_desc">Mighty horned demon. Vengeful, weeping destroyer. Do not arouse her anger.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_01">Exalted</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_meter_desc">Our two handed great ruler is the biggest ruler we make. But don&apos;t let its size fool you, as there&apos;s nothing awkward or clumsy about this awesome ruler.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_solus">Planetary Tomb Guardian</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_dark_purple_blue">Dark Purple / Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_shogun_desc">Don the mask and feel like a Japanese general from a distant past.$NL;$NL;It is said that this mask was the mask of a mad and desperate warrior, who rose above the ranks and became a great general, winning many battles.$NL;$NL;Common sense will not accomplish great things. You must become mad and desperate to do so.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_fur">Fur</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_buy_mask_title">Mask stash</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oliver">Oliver</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jimmy_desc">Jimmy&apos;s second attempt at making a mask went much better - that&apos;s because he got some help from Gage. It represents the Grim Reaper himself if he was coked up. The mask captures both the crazy and deadly side of Jimmy, aimed to sending fear into his enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_sap">Leather Sap</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_css_01">Community Safe 6</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_neoncity_desc">The 90s called and wanted these gloves back, but the Payday gang said &quot;fuck it&quot; and kept them instead.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_c">The Perfect Stranger</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_cs3_01">Community Safe 3</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bodhi_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Bodhi mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullhard">The Hard Skull</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_samurai">Somen Mempo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_cleaver">Cleaver Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_ti_rarity">Rarity</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dripper">The Dripper</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_male_begins">Ethan Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_extra">Extra</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview">Preview weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dbd_03_desc">A dark forest is scary to anyone, no matter how old you are. You fear whatever is in it, and the things lurking in the shadows. But you seldom think of the actual trees. You never think of Dendron. And when you do, it&apos;s already too late. Dendron strikes without mercy. So fear not what&apos;s behind the trees, but instead the trees.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_heatleather">Master</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_zeus">Electrical Brass Knuckles</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_cartelboss">Impresario</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_spatula">Spatula</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_electric">Electric</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_inventory_tradable_weapon_skins">Weapon Skins</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_facepaint_football">Football</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_demon_desc">A beast that came from the abyss.$NL;$NL;It has a lion&apos;s body, bear feet and a leopard&apos;s mouth.$NL;$NL;Not much else is known of this beast, nor who designed the mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_skill_locked_sentry_gun_silent">Requires the engineering skill</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_kabar_tanto">Ursa Tanto Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_murky">Mercenary</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_barrel_ext">Barrel Ext</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_ostry">Kazaguruma</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_tactical_desc">These are higher quality than anything the Washington DC cops own.</string>
	 <string id="bm_armor_level_5">Flak Jacket</string>
	 <string id="bm_clr_magenta_warm_yellow">Magenta / Warm Yellow</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_deployables">Equipment</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_range">Range</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_ammo_bag">Ammo Bag</string>
	 <string id="bm_al_pacino_desc">The original mobster that really made the criminal way of life something to strive for. A given member of the Payday crew if he were alive today. But now you can at least cosplay him, making the police scared as they think they&apos;ve seen a ghost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_nin">Pounder</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_drm_khaki_regular">Khaki Regular</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_01_desc">As if high on radioactive spray paint, the power level has been turned up a notch and is now close to bursting. When you go on a heist, everyone around you will duck for cover as you roll on by. Every geiger counter in town is about to go haywire.</string>
	 <string id="bm_grenade_molotov">Molotov Cocktail</string>
	 <string id="bm_equipment_trip_mine">Trip Mines and Shaped Charges</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_rainbowmittens_desc">You&apos;re not in it for the money.</string>
	 <string id="bm_madame_st_claire">Stephanie &quot;Madame&quot; St. Clair</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor1">German Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_preview_mask">Preview mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_askn_ast_armor6">Navy Admiral</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_bonemittens">Skeletal</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_chopper_desc">The heister who shuns pretension may find this discreet set of gloves to be a perfect fit.</string>
	 <string id="bm_gloves_tiger_desc">Show your solidarity with the plight of big cats everywhere with these stylish hand-warmers.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_agave">El Verdugo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_aziz">Tactical Flashlight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_chac">El Ritmo</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_chac_info"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_fight">Empty Palm Kata</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_grip">Knuckle Daggers</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_hammer">Carpenter&apos;s Delight</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_hauteur_desc">Japanese Tanto knives (or short swords) are characterized by their dagger-like design.</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_machete">Machete Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_melee_selfie">Selfie-Stick</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_armor_skins">Armor Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_equip_melee_weapon">Equip melee weapon</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_btn_remove_mod">Remove modification</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_cash">Cash bonus</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_empty_mask_slot">Empty mask slot</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_gadget">Gadget</string>
	 <string id="bm_menu_safe_wwt_01">Aldstone&apos;s Heritage Safe</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_04">Mega Arch Nemesis</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ami_06">Mega Greed</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_01_desc">One of the most brutal and ruthless pirates to ever exist. But also one of the most unknown. Just the way Schneider wanted it. Instead, Schneider&apos;s moniker &quot;the Devil&quot; was much more well known. He found it more profitable if nobody actually knew his face. But tales of how the &quot;devil&quot; sailed the seven seas traveled among bars in the Caribbean. To &quot;spot the Devil on the horizon&quot; was a common saying when someone had disappeared out at sea. But the truth was that Schneider had forever buried them in a watery grave.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_amp_02_desc">Every ship come bearing tales of ghost. Restless phantoms seen by tired spotters late at night. Everything from Krakens to mermaids. But the tale of Keelhauled Alex is maybe one of the most feared. Alex had been stealing food during a long sail out at sea. As he was caught, he was sentenced to be keelhauled. Not a serious crime, but a serious punishment. But as Alex was beneath the boat, another ship opened fire, and Alex was abandoned and forgotten on the bottom of the ship. As the dust settled, his corpse was thrown into the depths. But ever since then, Keelhauled Alex walks ships at night, staring down everyone from captains to simple deck hands. It is said that he can gaze into your soul and devour it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ant_07">WASP </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_arch_nemesis">Arch Nemesis</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_aviator_desc">Everyone loves a good pair of sunglasses.$NL;$NL;But only the cockiest, most wanted, cops be damned sons of bitches are crazy enough to rob a goddamn bank wearing &apos;em.$NL;$NL;That&apos;s you.$NL;$NL;This mask is an Infamy tree reward. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any pattern, color or material as well as the customization fee to put these together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bny_04">Red Beanie</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bodhi_begins">Bodhi Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bonnie_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Bonnie mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brainiack_desc">This is the mask of someone who has a lot on his mind.$NL;$NL;Putting on this mask sparks an excessive, almost explosive desire to learn more about crimes and how to commit them.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_brutal">Road Rage</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bullet">The Bullet</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_bush">The 43rd</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_card_king_desc">A classic made into a mask. The standard 52-card deck is the most played deck of playing cards used today, and regardless if you are a rookie or professional player, you will most likely recognize this face. A proper poker face-mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_character_locked_desc">Equipping this mask slot will make you wear your preferred character&apos;s mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chico">Scarface</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_chico_begins">Scarface Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_clowncry">The Crybaby</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_02_desc">Solving logic puzzles as a brain teaser is a great way to unwind after some intense criminal activity. Hoxton likes games that lets him wrap his head around a problem and figure it out one step at a time with the clues given.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmo_03_desc">Violent games help Wolf getting into the mood for a heist. The more blood, gore and carnage the better. He prefers games that test your reaction and speed. Games where every second counts for your survival against a nearly endless horde of enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_cmt_04">Ursus Maritimus</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_concert_male">Male Concert Goer</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_concert_male_desc">Tie-dyed shirts are so 70&apos;s. Holding up a lighter went out in the 80&apos;s. Whistles and glow sticks were left behind in the 90&apos;s, and the 00&apos;s, well, the less said the better. The modern concert goer, however, favors the mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dawg">Dawg</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_destroyer_desc">A warrior spirit doesn&apos;t appear naturally. It isn&apos;t something you are born with. Like steel, it is forged in fire. It is beaten in the furnace of battle - tempered, polished and sharpened. This mask celebrates the birth of this warrior spirit - the furnace-born steel given wings.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_dgm">Golden Dallas</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ecp_female_begins">Hila Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_evil">Black Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_fable_mouse_desc">Quiet as a Mouse, you&apos;ll enter and exit silently and none will be the wiser. And if they should spot you, who would suspect such wickedness from such a small creature? But yes, you are capable of it - all of it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_firedemon_desc">The head of the legendary Graug. A towering being of fire and smoking darkness, bound in blackened iron mail. Shaped like a man, but horned and visaged like a cruel demon. Body consumed by a furnace heat, hotter than Hell itself. Knows all the best tunes.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_franklin">The First American</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gagball">The Gagball</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gagball_desc">Take a walk on the submissive side with a gagball stuck to your face.$NL;$NL;People wear these for a variety of reasons, one being roleplays involving bondage. This isn&apos;t necessarily the case though, as gagballs apparently can be used in bank robberies too.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghm_desc">So this is it- the time of reckoning. Our family of heisters against a power we haven&apos;t seen the limit of. I know one thing- we&apos;ll either come out of this together or die trying. We&apos;re the Clowns, the fucking gods of thieving, and we play by our rules. So, whatever comes next, we&apos;re ready for a blaze of golden glory.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_ghx_desc">I remember the first time I put on a mask. Was it really seven years ago? When you&apos;ve been doing something for a long time, you eventually end up at a crossroads. In this line of work, you&apos;re either staring down the barrel of a gun or looking at the sweet life. Everybody has to make their choice. Everybody has to decide what that choice is worth risking. For PAYDAY, it&apos;s always been all-or-nothing!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goat">Dolph</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_goat_goat">Goat Goat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_greek_tragedy">Greek Tragedy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_groucho">Groucho</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_grv_03_desc">Finely crested for glory, this elaborate headpiece will impress. Wear it proudly, displaying the fine embroidery for all to envy. But watch out for low doorways.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_gwm_desc">Has it been five years already? Damn. Not many make it this far into the life. This last year has been hard. Real hard. The family has been hit where we were most vulnerable, the cops are getting closer every day, and we&apos;re almost in over our heads. The situation would have killed most heisters or put them away forever, but we&apos;re not just any two-bit crooks. We&apos;re PAYDAY. We always get it done right. And we always get the gold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_hectors_helmet">The Hard Hat</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_horse">Don Juan</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_horse_desc">Don Juan loves slamming doors in.$NL;$NL;Knock, knock. Who&apos;s there? It&apos;s Don Juan. Prepare yourself.$NL;$NL;Pro tip: In Hotline Miami, you get 2200 points while performing ground kills against the wall when using this mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_infamy_hood">Kamul</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_infamy_lurker">Lurker</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jfr_02">Wolfgang&apos;s Cap</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jiro">Jiro</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_joy_begins_desc">Flair and flash always have to start somewhere. Sometimes it&apos;s a thumping white basline, pristine and cold, ready for action.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_jw_shades_desc">These shades belonged to a colleague of John&apos;s that he was hired to kill.$NL;$NL;It started like any other night. Only this night, he got a contract to kill another contract killer who was making rounds that day. John knew he had five stops to make and was using the same taxi cab between all of them.$NL;$NL;In the end, he didn&apos;t even need to do the deed himself - he was already dead when he found him.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_king_of_jesters">King of Jesters</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_krampus">Krampus</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_kwm_desc">A tribute to our legendary adventurer [MANY GUN] CLOVERAPTOR- solver of mysteries and bringer of The Mega Death! Giving up a dream of being a banker, he faced his destiny and defeated the Cop Wizard and his minions, the Law Elementals. Who knows if it was his own will, or that of his pushy Crime Dad, that allowed him to prevail, but we will be forever grateful for his service.$NL;$NL;OVERKILL Salutes You!</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_lone">Lone Heister</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mad_mask">Zero 68</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mantis">Sphodromantis</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mason_vanguard_veteran_desc">This helmet was unearthed in an elaborate barrow, indicating that the wearer enjoyed prestige in the Mason army. These great warriors appear to have been Malric&apos;s elite troops, perhaps having served with him in the failed Tenosian crusade.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_maui">Maui</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_maw_01_desc">The mask is made from ancient stone, with carvings from each previous owner, and a symbol that radiates immense power. As the writing on the edge suggests, it is the beginning of the end for anyone who opposes the wearer.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_mp2_04_desc">Tempy is our tame lion. He&apos;s been away for 2 weeks now and we miss him. Tempy loves all kind of cuddle, as long as it&apos;s done by us. If you spot Tempy: Do not approach him in any way. Please tell us where you&apos;ve seen him. But you will get mutilated if he gets close. Other than that, he&apos;s a doll and he loves sleeping in the sun. Also don&apos;t let him see any kids...that doesn&apos;t end well.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_myh_begins_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Duke mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_nun_town_desc">A Catholic nun may not seem like the obvious choice for a terrifying mask, unless you know an actual Catholic nun. In which case, you&apos;ll know any notions of gentle, grandmotherly penguins are without merit. These bitter crones are the personification of evil, dishing out thrashings to any young buttocks within reach.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_obama">The 44th</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_oni_desc">The Oni is a Japanese devil.$NL;$NL;They are hideous, gigantic ogre-like creatures that have sharp claws and two horns growing from their heads.$NL;$NL;Their skin may have any number of colors, though red and blue are most common.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_orangutang_desc">Rutger the motherfucking orangutan. If you&apos;re strolling down the jungle and suddenly face an orangutan, you&apos;re in trouble. Statistics show that one orangutan is as dangerous as ten hobos with shotguns. You remember that movie about dinosaurs with the big dinosaur in the end saving the kids? Know who killed the dinosaur after the credits? The kids did, but you know who killed the kids? Rutger the motherfucking orangutan did.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_a_desc">This mask is made of strange materials, holding it feels awkward. Wearing it feels even stranger.$NL;$NL;Putting on the mask, you feel like an outsider, a foreigner, someone who constantly changes locations, staying away, not wanting to be recognized by anyone.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_outlandish_c_desc">The mask of a stranger in a strange land.$NL;$NL;Masks like these were used in a lost civilization, in war, on soldiers; ceremonially, for burial rites and for shamanistic ceremonies to drive away evil spirits.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_owl_desc">Rasmus has an eye for secrets.$NL;$NL;Owls are nocturnal birds of prey. They are known for their large eyes in comparison to their skulls. They can&apos;t actually move their eyes, they swivel their heads instead and are able to swivel 270 degrees. Shit you didn&apos;t know, amirite.$NL;$NL;&quot;I don&apos;t know you!&quot; &quot;You&apos;re no guest of mine!&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pachy_desc">Pachy the Pachycephalosaurus, meaning thick headed lizard, wasn&apos;t never that thick headed really. He never took that name for himself, the other dinosaurs gave it to him because they were jealous of his high rolls in intelligence, spirit and wisdom. Having earned a robe and a wizard hat as a second prize at the local prehistoric spelling bee didn&apos;t make it any better.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pbm">Simon</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pbm_desc">A wanna-be robber tried to knock over a liquor store, but neglected to properly conceal his identity, opting instead to use the paper bag he got when he last shopped there! Needless to say, the idiot was quickly identified and taken into custody. With no hostages to trade for freedom, his criminal career was cut short. The event, which did not even prompt a local news headline, now stands as a stark reminder that some things are best left to professionals.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pig">Aubrey</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_daisy">Daisy</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_dirty_russian_desc">A good way to not get shot in the head is to wear a helmet, but when you want to protect just your face from bullets and identification this will do. Does it really look bulletproof? What are you? A coward? Grab your fear by the balls and headbutt it in the face with this mask on.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pim_hotelier_desc">The Continental only serves the people who can respect the rules of the assassins&apos; sanctuary. It&apos;s not a cult or a secret society, it&apos;s a necessity in a business where everybody is willing to kill for money and everybody in there is on someone&apos;s list of targets.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pitbull_desc">Arnold the Bulldog has always been a doge of great ambition.$NL;$NL;He wanted to build much body - and he did. He became the biggest doge in his little mountain town and received such prize.$NL;$NL;He then moved to the States, got into office, starred in a couple of weird doge movies called &quot;The Dogenator&quot; and &quot;The Dogenator II - such judgement&quot;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_plague_desc">A plague doctor mask for the Mastermind.$NL;$NL;In the words of the Bhagavad-Gita: &quot;Now I am become death, destroyer of worlds.&quot;$NL;$NL;Or at least, that was the art direction.$NL;$NL;This mask is an Infamy tree reward. It can&apos;t drop during a Payday and it can&apos;t be sold. Instead, it can be returned to your mask stash for free, but any pattern, color or material as well as the customization fee to put these together will be lost.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_pokachu_desc">Untrained, the Electarodent can be found nibbling sweet carrots or frolicking across Alpine meadows. However, fully trained, the Electarodent is most often found wielding Bernetti 9&apos;s and eating through the face-plates of Skulldozers.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rageface">Rageface</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rambo">The Troubled War Veteran</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_robo_santa_desc">This jolly, festive automaton has the heart of Santa. He keeps it in a box, under a pile of elf corpses, and surrounded by severed reindeer heads.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rust">Rust</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rust_desc">The Devil is a moniker that has followed Rust through most of his life. Therefore, Rust&apos;s mask is a combination of a smiling clown with ominous horns protruding from the forehead, letting everyone know that the Devil is here.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rus_hat_desc">The world would be very different were it not for the howling, freezing Russian winter. Napoleon and Hitler both learned this. History could be very different if they only packed a warm hat.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_rvd_01">The Dons</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_drunk">Tipsy Santa</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_santa_mad">Furious Santa</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_02_desc">Old school street smarts and butch toughness is what you get here. A no nonsense get-the-job-done personality. You won&apos;t find a more devoted guard for your loot than this fellow.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sdm_03">Frou Frou</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skm_07">Mega Pirate</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullmonkey">Clint</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skulloverkillplus_desc">OVERKILL salutes you, bringer of death, slayer of law enforcers and finisher of difficulties. Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it. This isn&apos;t a human skull however, this is something completely different.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_skullveryhard_desc">A strange thing, the human skull. Not that this skull looks that human anymore. Humans can often recognize a human skull, even if it&apos;s only partially shown. The human brain even has a specific region for it. There&apos;s something strange with this skull though.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smiley_desc">There was once a clown who couldn&apos;t smile. He watched as the other clowns brought joy and happiness to both young and old. He grew envious and angry, so to the point that he stapled his lips to his cheecks, giving him a wide grin. But instead of making everyone happy, they were all afraid, why, he did not understand.$NL;$NL;He came to the conclusion perhaps this was his calling, to make people afraid... Very afraid.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_01">Chibi Kitteh</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_07_desc">Any child of the 1980s would kill for this mask. Show everyone who really rules the neon highways.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_smo_11">Mega Anubis</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_06">Egyptian Wolf Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_07_desc">The Sumerians began an age of wisdom, music, spiritual strength and had the imagination to dream up ideas of how the world began. On the surface, Chains may be a professional weapons-master, but inside, he is larger than life itself, and thus honors the culture which this mask represents. </string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sms_08">Watchers Hoxton Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_spa_03">Bird of Prey</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sputnik_desc">Despite being just a tiny, beeping sphere, the original Sputnik sent political shock-waves across 1950&apos;s Washington. Send some criminal shock-waves around the capital with this vintage-yet-pimped version.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_stoneface_desc">These shades belonged to an assassin from a distant land. The assassin John was sent to kill was built like a machine. This one would prove to be hard. He used a customized Improved Combined Tactical Vest. He was fully armored and very tough. Behind all that armor however, John knew there was only flesh and bones.$NL;$NL;John managed to kill him in the end. He knew however that when he removed him from his place, another would replace him.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_stonekisses_desc">The pout is a facial expression that humans can make.$NL;$NL;It is a protrusion of the lips, especially as an expression of sullen discontent.$NL;$NL;Who would not be discontent, having had their horns sawed off like that.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_sydney">Sydney</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tane">Tane</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tane_desc">Tane was the god of the forest who used his mighty strength to separate his parents, the earth and the sky. Legends also credit him with creating Tiki, the first man. Thus, he created the world as we know it, and the people within it.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tcn">Criminal Ambitions</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_tounge_desc">This mask somehow simultaneously conveys and expresses opposing or contradictory feelings, beliefs, and motivations.$NL;$NL;Legend says that four creatures merged together, forming a greater entity with the face of this mask.$NL;$NL;To summarize, it is a scary fucking mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_vampire">The Vampire</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_vampire_desc">The Vampire is a mythological undead creature, said to feed on the blood of the living.$NL;$NL;Vampires can appear as normal humans.$NL;$NL;When attacked they will reveal their vampire visage where their face changes and they grow fangs and pointed teeth.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_velociraptor">Vincent</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_venomorph">Venomorph</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_viking_desc">Mounting the prow of Viking ships, the dragon head was used to scare off sea monsters and evil spirits. Dozers and Cloakers are evil, right? Why not give it a go and see if it can scare them away? But have your gun ready just in case. For safety.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_vlad_armor_desc">&quot;Hey! Payday clowns! Vlad here with a little something from the Motherland. I wore this beautiful heavy bastard all through my days in Donetsk. It ain&apos;t pretty like your delicate American masks, but it kept me safe!&quot;</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wasp">Vespula</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wasp_desc">Two pairs of wings, an ovipositor or stinger, no thickened hairs and a pair of talons. That&apos;s the wasp for you. Almost every pest insect species has at least one wasp species that preys upon it or parasitizes it. This makes the wasps very important in natural control of their numbers.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_water_spirit">Tawhiri</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_welder">The Butcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wmp_02">The Trophy Helmet</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wolf_clean">Wolf Begins</string>
	 <string id="bm_msk_wolf_clean_desc">This is a clean version of the iconic Wolf mask, before it was painted.$NL;$NL;Never liked how the original one turned out? This is your chance to change history.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_01_desc">You lock your eyes on your prize until they water. Unattended, your slacking jaw lets slip a drop of saliva onto the floor as the need for possession takes over. The person you pine for is an object, the object is a person. It matters not, to your blinded senses.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_04">Wrath</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_04_desc">There is a cold fire in your heart. All those who have wronged you will pay. If you so have to burn with them in the conflagration, you will extract payment for any perceived or actual slight against your person. There is no rationality to your rage- it must simply be indulged.</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_06">Gluttony</string>
	 <string id="bm_msl_sds_06_desc">There it is, your unquenchable need to stuff your face and fill your belly with the ravaging furor of someone in a constant state of starvation. And when you stop, it&apos;s like a gaping hole opens up in the pit of your stomache, craving to be satiated.</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_carbon">Carbon Fiber</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_waterblue">Blue Water</string>
	 <string id="bm_mtl_whiterock">White Rock</string>
	 <string id="bm_paycheck_dallas_desc">Paycheck Dallas finally made the decision to stop using black plastic bags for concealment. He gathered the nerve to order a real Dallas-mask to honor his idol, but that online printing service didn&apos;t exactly deliver the real deal... Even so, with the mask, he&apos;s trying to step up his game and convinced the Paycheck gang to raid a china shop. The CCTV footage shows that Paycheck Dallas accidentally broke the biggest vase while storming in. That made him apologize to the owner, grab all small changes from register and run for the door.  Probably blushing like a tomato behind that smiling neon mask.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sfm_03_desc">The day Chad got the Barrori Flex sunglasses, everything changed.They gave him a brand new perspective on what&apos;s important in life. Looking cool and blase became his purpose, his reason to live. With his Italian sports coat, beige linen pants and loafers he caught jealous looks and turned necks wherever he went. But it couldn&apos;t last and when Chad&apos;s beauty faded so did his will to live. He made a good-looking corpse, best clothes on, when he swallowed a whole can of diet pills.</string>
	 <string id="bm_sha_03_desc">Be an aggressive, merciless, swarming menace. As you roll into town, death follows in the form of fire.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_cartelboss_desc">Death, symbolised in the white threads of this getup, is where all Cartel bosses end up, when their sins catch up to them.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_desperado">The Avenging Gunman</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_gentleman">The Long Gentleman</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_murky_suit">Murkywater Uniform</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_none">Default Outfit</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_peacoat_desc">The suit a heister wears occasionally needs to provide a modicum of formal respect, while still being casual and workmanlike. This combination of denim lower and more strict upper takes the best of both worlds and combines them. </string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_punk_desc">The punk rock jacket and pants are a suit of armor, worn with pride in defiance of the established norms of &quot;polite&quot; society. A true punk jacket has every stud added laboriously by hand, and every painted decoration, also added by hand, has a deeper meaning for the individual wearer. Unless it&apos;s just a big fuck-you to the world at large, of course.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_slaughterhouse">Legacy Tactical</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gentleman_default_desc">Discreet and dark, for the heister that wants to pass by in the night...</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_casual">Sandstorm</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_default">Highwayman</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_gunslinger_default_desc">Show the fat coachman you mean business when you rob the stagecoach.</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_var_t800_cowboy">Infamy Dust</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_winter_suit">Winter Camo Parka</string>
	 <string id="bm_suit_winter_suit_desc">This is a full suit sporting military winter camouflage. The idea is to reduce visibility in snow.</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_catface">Ambush</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_clutter">Scribbles</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_dragon_split">Dragon Split</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_emblem1">Two Lions</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_facecollage">Clown World</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_facename">Your Name Here</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_frankenstein">Patch Work</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_hearts">Candy Hearts</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_heraldry_ord_saltire">Saltire</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_horizon_circle">Moon and Water</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_hostage">The Hostage</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_imperial">Imperial</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_luchador">Mexican Wrestler</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_mantis">Praying Mantis</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ouroboros">The Ouroboros</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_hawkins">Hawkins</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_predator_poncho">Puncho</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_racestripes">Race Stripes</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ransom_1mdollars">1m dOlLaR$</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ransom_cashking">CA$h Is KiNg</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_ransom_diepig">die PIG</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_scars">Claw Attack</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_3d">Stereoscopic</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_shades_80s">Disco</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_sight">Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_splat">The Mist</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_target">The Orb</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_toto">Guardian</string>
	 <string id="bm_txt_vertical">Vertical Split</string>
	 <string id="bm_wolf_rising">Risen Wolf Mask</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_a_bow_explosion">Explosive Arrows</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45iron_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45rds_v2_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45steel">45 Degree Ironsights</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_45steel_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_fps_upg_o_sig_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_ace">Ace of Spades</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_hur">Throwing Axe</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_jav">Javelin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_target">Throwing Knife</string>
	 <string id="bm_wpn_prj_target_desc">A solid backup plan and a reliable tactic for a precise and silent kill. The Throwing Knife has been present in martial history for as long as people grew tired of throwing objects in a general direction and wanted a reliable weapon instead.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ak_s_psl">Wooden Sniper Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_arbiter_b_comp">Bombardier Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ass_s552_s_standard_green">Enhanced Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_b_longsupp">Futomaki Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_s_standard">No Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_baka_s_unfolded">Unfolded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_basset_m_extended">Big Brother Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beer_b_robo">Weller Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beer_g_lux">Cartel Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beer_g_robo">Weller Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beer_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beer_s_std">Federales Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ben_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ben_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ben_fg_standard">Tactical Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beretta_co_co2">The Competitor Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_beretta_g_ergo">Ergo Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_boot_body_exotic">Treated Body</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_boot_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_boot_s_long">Long Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_breech_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_breech_g_custom">Engraved Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_china_stock_short">Riot Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ching_s_pouch">Magpouch Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_coach_b_short">Sawed-Off Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_cobray_body_upper_jacket">80&apos;s Calling</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_corgi_body_strap">Dunes Tactical Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_czech_b_long">Sicario Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_czech_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_desertfox_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_g_wood">Wooden Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_m_explosive">Explosive Arrow</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_elastic_m_poison">Poison Arrow</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_famas_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_famas_b_sniper">Sniper Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_famas_b_suppressed">Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_fla_mk2_mag_welldone">Well Done</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g18c_co_comp_2">Velocity Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g26_body_salient">Striking Body kit</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g26_b_custom">Striking Slide</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g26_m_custom">Striking Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_fg_c">Compact Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_fg_ksk">Polizei Special Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_m_quick">Speed Pull Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_g36_s_sl8">Sniper Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_gre_m79_s_leather">Sawed-off Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_holt_g_bling">Bling Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_holt_g_ergo">Ergonomic Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_holt_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_huntsman_b_short">Road Warrior Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ksg_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_ksg_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_l85a2_m_emag">Expert Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_legacy_g_wood">Wooden Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_lemming_m_ext">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m14_body_ruger">B-Team Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1897_s_short">Artisan Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_b_long">Long barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m1928_s_discrete">Discreet Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m32_no_stock">No Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_b_medium">Medium Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_b_sd">Stealth Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m4_uupg_m_std">Milspec Mag.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m60_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m79_barrel_short">Pirate Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m95_b_barrel_short">CQB Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_m95_b_barrel_suppressed">Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_model70_ns_suppressor">Beak Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_b_sniper">Silenced Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mosin_ns_bayonet">Nagant Bayonet</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_fg_m5k">Sehr Kurze Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_fg_mp5a5">Polizei Tactical Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_m_straight">Straight Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_s_adjust">Adjustable Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp5_s_ring">Bare Essentials Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp7_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_mp9_s_skel">Skeletal Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_olympic_fg_railed">Railed Handguard</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_packrat_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_g_beavertail">Platypus Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_usp_b_expert">Expert Slide</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_pis_usp_b_match">Match Slide</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r700_s_military">Military Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r700_s_tactical">Tactical Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_body_rack">Shell Rack</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_s_solid">Standard Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r870_s_solid_big">Government Issue Tactical Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r93_body_wood">Wooden Body</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_r93_b_suppressed">Compensated Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_rota_b_standard">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saiga_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saiga_fg_lowerrail">The Tactical Russian Rail</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_saw_body_speed">Fast Motor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sbl_b_short">Wind Whistler Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sbl_s_saddle">Club Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_b_suppressed">Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_g_wood">Wooden Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_scorpion_m_extended">Extended Magazine</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_shrew_g_bling">Blinged Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_siltstone_iron_sight">Iron Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_siltstone_s_polymer">Lightweight Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sr2_ns_silencer">Tishina Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sr2_s_unfolded">Unfolded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_stech_s_standard">Federales Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_b_short">Short Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_m_short">Short Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_s_folded">Folded Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_sterling_s_nostock">No Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_striker_b_long">Long Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_striker_b_suppressed">Suppressed Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_system_b_wtf">Merlin Nozzle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_system_m_low">Low Temperature Mixture</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_tti_ns_hex">Contractor Silencer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_tti_s_vltor">Contractor Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_fg_zenit">Aluminum Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_g_hgrip">AK Rubber Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_g_wgrip">AK Wood Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ak_m_quad">AK Quadstacked Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_fg_lvoa">OVAL Foregrip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_m4_lower_reciever_core">THRUST Lower Receiver</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ass_ns_surefire">Tactical Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_arblast_explosion">Explosive Bolt</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_arblast_poison">Poison Bolt</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_bow_poison">Poisoned Arrows</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_bow_poison_desc">Arrow with a poison tip that does damage over time and has a chance to interrupt enemies.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_custom">000 Buckshot</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_custom2_desc">Bigger pellets with more impact. This ammo type is harder to find.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_custom_desc">Bigger pellets with more impact.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_dragons_breath">Dragon&apos;s Breath Round</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_dragons_breath_desc">Fires pellets that go up in sparks and flames. Burns through shields and body armor.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_explosive">HE Round</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_explosive_desc">Fires one explosive charge that kills or stuns targets. This ammo type is harder to find.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_frankish_poison">Poison Bolt</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_grenade_launcher_incendiary">Incendiary Round</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_grenade_launcher_incendiary_desc">Fires a round that causes a fire at point of impact.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_piercing">Flechette</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_piercing_desc">Long range armor piercing.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_slug">AP Slug</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_a_slug2_desc">Fires a single lead slug that penetrates body armor, enemies, shields and walls. This ammo type is harder to find.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_bonus_team_exp_money_p3_desc">+3% Experience &amp; money reward for you and your crew.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fg_smr">Gazelle Rail</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_laser_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_peq15">Military Laser Module</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_peq15_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_smg_sho_peqbox">Tactical Laser Module</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_smg_sho_surefire">Assault Light</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_smg_sho_surefire_desc">Turn it on/off by pressing $BTN_GADGET;.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_ass_utg">LED Combo</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_fl_pis_laser">Pocket Laser</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_i_autofire">Auto Fire</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_i_singlefire">Single Fire</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_m_quad">CAR Quadstacked Mag</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_s_crane">Wide Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_s_mk46">War-Torn Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_m4_s_ubr">2 Piece Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_filter">Budget Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_pbs1">PBS Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_firepig">Fire Breather Nozzle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_large">The Bigger the Better Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_small">Low Profile Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_stubby">Stubby Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_ass_smg_tank">The Tank Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_large_kac">Champion&apos;s Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_meatgrinder">Facepunch Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_medium_gem">Roctec Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_pis_jungle">Jungle Ninja Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_pis_large">Monolith Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_shot_shark">Shark Teeth Nozzle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_shot_thick">The Silent Killer Suppressor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_sho_salvo_large">Shh!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_ns_typhoon">Hurricane Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_acog">Acough Optic Scope</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_aimpoint">Military Red Dot Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_cs">Combat Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_eotech">Holographic Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_eotech_xps">Compact Holosight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_fc1">Compact Profile Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_mbus_rear">Flip-up Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_rikt">Riktpunkt Holosight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_rmr">Pistol Red Dot Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_rms">SKOLD Reflex Micro Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_rx30">Solar Sight</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_o_specter">Milspec Scope</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_shot_ns_king">King&apos;s Crown Compensator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_upg_smg_olympic_fg_lr300">Aftermarket Shorty</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_usp_co_comp_1">Ventilated .45</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_usp_m_big">I want more Magazine!</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_uzi_b_suppressed">Silent Death</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_uzi_s_leather">Ergonomic Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_uzi_s_solid">Solid Stock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_wa2000_b_long">Langer Barrel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_wa2000_g_light">Leichter Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_wa2000_g_stealth">Subtiler Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wp_wa2000_g_walnut">Walnuss Grip</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_aa12_cs3">Powerhouse</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_aa12_wac">Cataphract</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_akmsu_lones">Razor Splitter</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_nin">Baldwin&apos;s Armament</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_amcar_same_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_arbiter_cs3">Last Man Standing</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_arbiter_cs4">Biohazard</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_asval_waves">Wave Snake</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_asval_wolf">Smygvarg</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_b682_burn">Lead Dead Plaid</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_baka_waves">Chikara</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_baka_wolf">Hati</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_beer_tam">IMMORTAL PYTHON WEAPON SKIN</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_benelli_burn">Braindead</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_benelli_cola">Vix CQC</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_boot_cat">A Man Called Hero</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_breech_css">On Point</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_china_lones">Blockbuster</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_china_mxs">Maya</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_chinchilla_dss">Clyde</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ching_dss">Desert Stallion</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ching_skf">Spector</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_green_deluxe">Kelly Green</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_color_orange_mellow">Just Peachy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_contraband_css">Battle Zone</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_contraband_mxs">Chupacabra</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_contraband_sfs">Mansion Mauler </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_deagle_same">Flaming Deagle</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_desertfox_sfs">Everglade </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_desertfox_sfs_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_desertfox_wac_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_elastic_ait">Snow Camo</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_elastic_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_erma_dss">Classic Finish</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_erma_wwt">Tarnschmeisser</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_forest">Coin Ops</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_golddigger">Yggdrasil</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_famas_skf">Oathbreaker</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_bloodbath">Tiger Hazard</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_dallas">Chromed Combustion </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_fire">Dragon Lord</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_flamethrower_mk2_goldstripes">St. Basil</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_frankish_cs3">Modernized</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_g36_bloodbath">Perimeter Secure</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_g36_bloodsplat">The Torch</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_g36_goldstripes">Ice Leopard </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_gre_m79_burn">Poser Bash</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_gre_m79_dss">Oxidator</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_bloodbath">Frenzy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_burn">Anarcho</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_cs3">Dynamite</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_lones_desc">MODIFICATIONS INCLUDED</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_same">DIAMOND SPLINTER</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_woodland">Pixel </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_judge_wooh">Check Mate</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_cat">Cloaker Gold</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_ksg_ginger">Evergreen</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_legacy_nin">Fade Out</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_legacy_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_lemming_ait">Possessed</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_lemming_mxs">Tenochtitlan</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_lemming_skf">Respect</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m16_cs4">Born to Steal</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_buck">Rake</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_dss">Pallido Madre</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m1928_ginger">Xmas Noir</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m37_css">Heat Wave</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_bombmatta">Hype Train</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_css">The Tempest</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_dallas">Piercing Patriot </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_golddigger">Beta-2</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_m95_luxury">Matrjoschka</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mg42_wwt">The Devil&apos;s Piano</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_model70_lones">Star Spawn</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_model70_same">Airship</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_mp7_cat">LAZARUS ARMS</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_cs3">NITRO</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_goldstripes">Stripe On</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_payday">Safe Crasher</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_skullimov">Fade Zebra</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_new_m4_smosh">Royale Blue</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_par_css">Bulldozer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r870_sfs">Cuban </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_bloodsplat">Death From Above</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_css">Opposition</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_dallas">Reptilian Sting </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_forest">Fire Pixel</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_r93_wooh">Grenade Repellant</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rota_ait">Damascus</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rota_nin">Wildfire</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpg7_bloodbath">Fair Warning</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpg7_boom">Green Grin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_rpg7_cs4">Hope of Ashes</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_s552_wolf">Howl</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_saw_nin">The Lucky Gambler</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_scar_mxs">Caracara</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_scorpion_smosh">Ancient </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_cat">Loco</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_cat_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_cs4">Apocalypse</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_lones">Demon</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_serbu_woodland">Cosmonaut</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_shuno_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_shuno_tam_desc">This weapon skin is an Achievement Reward, it cannot be traded or sold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_siltstone_mxs_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_slap_ait">Battery</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_sterling_wwt">The Drop Buddy</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_striker_cs4">The Spear of War</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_striker_mxs">Chihuahua</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_striker_mxs_desc"> </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_striker_wolf">Denmother</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_system_ait">Firefighter</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_system_tam">Immortal Python Weapon Skin</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tam_desc">This weapon skin is an Achievement Reward, it cannot be traded or sold.</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tecci_ait">Underground Neon</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_tecci_grunt">Mars Ultor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_usp_cs4">Genesis</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_usp_same">Splitter</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_usp_waves">Lip Jibber</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_uzi_burn">Spewer</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_uzi_cola">Velox</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_uzi_sfs">Miami Spice </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_wa2000_buck">Muffler</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_wa2000_cs4">M9 Shepard</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_wa2000_ginger">Santa&apos;s Helper</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_wa2000_grunt">Boreas</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_winchester1874_buck">The Fork</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_winchester1874_dss">Presidential Oil</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_winchester1874_grunt">Royal Commander</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_winchester1874_nin">Survivor</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_1911_smosh">Tigershark</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_akmsu_sfs">Vice &amp; Dice </string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_beer_tam">IMMORTAL PYTHON WEAPON SKIN</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_coal_cat">Deadlock</string>
	 <string id="bm_wskn_x_czech_tam">IMMORTAL PYTHON WEAPON SKIN</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_akm">AK.762 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_akm_gold">Golden AK.762 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_arbiter">Arbiter Grenade Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_asval">Valkyria Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_b682">Joceline O/U 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_b92fs">Bernetti 9 Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_beer">Bernetti Auto Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_benelli">M1014 Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_boot">Breaker 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_breech">Parabellum Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_china">China Puff 40mm Grenade Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_chinchilla">Castigo .44 Revolver</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_coal">Tatonka Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_cobray">Jacket&apos;s Piece</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_czech">Czech 92 Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_desertfox">Desertfox Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ecp">Airbow</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_elastic">DECA Technologies Compound Bow</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_famas">Clarion Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_flamethrower_mk2">Flamethrower Mk.1</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_galil">Gecko 7.62 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_glock_18c">STRYK 18c Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_gre_m79">GL40 Grenade Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_hajk">CR 805B Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_hk21">Brenner-21 Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_holt">HOLT 9mm Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_hs2000">LEO Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_hunter">Pistol Crossbow</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_komodo">Tempest-21 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ksg">Raven Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_legacy">M13 9mm Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_lemming">5/7 AP Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_long">English Longbow</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m134">Vulcan Minigun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m14">M308 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m16">AMR-16 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m1897">Reinfeld 88 Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m1928">Chicago Typewriter Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m32">Piglet Grenade Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m37">GSPS 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m45">Swedish K Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_m95">Thanatos .50 cal Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mac10">Mark 10 Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mg42">Buzzsaw 42 Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_model3">Frenchman Model 87 Revolver</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_model70">Platypus 70 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mosin">Nagant Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mp5">Compact-5 Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_mp7">SpecOps Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_olympic">Para Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_p226">Signature .40 Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_packrat">Contractor Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_peacemaker">Peacemaker .45 Revolver</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_pl14">White Streak Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_plainsrider">Plainsrider Bow</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_polymer">Kross Vertex Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_r700">R700 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_raging_bull">Bronco .44 Revolver</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_ray_desc">AMMO PICKUPS ARE DISABLED FOR THIS WEAPON.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_rota">Goliath 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_rpg7">HRL-7 Rocket Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_rpg7_desc">AMMO PICKUPS ARE DISABLED FOR THIS WEAPON.</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_rpk">RPK Light Machine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_s552">Commando 553 Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_sbl">Bernetti Rangehitter Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_scar">Eagle Heavy Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_schakal">Jackal Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_scorpion">Cobra Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_serbu">Locomotive 12G Shotgun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_shepheard">Signature Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_shrew">Crosskill Guard Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_siltstone">Grom Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_slap">Compact 40mm Grenade Launcher</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_sparrow">Baby Deagle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_sterling">Patchett L2A1 Submachine Gun</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_sub2000">Cavity 9mm</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_system">MA-17 Flamethrower</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_tecci">Bootleg Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_tti">Contractor .308 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_usp">Interceptor 45 Pistol</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_wa2000">Lebensauger .308 Sniper Rifle</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_1911">Akimbo Crosskill Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_b92fs">Akimbo Bernetti 9 Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_baka">Akimbo Micro Uzi Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_basset">Brothers Grimm 12G Shotguns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_beer">Akimbo Bernetti Auto Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_breech">Akimbo Parabellum Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_c96">Akimbo Broomstick Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_coal">Akimbo Tatonka Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_g17">Akimbo Chimano 88 Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_g18c">Akimbo STRYK 18c Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_hajk">Akimbo CR 805B Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_holt">Akimbo HOLT 9mm Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_judge">Akimbo Judge Shotguns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_m1928">Akimbo Chicago Typewriter SMGs</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_model3">Akimbo Frenchman Model 87 Revolvers</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_mp9">Akimbo CMP Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_olympic">Akimbo Para Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_p90">Akimbo Kobus 90 Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_pl14">Akimbo White Streak Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_ppk">Akimbo Gruber Kurz Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_rage">Akimbo Bronco .44 Revolvers</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_schakal">Akimbo Jackal Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_shepheard">Akimbo Signature Submachine Guns</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_sparrow">Akimbo Baby Deagle Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_stech">Akimbo Igor Automatik Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_w_x_usp">Akimbo Interceptor 45 Pistols</string>
	 <string id="bm_zeal_mask_desc">He did not exist, not officially. Not since he came aboard Zeal, the top-secret strike force. He was always the last resort, deployed when extreme violence was needed. He never held back. For every operation, he lost a bit of his humanity. For every operation, he gained an edge as an instrument of death. He did not separate right from wrong, not anymore. Only obeyed the orders from above. Just one shadow in the dark legion of secret super soldiers. One day, he woke up and could only think of killing others. He had finally found his true purpose.</string>
	 <string id="female_1_desc">Nationality: Irish$NL;Age: 27$NL;$NL;Clover grew up in a rough house in a rough part of town. Her ancestors were fighters in every generation, and she is fiercely dedicated to her Irish heritage. She wears the clovers for luck, as well as a way to say &quot;I&apos;m Irish, and I&apos;m proud&quot;.</string>
	 <string id="menu_l_global_value_pdcon_2016">This is a PAYDAYCON 2016 secret mask item!</string>
	 <string id="menu_l_global_value_rota"> </string>
	 <string id="menu_l_global_value_solus_clan">This is a The Solus Project community item!</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_cs3_01">Community 3</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_event_bah">Goat</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_event_dinner">Slaughter</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_event_flake">Christmas</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_lones_01">Hoxton</string>
	 <string id="menu_steam_market_content_nin_01">Community 9</string>
	 <string id="old_hoxton_desc_codex">Hoxton is one of the original PAYDAY crew members. After a successful stint of major heists up until 2012, Hoxton was captured by the FBI and sent to prison. In 2014, the Payday Gang helped him escape. Ever since he got out, he has been convinced someone set him up.</string>
	 <string id="russian_desc">Nationality: American$NL;Age: 44$NL;$NL;Experienced, cunning, methodical. At the age of 30 he tried to play two of Chicago&apos;s mob families against each other. It went south and several mob bosses ordered Dallas&apos; head on a plate, but somehow he managed to go underground and survive. After things calmed down he worked his way back up the criminal ladder.$NL;$NL;Now he&apos;s the face that everyone fears.</string>
	 <string id="spanish_desc">Nationality: American$NL;Age: 37$NL;$NL;As a teenager, Chains always got into trouble. After years of jumping between foster homes and juvenile institutions, he ended up in the military. There he became an excellent soldier but he always hated being told what to do.$NL;$NL;Chains left the military and became a soldier of fortune, offering his military expertise to the highest bidder.</string>
</resources>