<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_02_01">Oooh, it&apos;s been a long time since Vlad did a good old-fashioned revenge taking. That piece of shit Buluc is going to wish he was born in Switzerland!$NL;</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_01_01">That card should get you entry to one of the train railcars.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_16_02">One of these is the truck carrying the voting machines to Washington. When you think you know which one it is, get the tracker on it and we can move on.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_02">Find some, and pour it in.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_09_03">That&apos;s the alarm. MPD response channels just went crazy. OK, no matter. Keep hacking those machines.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_13_02">Find the goods. I&apos;m sure you&apos;ll know it when you see it!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_02_any_03">OK you&apos;re in, good. Now you need at least four paintings, the good ones have red stickers - those are the ones our art lover intends to buy.</string>
	 <string id="pln_at1_brf_03_01">We&apos;re using a magnetic crane to drop a little present in the path of the Gensec convoy - a steel container of professional badasses. Hit the trucks, and get the loot to the getaway. These docks have a rich history of heistery, gentlemen - do it proud.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_24_03">There&apos;s a card reader by the security bars. Open it up.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_06">...I&apos;m sure. I&apos;m pretty sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_12_02">Alright. I need you to do one more errand before you bug out. Get to the security room and grab the footage from the cameras. Just in case they got anything incriminating.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_07_01">From what we know, Buluc keeps to himself a lot, when not holding court, so you&apos;ll probably find him in his office. See if you can find it.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_06_03">Thanks! My wrists hurt like hell!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_04_03">Pilot dropped the supplies. Get them into the house.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_14_01">Hey! I&apos;m not leaving without MY car!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_22_01">Put in the flash drive and get started.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_12_any_01">Look at all these nice things. Must have done a lot of public service in his career.</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_15_02">You know the Romanovs, eh?</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_16_02">Open those Murkywater containers. If anything has illegal loot, it will be them.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_40_01">Okay, our friend will know the way out, right? You just have to watch out for the guards.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_07_any_02">Get everyone into the train.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_21_any_01">Don&apos;t forget about those safe deposit boxes folks, can be good stuff in there.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_02_01">You can expect the security to be very tight, cameras and everything.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_end_01_02">That&apos;s how the pros do it! Chalk it up. Payday Gang one, Armadillo corp zero.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_22_02">Great. Now find something else to steal. We need to make it look like a simple robbery.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_04_02">That&apos;s the stuff. Keep going!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_06">That should get it on.</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_15_01">Ah, There are my precious things! Hurry, Hurry, take them!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_01_01">You see that fence? Cut it open and get inside.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_15_01">They&apos;re sending reinforcements.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_03_01">Keep sharp, gentleman. The warehouse will be tougher, but the rewards worth it.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_57_04">Use your guns! Put him in the ocean to drown!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_03_02">This is the warehouse. You can bet the better loot is right here.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_01_03">Great, we got our quarry. Make sure the chop stays secure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_03">Shush! What&apos;s that sound... Hmm, seems, nah seems OK.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_08_02">Another guard up ahead. Stay in the shadows.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_27_01">Damn, there&apos;s the alarm. They&apos;re on to us. Get the saw ready.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_28_01">Nicely done, friends! A job well done. We probably even emptied the Mayor&apos;s personal bank account this time!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_09_01">I&apos;ll count down the time.</string>
	 <string id="elp_framing_brf_speak_03b">Find a way to sneak into his apartment, steal the gold and plant incriminating evidence against him. Then leave undetected.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_02">...I... think.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_03_03">Great, two keycards. That&apos;s what we need. Get to work and open that vault.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_19_any_01">Good, OK, you can open the vault now. I have turned on the vault&apos;s camera feed as well.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_11_03">There&apos;s only one place I can sell that. Marrakech.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_24_01">It seems the armory has a different access level. You&apos;ll need to recode the key tag again.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_04_02">They probably keep the evidence files in the chief&apos;s computer. Try the upper floor.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_intro_a_04">This is gonna be easy as long as you steer clear of the security systems and guards. Well maybe not so easy. Take the paintings with red sold stickers and clear out. We need four at least.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_34_02">Easy enough. I got the next one too.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_03_01">Look out the window - Taxman is the guy in the white shirt.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c1_01">Caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_cash_brf_speak_04">A little cash goes a long way. The local Harvest &amp; Trustee branch bank needs to be lightened of its load.  Let&apos;s do this bank hit, get their vault open, and fill our pockets a little. </string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_01_01">There it is. Do your thing, guys, but Gage prefers you do it quietly. Front gate is dead ahead, but maybe you can find alternative routes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_13_02">Two card reader with a 10 second time lock? You can bet they&apos;re holding some serious hardware in that vault.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_15_01">Well, that&apos;s quite a mess all right. Now get these bodies out of sight.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_04_01">Quick! Answer his pager and make some crap up.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_end_01_02">That&apos;s how the pro&apos;s do it! Awesome work gentlemen!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_10_02">Dallas! There&apos;s a security guard outside and he&apos;s gonna see the broken camera. Take him out before he calls it in!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_01">Strike that...</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_intro_a_01">Pier 39. Tag the truck carrying the voting machines to Washington, and get back here. Let me stress, we&apos;re only here for the truck.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_01_01">Ok, keep our little V.I.P. dwankie safe and out of trouble.</string>
	 <string id="dr1_a01a_any_17">No-no-no-no-no!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_11_any_03">Get the cooking going - we can&apos;t stay here - at all in fact!</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_04_02">Hey, Hey, HEY. Don&apos;t you wave this off. Bain and Vlad have a long history together. I care about this shit.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_32_01">Mercy Hospital, please hold... Ok, now how can I help?</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_09_02">Those are all the bags we need but you guys know the drill, if you want more - stay and get more!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_23_any_01">There you go.  Now let&apos;s frame this guy, get up to the roof, and our guy will throw you the coke.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_01_any_01">Alright, get to the house and find the address, be careful.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_29_02">There you go! Hurry over to the vault.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_06_02">Alright then. Hmm... it says there&apos;s also physical evidence.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_gold_brf_speak_01">You can&apos;t go wrong with gold. The Harvest &amp; Trustee bank is trying to up its liquidity with a large deposit. It&apos;s something we should take advantage of, don&apos;t you think?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_09">...that&apos;s my very best guess.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_11_01">Looks like you need to find a specific office, then.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_35_01">They bought it. Keep working.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_14_02">That&apos;ll do for Gage, but you can stay for more.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_intro_01_02">Alright, that&apos;s the jewelery store. Get me the required amount and be ready for anything!</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_130_01">One moment please.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_27_03">So, that&apos;s it, yeah? Alright, friends. You need to cut the correct wires in the cable boxes to break the lock.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_50_02">Time to go!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_14_any_01">They are climbing into the building!</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_18_any_01">Damn it, they&apos;re burning it!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_13_01">Five.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap05_04">This is a nice house. Would look better with some of Vlad&apos;s furniture.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_12_any_02">The railway bridge! They are coming in from the railway bridge, keep them away.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_04">Nope, that&apos;s not it!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_21_02">Try and get by him unnoticed. Take your time.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_09_02">Get to the computer so we can code the tag for access.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_03_03">You&apos;re in the lair of the beast now, gang. Better loot, but bigger risk.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_g_02">It should be muriatic acid!</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_03_01">That&apos;s the stuff. Get it to the van.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_gold_brf_speak_03"> In unstable times like these, gold&apos;s all you can really depend on.  So who wants to go stabilize our economic future? The Harvest &amp; Trustee bank vault awaits.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_brf_01">Kerels are going to go bossies when they see what we are after, and will be coming after us in droves, so keep your eyes peeled and take them down fast. The longer you can keep them at bay, the more desperate they&apos;ll get and give us a bigger load of cash, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_end_03_01">Nice haul! This will bring in a nice chunk of change. Good job!</string>
	 <string id="bul_fex_tap01_01">Where the fuck is Raúl? You were supposed to find him! I have 50 guests coming tonight and you pull this shit you fucking whore! I will send you back to fucking San Dimas!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_23_01">Great, I&apos;m in. Keep watching those hostages.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_06_03">Never get tired of seeing gold bullion getting bagged.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_12_02">You got snipers around there!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_13_01">There&apos;s a lot of stuff in here! I guess you&apos;ll know what you&apos;re looking for when you see it.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_57c_01">There is old saying in Ukraine. Revenge is a dish best eaten by sharks.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_26_04">Go to the armory and find something that opens doors!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b1_02">It&apos;s muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="gsc_cs1_01_01">This is Hilary over at Gensec. Just checking in. Is Barney there?</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_01_02">OK, friends. Let&apos;s do this. Make your way into the bank.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_intro_a_03">That&apos;s the warehouse where the voting machines are kept. Time for a little political engineering.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_04_02">What&apos;s taking so long? Don&apos;t waste that thermite.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_02_01">Going to be a long day, isn&apos;t it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_14_03">Gage has what he wants. Great work. You can bug out now, or hang around a little.</string>
	 <string id="loc_mex_intro_01">Feels like we&apos;re going to get a kakspul of payback with this one, friends.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b2_04">...muriatic acid?</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_01_any_02">OK, here&apos;s the setup: we&apos;re looking for the paintings with red stickers on them. Security is going to be on the heavy side, cameras and guards. </string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_01_any_03">Quietly now. Sneak up and hit them hard. </string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_01_any_01">So the plan is, go in, get me the following objects. When you have them we&apos;ll connect them to our station on the roof.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_18_01">Use that paper shredder - it&apos;s the easy way.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_07_01">Great work. There&apos;s always a market for untraceable guns.</string>
	 <string id="elp_framing_brf_intro_01">I require your assistance in a matter...</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_58_03">Remember: blood poisoning and abnormal heart rate. Listen to Schneider.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_54_01">Good job, now let&apos;s get you into some scrubs.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_10">Shit!</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_01_03">You can try finding vault keycards, two of them, if you want to sneak this place. Maybe in the trunks. Or go loud - it&apos;s your choice.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_02_02">That&apos;s the ordnance, but it&apos;s not the turret. Get it out if you can, but keep looking.</string>
	 <string id="txm_man_01_01">It&apos;s nearby. Can I see the funds?</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_07_03">Illegal untraceable weapons. This is what Gage is all about.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_04_02">There we go - green lights. Let the time lock do it&apos;s thing. I&apos;d love to see the managers face when those doors swing wide open.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_11">OK, keep that smoke to a minimum... Keep going.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_13_01">Vault with simultaneous two card reader. Probably 10 second time lock. They must be hiding something tasty.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_02_any_02">Alright... OK, we need at least four paintings, remember, the ones with red stickers.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_05_03">Damnit, that&apos;s the alarm. Stay frosty and get ready!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_04_01">Used dinars. Hard to trace. Perfect.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_06_01">There we go. Hmm... it says there&apos;s physical evidence on our friend around here as well...</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_26_01">Ah, that&apos;s it friends. A nice little Payday, though I think we could have gotten more!</string>
	 <string id="bul_fex_tap04_01">Yes?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_07">Okay, what comes after that...</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_05_01">The other party is now a minute away.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_08_02">Why the hell did some Iraqi dictactor have seventeenth century Swedish masterpieces?</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_02_any_01">OK, the vault&apos;s got the gold. </string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_25_01">Ach, you&apos;re making me go bossies! We couldn&apos;t  afford to lose anyone! Abort and return to the safehouse.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_22_02">Armor of a Shogun. Nabunaga. Thought lost for centuries, but... here it is. Get the pieces bagged.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_15_03">You still got your old reflexes, old friend. Quickly, get these bodies out of sight.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_06_02">You know what to do. Signal the chopper, and we&apos;ll drop off more ingredients. Or bail. Your choice.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_end_a_02">It takes special skills to ninja through a secure warehouse in broad daylight. Great work. Now, let&apos;s see if it was worth it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_32_03">If you don&apos;get moving soon, I think Vlad&apos;s going to go bossies!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_15_04">Find a means to destroy the evidence!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_88_02">One more sample in the cooler before you can leave.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b2_01">...muriatic acid?</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_05_01">That&apos;s the alarm guys. Watch out for the cops!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_04_any_01">You are looking for muriatic acid, caustic soda and hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_07">Sorry, that wasn&apos;t right.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_12_01">He&apos;s at the trunk. He um....</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_16_03">These are the trucks. When you&apos;re done searching for clues, get the that GPS on the truck you think is carrying the voting machines to Washington.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_33_02">Are you giving him the earpiece? Good!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_12">...this isn&apos;t my specialty, really.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_29_03">Good job, Dallas. You still have it in you. Now, throw the loot in the van and let&apos;s leave.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_12_01">Look out for snipers!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_26_03">Remember what I said: don&apos;t kill the guard. Your nonsense won&apos;t trick the Control-Guy again and he&apos;ll sound the alarm.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_09_any_01">That&apos;s one of the external hard drives.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_03_01">Looks like we got everything, gang, Your pick-up is on its way.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_18_01">God dammit! Another guy, and this one&apos;s watching the server room. I guess you have to take him out as well.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_end_b_02">You cleaned the joint out. Now we&apos;ll have perfect coverage in the senator&apos;s apartment. I&apos;ll ensure we get the surveillance equipment in the paintings and set up the trade.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_33_02">Uhuh... uhuh... OK, sure. We&apos;ll have a look.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_57_01">Now get to the ICU. Find and listen to Dr. Schneider, the patient we&apos;re looking for should have blood poisoning and an abnormal heart rate.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap04_01"> </string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_09_01">That&apos;s all we need but feel free to stick around for more.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_03">Don&apos;t let the coppers take back the hostage.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_26_02">Now go sack that armory, friends!</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_01_any_02">OK, that&apos;s the clubhouse. Bikers&apos; got the address we need. Sneak in.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_07_02">See if you can find Buluc&apos;s office. He apparently spends a lot of time in there, so it&apos;s a solid bet.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed3_20_01">Those cameras won&apos;t be a problem anymore!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_04_any_02">We need chemicals to cook. Muriatic acid, caustic soda and hydrogen chloride. Easy.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_33_05">Yeah, the uh... monitor here just broke. Made a lot of noise. Scared an old lady but the janitor took care of her.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_05_02">Alright I&apos;m in! *whistles, impressed* These guys aren&apos;t messing around. Lots of additional firewalls.</string>
	 <string id="nmh_intro_08_01">We&apos;re doin&apos; this shit for a fucking book?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_99_01">Guys!... Guys! You still there?! Get... -out!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_18_any_01">It feels bad to leave the gold, but we will get paid. Maybe we can return.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_07_03">Get past the gates, but don&apos;t get spotted.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_08">Uh... mhm...</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_03_any_01">Damn it! That&apos;s the alarm!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_71_02">The concentration in that sample wasn&apos;t even close. You need to go again.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_09">Nice... Seems to be OK.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_23_02">Ach, that&apos;s what you get from dossing about, friends! They just took the hostage and we gotta go back empty-handed!</string>
	 <string id="elp_bigoil_brf_speak_02">An inventor named Rossy - residing somewhere in DC - may have found a cheap way to produce energy from water.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_121_01">You&apos;re through to Mortimer at Roberts Bank. I&apos;d be happy to assist.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_39_01">Keep the elevator under watch, guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_10_any_03">Halfway there with the painting collection. Now just get the rest and we&apos;re home free.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_32_02">Hi! Yes, what can I do for you?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_02">OK - looks stable, for now. Add more stuff...</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_01_03">Nice and easy. Time for a casual stroll into the bank, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_13_any_01">Public office. Wow, we are in the wrong line of work gentlemen.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_14_any_01">Good, with that guy out of the picture, no more cameras.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_24_01">You gotta get the security bars open. Crack open the card reader near it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_15">...these internet descriptions are iffy at best.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_19_01">Guys, get into those cars and find the one with the turret.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_01_02">There it is, right ahead. Do your thing, guys, but do it quietly. It goes loud, and I&apos;ll have to pull you out fast.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_14_02">Damn! Someone must have found the body! Take him out before he sounds the alarm!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_07">Go for it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_11_02">Good job. Answer the pager and then hide the body in the dumpster.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_19_01">Just got a message from The Elephant. Your bonus for keeping things clandestine has been dropped off. It&apos;s near the escape van.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_60_01">One of you guys answer the phone and patch me through.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_18_02">Why isn&apos;t that chopper on any flight plans?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_21_02">Hook me into the reception computer so that I can see where the doctors are keeping our target.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_03_01">Your instincts are correct my friend. You&apos;ll have to take him out.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_05_any_01">Great, you found the laptop.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_39_01b">I know that crest! it belonged to the Romanov dynasty, for sure!</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_46_01">Right. He got called in to a meeting with a big account. He&apos;s doing a great job.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_11_any_01">Damn it! They&apos;ve spotted you!</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_05_02">Great. There&apos;s no shortage of buyers for these military rounds.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_17_02">Time to use the keycard you picked up. Have your gun ready and take out anyone on the other side of that door.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_02_01">Now keep moving. And as much as you hate this, this is still a real thing. You get discovered you&apos;ll trigger the alarm.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bigoil_stage1_intro_a_01">I don&apos;t know how the bikers know we&apos;re coming but they do. Maybe all that meth they&apos;re doing gives them a sixth sense...</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_08_01a">I have been in the bank one time, a few years ago. The bank manager is an idiot. He keeps his access key in a personal safe, but I don&apos;t actually remember where.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_25">...I&apos;m 72% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_14_any_01">Be careful! They have snipers incoming!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_09_03">I can&apos;t wait to see what these shady assholes were hiding on that server.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_01_any_01">OK guys, get inside and locate the art. We want the paintings with the red stickers on. Look out for guards and cameras.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_03">Okay, what&apos;s next...</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_01_01">Your first job is getting into the depot. Scout the area, check for cameras and guards. Keep it quiet.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_intro_01_01">Alright, get ready! Get me the required amount of bags and I&apos;ll meet you at the safe house.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_i_04">We need hydrogen chloride!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_02_any_01">We need his phone, his tablet, his laptop and two external hard drives.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_34_02">They tied him down. We&apos;ll need to cut him loose.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_05">The domkops are trying to get off cheapsies with that offer, yeah? We can get more if we just don&apos;t give up.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_23_03">You let them take the hostage, you chops! It&apos;s over, we gotta get you out of there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_108_01">It&apos;s on fire! The whole damn roof!</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_cash_brf_speak_03">Today&apos;s our lucky day - cash delivery from the airport to this bank, all sorts of denominations... So I propose we do a little money exchange of our own. </string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_02_any_03">Don&apos;t let them destroy any intel. Get it all!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_00_03">You done? Good. Put on your mask now.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_04_02">Look for something to crack those crates open. </string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_31_03">Take a look around and see if you can find a clue on how to crack that code. Check the workstations.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_intro_04_01">Why do you keep going bossies over Bain? Look, we&apos;ve got it under control, yeah?$NL;</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_09_02">Anything could be on that server. Maybe the President&apos;s email address.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_28_03">A bit hairy in the end but you got there. I don&apos;t think we could have gotten another penny from those chops. Nice work!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_g_06">My bad. It&apos;s muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_at1_cbf_01_02">Gensec are a big security company on the East Coast. Got a great reputation with the banks and politicians, but today we&apos;re going to see what we can do about that. Got a tip-off about a convoy coming into the city. We&apos;re going after it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_03_any_01">OK, OK, we gotta change this up!</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_intro_02">You&apos;re almost there, everyone get your guns ready.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_13_any_02">They are coming in from the forest next to the road! Keep them away!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_20_04">The cell block is nearby. That&apos;s where they&apos;ll be keeping our friend.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_01_01">OK, make your way inside. Keep it quiet. </string>
	 <string id="pln_misc_sj_dgh_04_02">Good job. Leave them there for now while we take care of the bank. </string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_03_any_01">They&apos;re pretty antsy - just get the paintings on the table and keep both eyes open for anything weird.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_22_02">See if you can find Buluc&apos;s secret meeting room. The solution for getting into his office should be there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_05_01">Great! That&apos;s one of our voting machines! Hack it when there&apos;s no one nearby. If they see what you&apos;re up to, things will get loud.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_02_01">Look around. Search the Murkywater containers. Just grab any valuables you can.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_02_02">This will be a tough one but you can handle it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_33_01">Uhm... didn&apos;t we solve this already? </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_24">...I&apos;m 79% sure.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_29_04">You know what to do with that!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_25_any_01">That&apos;s it, fine work. The escape is ready for you. Unless you want to stick around and clean out the vault. Either way the vehicle&apos;s waiting.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_15_any_03">Cameras will set of the mines, guys! Stay away!</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_24_01">That codex! Those symbols... that&apos;s how we get the Mayan door to open, yeah? Look around for more clues!</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_02_02">You going to keep this up all day?</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_cbf_01_01">Got a line on a recent drop of hard currency. It&apos;s tucked away in the vault of a branch of Roberts bank. It&apos;s a quiet area. Nothing happens here, so they won&apos;t be expecting a hit. Let&apos;s punish that complacency. </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_20">...I&apos;m 93% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_06_01">The van had to leave. He&apos;ll be back soon at another location.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_05">...unless I&apos;ve missed something...</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_05_any_01">Alright, that&apos;s enough to go now if you want, but if we want more - get me access to the surveillance room so I can see what&apos;s on their network.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_10_any_01">Man... This place... Find that gold and we can buy one of our own.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_02">Look like the chops are ready to talk, but we can squeeze them for more cash if you just keep going.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_80_any_01">OK people, there&apos;s the bank, I don&apos;t know what&apos;s in there but it&apos;s gonna be good...</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh21_brf_01_01">Okay, Dallas. It&apos;s been two years since we worked together, and I need to see that you still got what it takes. We&apos;ll start with something simple, all right? An acquaintance of mine recently got robbed on a cocaine deal by some low-life mobster. I need to you to break into his night club and see if you can find the stolen cocaine and get it back. Easy, right?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_86_01">I had a contact hide a cooler in the elevator for us. Drop the vials in there!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_07_03">Okay, let&apos;s move it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_esc_pep">Keep it together! You can&apos;t fall apart now!</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_03_02">The thermite I gave you will let you get past the mansion walls, and inside.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_01_02">First, you need to break into the depot. Try and keep it quiet. If you can&apos;t keep it quiet, make it fast.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_03_03">Once you have something to break them open, get searching the crates.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_01_02">There&apos;s goes the alarm. And our camera feeds with it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_02_02">Great. Now search the docks. You&apos;re looking for something that tells you which truck has the voting machines and is headed for Washington. Search containers, computers - anything. When you&apos;ve figured it out, tag the right truck.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_04">You have to keep them away from the hostage.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_04_02">That&apos;s used bank notes from our &apos;allies&apos; overseas. </string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_08">They must think we&apos;re a bunch of chops with an offer like that. I think we should make them give us more.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_22_01">Guys, you need to get those pieces to the pick-up.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_10_02">They&apos;re sending in Minigun Dozers too!</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_gold_brf_speak_02">The Harvest &amp; Trustee bank just got a big gold shipment from South Africa. I think we should make it go away. I can&apos;t see they&apos;ll miss them much.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_end_a_01">That was a superb display of stealth. You guys are made of shadows. The machines are hacked, the votes are flooding in and it is a landslide for The Elephant&apos;s man. God bless democracy!</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_06">An offer is on the table, but it&apos;s hardly even enough to bribe our dear Mayor! Press them for more, friends.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_05_01">There it goes. The vault is open. It&apos;s all yours, gang. </string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_84_any_01">OK, great. Now get that thing to the vault door.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_intro_01_01">OK, pull over here, and get your masks on.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_29_01">Good, now get to the vault!</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_brf_01_01">Keep the civs down, look out for cameras. Scout the place and find the best way to do it without raising the alarm.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_11">...this is not my forte.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_06_02">Piles of green! Thats why we&apos;re in this business, gang. </string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_05_any_01">Yep, that&apos;s the inventors address. Beautiful.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d1_02">It&apos;s hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_09_02">There you go. The vault with Vlad&apos;s merchandise is behind a security gate.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_07_02">That&apos;s... two. Two guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d1_03">Chloride. Hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_26_any_02">Ah,what!? Guys, you have to be careful with that stuff, I told you!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_20_03">That&apos;s bag one. Keep bagging, gang.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_03_03">That&apos;s it. Now wait for the pilot to signal in.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_random_stage1_intro_a_01">OK, this is the bank. I advise casing the place, then grab the thermal drill from the back parking lot somewhere. Hit the vault however you want. There&apos;s usually a security room so be cautious. </string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_05_02">Ach, and they&apos;re sending in Cuff Cloakers now.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_23_01">If it were me, I might hide something important in a lamp or something.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_01_02">An old fashioned break in. Stay out of sight.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_81_any_01">Nice, seems the surprise loot was cash. Bag it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_11_03">Well, logic would suggest he keeps the thing in his office, for sure.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_26_03">OK, that&apos;s done. We got a pretty good payment this time but we could probably have held out longer.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_30_02">You got in and out without making a sound. Good job, Dallas. I mean it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_28_any_01">Alright, vault is popped, but watch out for those lasers, they connect directly to the alarm</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_09_any_02">Now we wait. Remember we get a bag of cash for every painting we throw into the chopper. All we need to do is be patient and lucky. </string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_05">The hostage is in danger.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_08_01">Damn, that&apos;s an original Gustoff!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_20_02">Now you just gotta make sure no one gets away and alerts the guards in the ICU.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_89_any_01">Good thinking, boards will slow them down.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_11_03">There&apos;s a few body bags stashed nearby.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_01_01">Right, you chops. Let&apos;s get you ambling into the bank.</string>
	 <string id="elp_framing_brf_outro_01">Best of luck, gentlemen.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_78_02">Protect the hacking device!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_01_02">There should be a fence nearby. Cut it open and get inside.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_18_any_02">I think those tunnels will get you into the warehouse folks.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_24_02">Don&apos;t let any civilians get near the alarms!</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_cbf_01_03">A jewelry store downtown has just stocked up with jewelery. That jewelery could be ours. You up for it?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_04">...caustic soda?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_10">Uh, I hope I got this right...</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_random_brf_speak_04">OK people, my guy says this is a good time to hit the bank. Turns out the Harvest &amp; Trustee bank manager should have kept his mouth shut. Anything could be in here.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_16_any_01">We are going to need ingredients, so scout the place and see what you can find.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_08_03">Another guard. Stay hidden.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_03_01">These fuckers chained me up! Get this shit off me!</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_intro_01_01">Find the railcar with the turret. You might be able to find an access card somewhere to speed things up.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_05_02">Great. Bag that body and get it out of sight before someone sees it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_18_any_01">Those tunnels will lead you into the warehouse.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_57_01">Almost there, gang. Any second now.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_17_01">Flush it down the toilet! It will mix with the rest of the kak.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_04_01">Come on friends, you have the thermite. Get inside.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_18_01">Uh, guys...what&apos;s that noise?</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_05_01">Ach, the door is locked. Buluc likes to keep his wine safe. You&apos;ll need to find the code to unlock it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_10_01">The incoming group has Minigun Dozers!</string>
	 <string id="loc_mex_intro_04">If you chops find a guitar case full of guns... just let it be, yeah?  </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_h_04">We need caustic soda!</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_04_01">Great, keep &apos;em coming!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_15_01">Three.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_16_any_01">Alright now, I have access, hold on a sec...</string>
	 <string id="gsc_cs1_03_01">Well, look... I&apos;m going to send some guys over there to check on things.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_brf_01">Our client needs a blood sample from a patient being kept in the isolation ward of Mercy Hostpital. You gotta go in there, take out the surveillance, subdue the civilians and get me into the patient database so I can ID the guy. With the low security in this place, it should be a nice, clean job. I&apos;ll get you out via the roof when you&apos;re done. This job is a little shady, brokered through a third party- got some serious shadow-company military industrial vibes, but worth the risk. The payday is something we&apos;re gonna need in the future, plus a nice cash bonus.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_11_any_03">OK, this is a fight - they will destroy the intel!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_09_03">Now we need to code the tag for access. Get it to the computer!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_05_01">Better find that computer, friends.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_02">I&apos;m going with caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_07_any_01">That&apos;s the tablet PC. Perfect.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_68_01">We need a viral concentration of 65% or more.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_20_02">Now let&apos;s rescue our friend. The cell block should be nearby.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_16_02">Remember to sneak under the cameras so they won&apos;t spot you.</string>
	 <string id="loc_brb_cbf_01">Dear Friends, we&apos;re going back to New York. Theres something buried in the foundation of the old Brooklyn Bank that Bain was after. Could be a way out of this current predicament we&apos;re in. While we&apos;re there, it might be a good idea to pick up some extra operating cash to keep us going. Replacing all of Bain&apos;s equipment isn&apos;t going to be cheap I can tell you, and the stuff I&apos;ve got running as backup isn&apos;t going to hold up for long, yeah? At the moment, we&apos;re open targets.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_15_any_02">Fuck! That&apos;s landmines. Keep off the grass and stay out of the camera view.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_98_01">They&apos;re crazy! Shooting up the building with missiles! What the hell is this?!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_02_02">There&apos;s a lot of stuff coming home. Weapons, ammo and anything that murkier elements can liberate. Check Murkywater&apos;s containers.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_05">...caustic soda?</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_11_01">A contact of mine stashed a few body bags nearby just in case.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_04_01">There&apos;s the drop. Snatch it and place it by the lab.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_11_any_02">Keep cooking people. Tempo!</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_01">Ok, you made it so far and the kerels have made an offer. I think we can hold out for more.</string>
	 <string id="bul_fex_tap01_02">You piece of shit San Dimas puta! Where the fuck is Miguel? I told you to get him half an hour ago!</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_01_01">Get into the store, watch the civilians, watch the cameras and get it done.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_26_02">Keep looking for a manual or something.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_64_02">Our patient should have a tattoo on his neck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_04_any_01">I hope you got a lot of cameras. It&apos;ll make it easier for us to find all the devices.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bigoil_stage1_intro_a_03">Ride or die - that was their motto. Well done. This intel will help us greatly. Study it closely before we hit the scientists house. Let&apos;s go get this fusion engine.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_81_02">They cut the power, get it back up! Fast! The elevator won&apos;t move otherwise.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_brf_01_03">Scout the place and hit them hard. Get those jewels and keep the civs at bay. Let&apos;s get rich!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_21">...I&apos;m 91% sure.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_01_02">Right, friends, let&apos;s keep our hostage out of trouble and safe, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_52_01">That&apos;s a proper jailbreak, my friends!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed3_brf_b_01">That truck you assholes tagged wasn&apos;t the right one, so we can forget about intercepting those voting machines. We&apos;re going to try something else to keep the Elephant sweet. We can trigger a re-election by scrambling the server at the polling place. To avoid suspicion on our sponsor, we&apos;ll make it look like collateral damage by robbing the bank next door.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_15_01">There&apos;s the main gate. Could be watched. Maybe find another way in?</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_end_a_12">If there were more crews like you I think the world would need to store its valuables elsewhere.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_brief_02">Alright. Scanning equipment is in position on the rooftop. Sneak in, take his mobile phone, laptop, hard drives, and tablet pc. Anything technical. Then bring it to the roof.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_03_any_03">This seems fishy but I don&apos;t know - get the paintings on the table and keep your spider sense tingling.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_15_03">The main gate is the quickest way in, but probably watched. Maybe other ways in?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_06_any_02">C&apos;mon, move it get into the house.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_end_stealth_01">Nice job, sneaking Vlad&apos;s dwankie brother-in-law out of there. Maybe he will stay out of trouble in the future, yeah? (Heh.. not likely...)</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_08_01">There&apos;s another guard. Stay out of sight.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_25_02">Hmm, I&apos;m not familiar with that design. Must be very unusual. Have a look in the nearby utility rooms and see of you can find a schematic.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_25_03">That&apos;s not how we do it! Never let them take you. This job is over.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_82_01">Remember where that ladder is, gang. You can access the roof there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_42_01">I&apos;ve arranged a false pager for a first-year resident, but first you need to get hold of a patient file.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_04_02a">And people are starting to talk and wonder what the hell is going on.$NL;</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_28_03">A door breaker! Couldn&apos;t have wished for anything better!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_02_03">Your next target is the voting machines. I&apos;ll bet they&apos;re stored in sealed crates. You clowns will need to improvise to open them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_04">...I think so, at least.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_14_03">There should be clues around to help you figure out the truck. Get Sherlocking. Look for open containers, they might indicate what the trucks are carrying.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_09_any_02">Good, now we need at least 3 more just like this and you need to get them to the van. It&apos;s in the parking lot next to the gallery.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_23_01">Blerrie, they took the hostage out from under your noses! We&apos;ve messed this one up good!</string>
	 <string id="pln_al1_cbf_01_01">Gensec have a brand new vault - the Investment Safe. Unbreakable, they say, and they&apos;re showcasing it at the arena. The door is made of their new compound - Vivinite. But everything has a soft spot. With a bit of C4 and a new circular cutter, we can steal their cash out right from beneath them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_07_01">That&apos;s the first machine hacked. Make sure you close up that crate. Don&apos;t want anyone getting suspicious.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_16_any_01">1600 Penn, maybe we go there for our next big score.</string>
	 <string id="elp_election_brf_speak_03">Help the citizens of DC to vote right. We need to find the ballot machines in the harbor and intercept them before they get deployed. The machines must swing votes to me!</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_11_01">Look out, tear gas!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_51_01">OK, that&apos;s the Petersson file. They got him isolated in the ICU and you gotta get to him. Time to play doctor, guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_11_02">People will pay fortunes for this ancient Babylonian shit.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_09_01">That terminal is showing which truck is going where. Keep checking. It might help pinpoint our truck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_12_02">Great. There it is. Disassemble it and then move the pieces out.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_04_01">Vlad is grateful you are doing this job. When this shit is over, and Buluc is dead, we get back to work for real, yes?</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_11_any_01">One more, keep looking.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_28_02">Use the manual to find which cable to cut, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_14">...what&apos;s the worst that could happen, right?</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_brief_01b">I&apos;ve set up the meeting location. You meet in an abandoned trainyard. Good luck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c1_02">It&apos;s caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_42_03">When you feel ready, go ahead and make your way out.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_01_01">First, see if you can get inside. You might want to try a quiet approach.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_11_any_02">Incoming! From the lumber mill! Stay on your toes!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_02_03">Keep an eye out for anything you can hustle out of there. The Murkywater containers are your best bet - get them open.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_07_02">Find some way past the gates without raising any suspicions.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_04">Look at that. The kerels must think we&apos;re idiots, making an offer so low. Let&apos;s see how far they will go, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_17">...and cross your fingers.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_15_02">Reinforcements are incoming.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_01_02">Ah hell. Heat is on the way. Guess the cops were watching the place.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_brief_01">The senator loves to collect art - outsider art in particular. Lucky for us, the Capitol Art Gallery is hosting an exhibition this week.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_02_01">You&apos;ll have about seven seconds to take out the cameras before the alarm goes off.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_19_02">Gang, you need to locate that turret.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_01_01">OK, guys. Remember:  computer, blood sample, validation and then get the hell out by the elevator. Oh, and I hope you brought something to take out the security cameras with.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_09_01">You&apos;ve been made! Damn, this is gonna get messy. Just keep hacking, I&apos;ll think of something.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_04_01">Yeah get me out of these chains man.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_14_01">Four.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_01">...caustic soda?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_12_01">Six.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_06_03">Another security buffer kicked in.Need to be disconnected manually.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_05_02">Remember, you&apos;re looking for the chief kerel&apos;s computer.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_21_02">Grab the encrypted flash drive. It should be in a laptop somewhere.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_04_02">Each vault door has a security system, and that drive will hack it open. Should be useful.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_43_01">Good! Now steal one of the police cars and get out of there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_random_stage1_brief_02">The Harvest &amp; Trustee is a vulnerable bank so I see an opportunity for us. Case it so you can find out where. You&apos;re going to need to get into the vault using a thermal drill, get whatever&apos;s in there bagged up and moved back to the escape car. Use your judgment and don&apos;t be greedy... Good luck, folks.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_17_03">The van will leave in one minute. Make sure you&apos;re in it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_end_win">Good job friends, that was some quick and easy money for us. Going to buy a lot of nice things we can use to pull off more jobs in the future, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_06_01">They&apos;ve blocked me. I need you to disconnect their security buffer.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_66_01">Crap. That&apos;s Gensec. Get ready to deal with them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_96_01">Guys, they&apos;re trying to jam the comms. Bile is on the way but he&apos;s gotta be careful. </string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_95_01">What the hell... you&apos;re not gonna ... other air units in the area.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_15_03">That&apos;s the last one. Tip toe back to the van, and we can consider this a job well done.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_01_01">OK, friends. Find Buluc&apos;s wine cellar. That&apos;s a nice, quiet way into the mansion.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_14_any_01">Look at the that view...</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_01_03">Get into docks. There&apos;ll be security, so stay hidden and stay quiet.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_53_05">That doesn&apos;t sound good! Be ready to fight!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_69_01">We&apos;re gonna need two vials. If one of them fails the test, you gotta get more blood and start again.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_20_01">That&apos;s the first one, guys. Keep working.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_45_01">You need to figure out which key goes with his car. This would really be easier if we could just take any car.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_03_01">You need to get inside the mansion walls. Use the thermite I have supplied you with, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_15_02">Okay, take a look around and see if you can find one.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_09_03">Now, the next thing is to get past the security gate so you can access the vault.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_04a_02">Right, now find a way into the mansion.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_02_02">That&apos;s the turret recovered. The driver will be back for the ammo.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_05_01">Be careful with the cooking, gentlemen.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_24_01">Keep the civilians away from the alarms.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_58_01">And there goes the escape driver. Keep going. I&apos;ll figure something out.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_07_01">Grab the raw materials and get them in the house.</string>
	 <string id="loc_mex_01_03">Find that tunnel, friends. They&apos;ve probably got it hidden, but it shouldn&apos;t be too hard to locate.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_end_01_03">Ninja&apos;s in socks tiptoeing on thick carpet make more noise than you. Expertly done!</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_17_02">All right, with that taken care of it&apos;s time to find the server room.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_01_01">Damn, looks like the cops had been staking the place. Move it!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_intro_a_02">This is the gallery.  You&apos;re looking for the paintings marked by a red sold sticker. We need at least four to make this work. The place is closed and locked down. Find a way in. Go.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_brief_02">OK, you&apos;re  in position at the trainyard. Eyes open. Watch for suits. I can&apos;t see any active vehicles nearby but that doesn&apos;t mean much. Go to the train car and wait for contact.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_14_any_01">Great! Now get them up to the station on the roof and connect them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_01_01">We&apos;re doing this nice and quiet. The computer we&apos;re looking for should be located on the second floor. </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_01_03">No time to waste. Get in there!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_16_01">You have to destroy that evidence!</string>
	 <string id="pln_at1_cbf_01_03">Gensec&apos;s overland armored convoys employ a lot of ex-military types, providing firepower and muscle, and they move everything from little Jimmy&apos;s favorite baseball card to the Crown Jewels. We got a line on a convoy moving into D.C. Let&apos;s see what we can get.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_41_02">OK, now you can take all of Vlad&apos;s special loot, but don&apos;t make too much noise.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_01_02">Get into the store, you know what to do! Let&apos;s get those jewels.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_78_01">Damn thing keeps stopping. I gotta override the system. It&apos;ll be a while until it reaches you.</string>
	 <string id="pln_esc_plan_b">I&apos;ll get you out of there. Just keep the loot safe!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed3_20_03">The surveillance operator is down. Those cameras shouldn&apos;t bother you anymore!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_07_03">The machine&apos;s done. That should make The Elephant happy. Now close up the crate and keep going.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_04_any_01">The arms deal guys... We got to get that deal exposed in the media and fast. It will create a framing effect for sure.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_11_01">The evidence storage should be on the second floor, find it and use the key tag to get in. </string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_16_01">Two.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_25_01">Well done, Dallas. Head to the van and get out of there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_04_any_03">We don&apos;t have enough paintings yet! Can someone get me access to the computer in the surveillance room, fast? I&apos;ll get it open, don&apos;t you worry about your pretty little heads.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_07_01">Watch out, friends. LMG Dozers are coming!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_29_03">Pick up the phone and let me do the talking.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_11_any_02">We have four now and four&apos;s what we need - now if you want to get more, your move.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_02_02">Keep moving and don&apos;t play around. You trigger the alarm, we&apos;re screwed.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_09_01">Who knows what&apos;s on that server. Blueprints, records - maybe the password for Area 51.</string>
	 <string id="pln_esc_02_to_arrival">Two minutes until you can get the hell out of there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_06_01">Damn, this gold was likely boosted from Saddam&apos;s palace!</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_09_01">I&apos;ll eavesdrop, relaying...</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_34_03">Right, now memorize that code, chop chop.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_12_02">You gotta find that safe, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="pln_esc_fixed_heli">Guys, I&apos;ve secured a chopper to get you out. Stay put!</string>
	 <string id="elp_framing_brf_speak_03">Now that senator Borrico has closed his little arms for gold deal, he is ripe for the taking.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_brf_01_02">Keep an eye out on the alley ways, keep those civilians down and work fast. Let&apos;s get some jewels!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_14_any_02">Great, so much for the camera alarm.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_11_02">Tear gas! Heads up!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_01">...I think.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_intro_01_02">We&apos;re here. Get inside and get your hands on the access codes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_end_01_01">Real professional gentlemen! They don&apos;t even know what hit them!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_22_any_01">Look for bookshelves, see if you can move them and find something.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_23_03">Heard a story about this guy once... hid something in a light fixture, then electrocuted himself to death by not being careful when he went to get it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_15_any_01">They&apos;ve mined the place! Watch your step!</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_07_any_02">Codes. Bring them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bigoil_stage1_intro_a_02">Looks like they expect a fight. I know you will give em one. Find the safe and the address... get as much intel from these scumbags as you can. Let&apos;s roll.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_intro_01_03">It&apos;s a dirty job, but easy money.</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_01_03">And bring me back some chimichangas or something!</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_09_03">One of Buluc&apos;s old girlfriends &quot;volunteered&quot; information after we threw some cash her way,  that you can find the way to open this door in a part of the house that Buluc calls the &quot;inner sanctum&quot;. Go find the entrance to it, chop chop.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_07_01">What? You want me to dress up like a cop??</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_05_any_03">Alright, they just need to call you back. Faster the better.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_02">Kerels are trying to take back the hostage.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_intro_01_01">OK, gang. We&apos;re here.</string>
	 <string id="elp_bigoil_brf_intro_01">Politics is as you know global - I need you for a global effort.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_05_02">Damn, that&apos;s the alarm. Get ready for action!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_06">Mmmhmm, fine fine.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_01_01">Remember we need both the Taxman and the server, people. Scare him and make him go into the limo once we&apos;ve confirmed that he has the server on him.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_cbf_01_02">This is Roberts bank. It&apos;s a small DC company, almost as old as the city itself. And while I have a lot of respect for the fine institutions of this nation, I have greater respect for what they hold in their vault. My intel says this branch has the lowest hit-rate in the country. Time to change that.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_11_any_01">OK, be careful! It will be worth sneaking all the way through, boys. No alarms and this framing will be perfect!</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_13_01">That dinges is not going to crack without causing a racket.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_00_01">Yeah yeah, just put on your mask now.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_14_02">What about taking the manager&apos;s fingerprints off something with a piece of tape, so we can bypass the scanner quietly?</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_22_02">That door is too tough for the drill. But I&apos;m sure the armory will have something that can take it out.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_03_02">That&apos;s what we are after. Get it to the van.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_03_03">GPS is online. Providing you tagged the right truck, this is great work. Time to go.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_28_03">C&apos;mon friends, the manual should show what wires you need to cut.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_07_any_01">We have to hurry! The cop&apos;s radio is buzzing like crazy. They&apos;re already on their way!</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_02_any_02">OK, no time to lose, get all that intel.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_intro_01_03">Here we are, get in there and get me required amount. We go in quiet and go out with a boom!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_07_02">Great, that one&apos;s hacked. Get that crate closed, then find another.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_end_a_02">Outstanding work. Tonight, you clowns made yourself a friend in high places. You&apos;ll never pay another parking ticket in this town.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_14_01">Yeah.. I ... I don&apos;t know .. It could have been a big gun.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_09_01">Kerels are sending in Medic Dozers with this round.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_14_02">Look around. There should be clues that will point you to the right truck. Perhaps matching their color to the containers.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_123_01">This is Roberts Bank. How may I help you today?</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_13_any_01">Alright, bring it to the van, it&apos;s right across the street.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_05">That should get the process going.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_09_04">Next step is to code the tag. Get it to the computer!</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_35_01">Open sesame, friends!</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_39_02a"> Yes, Duke lent me a book. But exactly why are these things so important, aside from their considerable monetary value?</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_01_03">First, you gotta break into the warehouse. It&apos;d be great if you can keep the noise down.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_15_01">Look inside the containers. Find what cargo they&apos;re carrying. Maybe that could help you figure out which is the right truck.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_35_01">Now cut him loose.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_14_01">Damn! Someone saw the body! Take him out before he calls it in!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_14_01">There have to be clues around the wharf that&apos;ll help you figure out which truck is carrying the machines to Washington. Keep your eyes peeled.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c1_03">Soda. Caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_random_stage1_brief_02b">You&apos;re going to need to get into the vault using a thermal drill, get whatever&apos;s in there bagged up and moved back to the escape car. Use your judgment and don&apos;t be greedy... Good luck, folks.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_06">Keep your eyes on the hostage!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_end_b_01">Things got messy, but you got through in the end. The hacks worked. It looks like the good lady Mayor&apos;s people was behind this. The press are already sharpening the knives for Schwartz. Needless to say, The Elephant is ecstatic. You have served your city well tonight, my friends.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_brief_01">OK, the cameras are installed in the paintings. We&apos;re ready. The senator&apos;s men are jumpy but ready to deal with us. So let&apos;s deal. Money for art.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_23_03">Excellent. We&apos;re almost done. Bear with me.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_03">...IF my calculations are correct.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_31_any_01">Use the camera to see when they turn on, and then turn them off again.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_01_any_02">Head over to the phone, the phone&apos;s ringing. Make the contact there.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_09_02">Don&apos;t worry, I&apos;ll lead the way.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_04_01a">Maybe you tell me what is going on with Bain and what you have planned next?$NL;</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_30_02">Knock knock! Now find the prisoner!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_09_03">The PC is showing where the trucks are headed. Keep an eye out for those bound for Washington.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_97_01">Shit guys! They got an aircraft launching rockets!</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_85_any_01">Nice. Now start her up.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_29_02">Somebody, grab the phone and let me handle it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_34_01">Nailed it. Keep going guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_09_02">That computer is showing which truck is going where. Could be valuable to know that.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_intro_04_02">They can keep wondering all they want. Payday business is no one else&apos;s.$NL;</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_intro_a_03">OK, gallery&apos;s just ahead. Watch out for motion detectors, cameras and guards. Get in there and bring me four of the paintings marked with a red sold sticker. Time is ticking guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_93_01">Awesome. Now just sit tight for 30 floors...</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_05_03">That&apos;s one of the voting machines. Great job! Alright, when the coast is clear, get the hack started. </string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_18_any_03">Intel guys, intel! Get it!</string>
	 <string id="elp_election_brf_speak_02">Gentlemen - today we vote. They say: one man, one vote. I say: four men and lots of votes. I need you to rig the voting machines in my district.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_28_01">Check the schematic and find the right wires!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_intro_02">You need to get in there, get our man out, and destroy whatever incriminating evidence the kerels are keeping on him. Got it?</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_24_03">Gage sorted a dumpster to stash a bit of loot in. His people will collect it in the morning.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_04_01">Those shipping crates are sealed tighter than a gnat&apos;s asshole. You need to find something to break them open.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_15_02">Maybe the contents of those shipping containers can help you figure out which is our truck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_23_03">I like the sweet sound of that! Now, leave it be for a few seconds and we should be in the clear.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_02_03">This place is running low on supplies. If you wanna go for more ingredients, signal the chopper with a flare. This pilot&apos;s on the clock, so make it worth while. Or you can bounce. Your call.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_56_01">Alright, one more minute til the time lock opens the vault.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_17_01">One.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_11_any_01">OK, we can leave now, but try and take it all if you can.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_38_any_01">It&apos;s open! Bag the gold!</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_44_01">Uh, Barney&apos;s not available right now. Can I take a message?</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_03_any_01">You can access the hidden cameras in the paintings with the laptop on the roof.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_08_02">The bluechip hired henchmen are here.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_05_02">That certainly looks like one of the voting machines. When you&apos;re ready to kill democracy, start the hack. Make sure no-one sees you.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_06_02">The van had to leave. He&apos;ll be back, keep your eyes out for the new location.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_86_any_01">Here we go. We should be through in a couple of minutes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_13_01">Check the camera and see what&apos;s in the vault.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_26_01">Found a schematic yet?</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_03_02">We&apos;re not going in by the main entrance. You see that fence? That&apos;s our way in.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_20_03">Time for the main act, getting our friend out. Look for the cell block, it should be nearby.</string>
	 <string id="pln_esc_start">Watch out, guys! The cops are surrounding you!</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_40_any_01">It&apos;s open! Let&apos;s see what we got!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_30_any_01">Use his computer again, be careful, they only go down for a small amount of time.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_brief_02b">Search well and eyes peeled for guards. </string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_01_03">Okay friends, time to crack this nut. Find a way in.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_brf_01">I&apos;ve traced the truck to a warehouse out by Goose Island. It&apos;s a distribution depot, contracted to ship the voting machines to their final destination. With a little technical wizardry, we&apos;re going to make those machines a bit more sympathetic to The Elephant&apos;s mayoral candidate - that slimy ballbag McKendrick. Get in there, get them hacked, get out - simple. Once again, The Elephant is extending his stealth bonus if you can keep it quiet.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_06_02">Gold bullion. Probably taken from the enemies of freedom. </string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_23_01">The armory, friends. Try following the smell of gun oil?</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_intro_01">Get ready friends, we&apos;re almost at the target site.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_09_03">That&apos;s how much we need. You guys can stay and get more if you feel like you are on a roll!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_12_any_01">Two more, keep on searching.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bigoil_stage1_brief_01">The Elephant gave us the locations of the biker gang hunting for the scientist&apos;s little device. I think they&apos;re close to finding him - we need their intel so we can get to him first.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_89_02">That should be all the clues. You should be able to figure out how to open it up now.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_24_01">Gage has arranged for one of the dumpsters to be used to stash some loot. </string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_14_01">Alright, that&apos;ll keep Gage sweet. You guys can cash this out now, or stay for more.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_brf_02">The Elephant&apos;s PR will claim he came to power through depth, leadership and integrity, but that&apos;s bullshit. That oily bastard&apos;s going to cheat his way to the Senate, and this is where you come in. There are trucks at Pier 39. One of them has voting machines. Find the truck and attach a GPS-tracker to it. We&apos;ll deal with it down the line. Naturally, The Elephant wants this done with as little chance of bad press coming back to him as possible. So he&apos;s ear-marked some of his considerable campaign funds for a special black-ops bonus. You guys do this quietly, and the good politician will see you well rewarded.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_19_01">Use the kitchen blender to make an evidence cocktail.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_07_01">You&apos;ve got to find a way past the gates.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_04_01">They&apos;ve seen you! The trucks are moving out. Alright, we need a Plan B. Lemme think.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_37_02">Bliksem! Don&apos;t disturb those lasers! Can&apos;t find anything in the blueprints about them. Probably added later. That kind of system can usually be disabled via the roof.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_13_04">See if you can find the evidence. It should be here somewhere!</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_01_any_03">Ready for the shot? OK listen: you are looking for the paintings marked with red stickers. They&apos;ve got unusually tight security here. A lot of cameras, even a security room, so do your homework.</string>
	 <string id="gsc_cs1_11_01">Yeah, tell him his ass is on the line if he isn&apos;t available for the regular time-lock check in.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_03">There&apos;s an offer on the table. Not enough in Locke&apos;s humble opinion. Let&apos;s hold out for more, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_25_02">You&apos;re not supposed to get captured, you chops! We gotta give this one up.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_02_02">You got one of the keycards, now find the other one.</string>
	 <string id="nmh_intro_06_01">Did you press the right floor? Press the right floor!</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_02a_02">For a murdering low-life cartel gangster, this guy knows his wine. Shame you don&apos;t have time to take some back.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_tap02_01a">Vlad, we don&apos;t have time for this.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_intro_a_01">Pull over here. There&apos;s the warehouse up ahead. Let&apos;s do this.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_24_04">Looks like the key tag needs a higher level coding for the armory. You&apos;ll have to recode it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_07_02">Looks like LMG Dozers are part of the assault this time.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_end_a_01">That was an excellent piece of whisper-work. They didn&apos;t know you were there. Now let&apos;s see where that truck leads us.</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_15_01">I&apos;m gonna need the car key here, guys.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_22_01">They&apos;re going for the hostage. Stop them!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_intro_a_02">That&apos;s the depot where the machines are kept. Move out, you clowns.</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_32_01">You should be searching, not dawdling.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_126_01">Roberts Bank. Everything&apos;s under control. How can I help you?</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_19_07">Bah, that offer is for chops. We can make them do better fo&apos; sho&apos;. Stay frosty, friends.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_07_03">We&apos;ve learned that most of the time, you can find Buluc in his office brooding over something, so it&apos;s a good place to look for him. Find it, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="loc_bex_13_02">Oh, dear. You&apos;re not going to break that open without making a lotta noise.</string>
	 <string id="loc_fex_tap01_02a">Just your friendly neighborhood kek, yeah?</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_05_01">Blerrie, They&apos;re sending in Cuff Cloakers along with this group.</string>
	 <string id="hnc_man_01_02">Mr. Sturr, I presume? You got the data? </string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_43_02">I&apos;m putting you through to our CEO. Please hold.</string>
	 <string id="elp_election_brf_speak_01">The voting will begin tomorrow. We need to act now to make a difference. New voting machines have arrived in the harbor.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_15_02">Now find some way to destroy it!</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_37_01">We need to get him out of that prisoner outfit. Find him a spare police uniform!</string>
	 <string id="alm_pex_01_01">What... hey! Did Vlad send you to get me out?</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_07_02">Their doors open with coded key tags. See if you can find a blank one that we can code.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_11_02">Use your key to get into the evidence storage. It should be on the second floor.</string>
	 <string id="loc_pex_22_04">No drill will break that door. But the armory might have something that can take care of it.</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_09_02">Medic Dozers coming as well. Bunch of kakspul!</string>
	 <string id="loc_skm_26_02">Good job, everyone. That chop gave us an OK bundle of money to take home, but next time maybe we&apos;ll do better.</string>
	 <string id="pln_at1_cbf_01_01">I&apos;m sure you guys have tangled with Gensec before. They&apos;re the East Coast&apos;s premier provider of security solutions, if you believe their brochure. But, PR aside, these guys are serious. Today, we hit them.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bigoil_stage1_brief_02">Yeah, they&apos;re ready for us judging by the number of lookouts... Looks like they have cameras too. Make sure you get close before you hit &apos;em.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_02_any_01">OK guys, search the place. They have a safe somewhere, it&apos;s probably in there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_bo1_03_any_03">Check the safe - find it. Fast!</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_random_stage1_intro_a_03">Everyone, you know how it&apos;s done. My guy dropped the thermal drill in the parking lot, so grab that before you make your move inside. Some surveillance would be smart.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_35_any_01">Now it&apos;s just a matter of time.</string>
	 <string id="pln_branchbank_stage1_35_any_03">Dammit. Now we go the painful way.</string>
	 <string id="pln_cs1_brf_01">We got a bank here. Not a big branch but I&apos;ve learned the vault is temporarily holding stacks of cash in transit. Foreign exchange notes. Anyway, you know how to do it - your way. Sneak in silent, or unleash hell. Either way, I got a little idea for how to lift the money out of there. You&apos;ll see what I mean. I think you&apos;ll like it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_02_01">Alright. You&apos;re in. Now hunt around. There&apos;s gotta be a clue about which truck is carrying the voting machines to Washington. Search containers, check computers - anything you can to figure out the right truck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_02_03">OK, now look around. We need to tag the truck headed for Washington. Look around for clues. Containers, terminals, any records. Find the right one, and tag it.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_03_01">Tracker placed. Signal coming through. Now haul ass, and let&apos;s hope we&apos;re chasing Elephant&apos;s machines.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_03_02">Getting a nice clear signal. Time to leave, guys. I hope you tagged the right truck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_04_02">Crap! You were seen, and the convoy is rolling out. We need another way to find our truck.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_04_03">The trucks are on the move. Someone saw you! OK, time for another plan.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_15_03">Those containers have cargo. That might help you eliminate the wrong trucks.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_16_01">One of these trucks is the one we want. When you&apos;ve finished searching for clues, get the tag on the truck you think is our target. You get one chance, so make sure you&apos;re certain.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed1_intro_a_02">Pier 39. Find the truck that has the voting machines. It will be bound for Washington. Figure out which one it is, slap on the tracker and get the hell out. Keep it quiet.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed2_end_b_02">Great work! The hacked machines have made it look like the Mayor&apos;s people were behind this. Even if an enquiry exonerates her, the papers are hurling so many buckets of shit at the Mayor that she&apos;s finished. And The Elephant? Well, his man is picking out new furniture for City Hall. Great work, gang!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ed3_20_02">That&apos;ll keep nosy bastards from spying on our business. Good.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ff3_09_any_01">What a flat! These arms deals sure are a nice addition to his senator pay.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_cbf_01_01">Theres a jewelry store downtown, fairly simple target. But be ready for the heat if the alarm goes off.</string>
	 <string id="pln_fj1_cbf_01_02">The new jewelry store down town is loaded with jewels. Those could be ours. You want to pay them a visit?</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_09_any_01">Great, we need at least 3 more, get it to the van. It&apos;s in the parking lot next to the gallery.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage1_brief_01b">You need to take the marked paintings to the senator&apos;s apartment. They&apos;ll have cameras installed in them. Eyes on the inside will make your job easier, trust me.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_01_any_01">OK people, get the phone. Let&apos;s get this trade out of the way.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_05_any_02">OK, now let&apos;s just hope they call you fast.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_07_any_01">OK folks, everyone into the train.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage2_09_any_01">OK now remember, one bag of cash for every painting. </string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_17_any_01">OK! We&apos;re gold. I think I got everything we need. You should be able to access his desktop computer now.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_18_any_01">It&apos;s located in his office.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_20_any_01">There&apos;s just a little problem... I don&apos;t actually know where the vault is, physically.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_27_any_01">If you want to go for more, use his desktop PC, it should open the vault up for you.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_29_any_01">We have to shut them off.</string>
	 <string id="pln_framing_stage3_end_a_01">Drugs planted, senator framed. Bad guys 1, Politicians 0. Well done, very smooth operation in there. The Elephant will love this outcome.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_01_03">That&apos;s the depot. You know what you need to do, but keep it quiet. If the alarm goes, I&apos;ll have to pull you out.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_04_03">A nice stash of used dinars. Good find.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_05_01">I hope they weren&apos;t giving this marching powder to our boys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_05_02">This coke won&apos;t be funding any more terrorism. Just good old American crime.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_05_03">Columbian. Bolivian. Mexican. Wherever it&apos;s from, it&apos;s ours now.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_07_02">Rifles, pistols and bullets. This will make Gage happy.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_13_03">The vault needs two cards, entered almost simultaneously. You can bet there&apos;s something particularly tasty in there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_16_01">Those Murkywater containers are brought direct from the world&apos;s hotspots. Crack them open. They&apos;ll be your best bet for loot.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_17_01">The driver&apos;s gonna bail! Make sure you&apos;re with him.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_20_02">A good start.</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_22_01">That&apos;s the armor of Oda Nabunaga. Bag the pieces. If that&apos;s genuine...</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_23_01">I can&apos;t believe we scored Oda&apos;s armor. Outstanding work!</string>
	 <string id="pln_ko1_end_01_02">That was text-book whisper mode, guys. Great work.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_11_02">Okay, keep an eye on what&apos;s happening. We want to actually see the server.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_13_02">He put something inside his shirt. </string>
	 <string id="pln_man_17_01">WHAT! Guys get your heads down.</string>
	 <string id="pln_man_brf_01">The Taxman thought he was clever making a deal with a big corporation, but the information leaked, and now bigger sharks want in - all in. We have a complete, run-down building to ourselves, overlooking the deal. We&apos;ve got a set-up installed. Alex will help with the crane. Scare the Taxman into his limo, shake him up, and he&apos;ll be sure to give us the server and the codes. When it&apos;s about $25,000,000, anything goes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_misc_sj_dgh_02_01">You killed one of them? Damn, I can&apos;t say the prick didn&apos;t deserve it, but Wick wanted the pleasure himself.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_05_01">You got nine cameras to take care of.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_112_01">Great, now down the ramp and get outside.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_115_01">Whoa. Close one guys. How you feeling?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_11_01">Seven.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_18_01">Ok, that takes care of the cameras.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_25_01">There goes the alarm. Guess we gotta do this the hard way.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_32_04">Hello, B-uhm... nurse Bain speaking. What do you need?</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_33_04">Really? Ok, we&apos;ll be here.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_35_03">They sounded convinced. We&apos;re in the clear for now.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_37_01">Guys, you got guards coming. Take them out before they find anything.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_40_01">There&apos;s a repair man coming to check the cameras.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_43_01">You gotta find the patient file, guys.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_48_01">Whoa, that didn&apos;t take long!</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_52_02">OK, gotta find a way to make sure none of the hostages does anything stupid. Set up the fake sentry guns.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_58_02">Don&apos;t forget- stay in character.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_60_02">Door to the ICU is open, get in there and find that patient.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_61_01">If that&apos;s the wrong room, we&apos;ll have to cut the other doors with a saw. We gotta get that blood sample...</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_71_04">Still not enough, you need to take another sample.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_79_01">Maybe... two minutes. IF I don&apos;t get interrupted.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_92_03">Come on guys, express elevator... going up as soon as you push the button.</string>
	 <string id="pln_nmh_94_01">That&apos;s strange... merc units are pulling out. </string>
	 <string id="pln_pal_cbf_01">Pack your bags, gang. This one is south of the Mason-Dixie. We&apos;re going after Mitchell and Wilson - couple of counterfeiters down in Pensacola. Running a printing operation out of his basement. It&apos;s a discreet operation, and this guy&apos;s work is solid, so he&apos;s making serious bank. Let&apos;s grab a piece!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_10_any_01">Here they come guys. Choppers and SWAT vans all over the place around you. Stay on your toes!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_11_any_01">SWATs incoming from the lumber mill. Keep them away!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_11_any_03">They are coming in from the lumber mill, watch out!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_12_any_01">They are coming from the railway bridge! Watch out!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_13_any_01">SWATs are incoming from the forest next to the road, be careful!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_18_any_01">Remember to be careful! We can not use the wrong ingredient. You need to be careful!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_28_any_01">The process is done! Bag it up, and let&apos;s do another round.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_29_any_01">Get the bags to the van to secure them. Don&apos;t let the cops run away with your hard earned meth!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rats_stage1_34_any_01">Good thinking! Use those boards to barricade more windows.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_02_02">There are only a few ingredients left. You want more, just use a flare to signal the helicopter. He&apos;s got what you need for cooking more. Or you can bug out now. Up to you.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_03_02">OK, now wait for the pilot.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_05_03">Great. Let&apos;s cook a little more product. Just don&apos;t set anything on fire.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_08_01">We can&apos;t use the lab anymore, it&apos;s gone</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_brf_01_01">This is a simple job, but that doesn&apos;t mean it will be easy. We&apos;re going to head out to the forest. You remember the place. We did some work for Hector out there. Anyway, I scoped the place out and it is still intact. So, we&apos;re headed there to cook up as much meth as we can. You can stay as long as you want. If you run out of supplies, I&apos;ll get more flown in. Should be easy money.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_cbf_01_01">You guys remember that sketchy old house out in the forest? Where Hector&apos;s guys were cooking up meth? Well, we&apos;re headed back there. </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1b_intro_01_02">This is the place. It&apos;s hardly changed.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_01_any_01">They turned the power off! The lights are down.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_01_any_02">They cut the power to the house! Lights are down.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_01_any_03">Cops killed the lights - get it back on.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_06_any_01">Get into the house.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_01">Good,OK, the reaction seems fine, keep going. </string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_04">OK, OK good.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_05">Alright on this webpage. What did you just add? Alright. OK, OK.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_07">OK, let&apos;s try that.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_08">OK, solid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_12_any_10">Legit... I&apos;m sure. Cooking fine.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_14_any_03">Shit, you got crawlers outside. Watch those windows!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_01">Alright, let&apos;s see...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_02">Hold on...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_04">So, next step iiis...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_05">Now we need...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_06">Alright, next ingredient...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_a_09">Uh, if I read this correctly... uh...</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b1_01">Muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b1_03">Acid. Muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b2_02">Oh I&apos;m going with muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_b2_03">We&apos;ll go with muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_03">We&apos;ll go with caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_c2_06">Oh I&apos;m going with caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d1_01">Hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d2_01">...hydrogen chloride?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d2_02">I&apos;m going with hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_d2_03">We&apos;ll go with hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_03">You got some of that somewhere?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_04">That should get things cooking.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_09">Add some.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_e_10">Pour it in.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_02">Hold up!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_08">Wait!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_f_09">Hold it! You didn&apos;t put it in yet, right?</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_g_05">Yeah it&apos;s acid, muriatic acid.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_h_02">It should be caustic soda!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_h_03">That should&apos;a been caustic soda!</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_h_08">By method of elimination it has to be caustic soda.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_i_07">I messed up. It should&apos;a been hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_i_08">By method of elimination it has to be hydrogen chloride.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_07">...for sure. Or, most likely.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_08">...that&apos;s my best guess.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_10">...it has to be.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_13">...this website better be accurate.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_16">...yeah... yeah.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_18">...and kiss your lucky charms.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_22">...I&apos;m 86% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_23">...I&apos;m 84% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_26">...I&apos;m 68% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_27">...I&apos;m 65.5% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rt1_j_28">...I&apos;m 57% sure.</string>
	 <string id="pln_rvd_cbf_01">Guys, we need to talk about what happened up in Alaska, but I&apos;ve got another job first, while you&apos;re still out west. So, the son of an old friend of mine in L.A., member of the Cabot crime family needs help hitting a jewelry store for a haul of diamonds. I owe him big from years ago, when his dad got me out of a jam, so I promised him a little extra muscle as payback. These guys are pro&apos;s, real characters. They even use code names! You guys up for it?</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_02_03">Keep moving and get inside.This might be a game to you, but there are guards all around.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_04_02">Hurry! Answer his pager before they raise the alarm. Try and improvise or something.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_05_01">Okay, good. Now, bag that body and get it out of sight before someone comes looking.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_06_02">How about that dumpster?</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_06_03">That dumpster should do the trick.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_07_02">Okay, good. Now, keep going.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_09_01">Eh, screw it. It doesn&apos;t look like you&apos;ll be able to pass him undetected. Take him out.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_10_03">Remember to hide that body.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_12_03">I got your back this time, but in the future you&apos;ll have to pay for these kinds of &quot;special&quot; favors. My contacts are good people and they expect good money in return.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_16_01">Behind those crates should do. Now, get the other guy. Remember to grab another body bag.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_19_03">We&apos;re lucky that Control-Guy is stupid as hell, but he&apos;s getting suspicious. Next time he&apos;ll most likely sound the alarm.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_20_03">Throw him down there where no one should find him.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_28_02">Easy now, Speedy Gonzales. Hang back and let him pass first.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh11_intro_01_01">All right, this is the place. Remember, we&apos;re here for the access codes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_05_03">Use the ECM Jammer to disable the camera, that way you can lockpick the door undetected.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_08_01">Damn it, Dallas! I told you to use the ECM Jammer. Destroying it will draw unnecessary attention.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_12_01">Now get back inside and look for the computer.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_13_03">Sneak by it and look for the security room. If we do that, we can disable all cameras at once.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_18_01">Answer the pager and we should be fine. The cameras won&apos;t present any more trouble.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_24_03">Bring the flash drive with you and get out of there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_27_02">I stashed some more body bags if you need some. Always plan ahead, Dallas. Always plan ahead.</string>
	 <string id="pln_sh12_brf_01_01">All right, Dallas. It&apos;s time to use those access codes we stole last night. Find a way inside the building - access the Police database and delete all the intel they have on Crime.Net. This won&apos;t be a walk in the park, so show me you still got what it takes.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_01_03">Damn! Alright, I&apos;m sending the drill.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_04_03">We can hack open a train vault if you plug that hard-drive into its security panel.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_07_01">I&apos;m reconnected. Thanks.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_07_03">Alright, I&apos;m back in.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1b_cbf_01_01">The blueprint you found was for a new Type of Turret. It looks like the government is transporting it soon. If we act fast, we can catch them off guard and steal it without anyone noticing.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_01_03">An access card. Great! That will help you get silent access to a railcar.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_02_01">We can sell those shells, if you can carry them out. But focus on the turret.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_08_03">Gently does it. Very gently.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_13_03">OK, we&apos;re into the railcar. Use the camera to see what&apos;s inside.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_29_03">One high-tech, high-value piece of military badass right there.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_brf_01_01">That blueprint you found was for a new type of infantry turret - codenamed RC1. Real next-gen shit. Digging a little deeper, I got word of a specially chartered train, headed in to the Pentagon. I&apos;ve hacked the rail network, and they think they&apos;ve stopped due to a glitch in the switches. Three railcars. One has the hardware. The other two have its ammo. It all sells, but your priority is the turret. They won&apos;t be expecting you.</string>
	 <string id="pln_tr1_intro_01_02">You need to get close and locate the right railcar. Once you&apos;ve ID&apos;d it, look around - you might be able to find an access card for the railcars.</string>
	 <string id="txm_man_02_01">... Nice. I&apos;ll get the server.</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_01_01">You need to tell them that shit? What are they, you treat them like babies?</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_04_01">You think they have lots of goats in Mexico?</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_09_01">What is taking so much time?</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_15_03">You got... Is old family thing. Don&apos;t you mind... just get it out of there!</string>
	 <string id="vld_bex_29_01">Just start shooting, that gets people moving!</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_intro_04_03">Ok, ok... you just remember what I told you. Shit can come back to stalk you.$NL;</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap02_01">Hey guys... listen to this.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap02_01b">Sure we do! Listen...</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap05_01">Oh, that piece of shit is going to wish he had not fucked with Vlad.</string>
	 <string id="vld_fex_tap05_03">Such a waste, all this space, for that Mexican shit and his Coyopas...</string>
</resources>